[{"questionId": 1, "questionText": "KIQ7RW88N9TBZ6M6XOPZY49QG7R99X9I0VLJW0FJIVJ1HIT3MNSZD6F54ATCRE37NEIFTLVTL10NVC7OLNCW5EA4RMXKV33GOWAFW", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "3.KGAXD2BMLNBPHQS9SUC701EQ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.3X38AP8SZ336T4P5V6WU9ZARZGCBH4E6", "2.3SQ9RNRAC119OJBK74L20IY5LH69Q"], "questionOptions": ["1.3X38AP8SZ336T4P5V6WU9ZARZGCBH4E6", "2.3SQ9RNRAC119OJBK74L20IY5LH69Q", "3.KGAXD2BMLNBPHQS9SUC701EQ"], "answerLink": "LRQZRONN8X"}, {"questionId": 2, "questionText": "T30EN5I2Q3CW6XB6FDNYN684VDIRA38WKBE6IJI94QL5FH2D9ZRE6YX5NX2KZIAHBOYKFE2YOMZRUSA", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "1.16I46NR02XX3R3BE5N2Y2OG1E5809UQ", "wrongAnswers": ["2.XRDWW4FU8K11JXQNLU", "3.618ZC4G9XID80KWICIBTJCSBGGCKGTT"], "questionOptions": ["1.16I46NR02XX3R3BE5N2Y2OG1E5809UQ", "2.XRDWW4FU8K11JXQNLU", "3.618ZC4G9XID80KWICIBTJCSBGGCKGTT"], "answerLink": "4WMR39U3WD"}, {"questionId": 3, "questionText": "C2WPDLF4VTX7SGTL7IHPSH8VQVKSCUTBM4BXR4Y2KJ0W2TF26UOPNMBJ27SN62B4J2VIQDZG6V", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "1.3D77QM0MN4B8XZ3N", "wrongAnswers": ["2.H5VSBQ4JDH02C3BAEQN", "3.7WK5PAPI6BG76MD8A9QK4PZG"], "questionOptions": ["1.3D77QM0MN4B8XZ3N", "2.H5VSBQ4JDH02C3BAEQN", "3.7WK5PAPI6BG76MD8A9QK4PZG"], "answerLink": "LKSBLH0B0E"}, {"questionId": 4, "questionText": "IBJPAF6MNPB1C3KHH1W5DJXETNOLDSVTOGIQL614II07TIWBA0CSCHAIUKLNP80XF9UHRYXIIUI1I3BBG6B5153BHW3VBBG", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "1.I65QPHKEHNWE4S1RIK7Q96HO", "wrongAnswers": ["2.K0I4LR00MAWQRI5ZYXEXHRBC947WUS95", "3.O7YF7U0075EH6FTJ8Q7RLK8"], "questionOptions": ["1.I65QPHKEHNWE4S1RIK7Q96HO", "2.K0I4LR00MAWQRI5ZYXEXHRBC947WUS95", "3.O7YF7U0075EH6FTJ8Q7RLK8"], "answerLink": "9SZ0MWHAK0"}, {"questionId": 5, "questionText": "395QIRCYW4NJ6GWZTGB0QTVCWXSKGAU8GVHMMCTE9C26YOPK1RMD0SDEZIN0L3L852W2VFWWFDGPX4NFU7M285EEZZE", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "2.UQ5O7VZ8QJ7I2JYKEZL5QMIKH", "wrongAnswers": ["1.TGSAY0MV8CU9GYEUOZT5VS", "3.4J7359RDI5KNPKCY8ZKZY"], "questionOptions": ["1.TGSAY0MV8CU9GYEUOZT5VS", "2.UQ5O7VZ8QJ7I2JYKEZL5QMIKH", "3.4J7359RDI5KNPKCY8ZKZY"], "answerLink": "G1XLH7S45I"}, {"questionId": 6, "questionText": "1G80KDCHQES66F9S1GCPMS2YV4PC98SN6PVOJ5TT2NFXJF62CJOJFFS6QHGY5FE88IZ5ICPXNNTZX3", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "1.PNO3T3GX4FY7EQKBU", "wrongAnswers": ["2.SF6Q2CWZQKUD4A7I6JTNC80", "3.0JLYSMG3W1BWVU0AGRX5Q"], "questionOptions": ["1.PNO3T3GX4FY7EQKBU", "2.SF6Q2CWZQKUD4A7I6JTNC80", "3.0JLYSMG3W1BWVU0AGRX5Q"], "answerLink": "P9M1QW7EUL"}, {"questionId": 7, "questionText": "4ZB9Z0U4BGD2PV7AWCXM07U46PTN0RNWYJX4VA32JKQVXHIC3H57TEFETTJSU6Z5KOA36EZORSCMWW5KZ4I5ZMYIXK33HUZEAI35XYVAJDPOL2H6CN9X7VBG2VF", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "2.PS6T0LJ35RRSSDPZUFIKVOVT32C1SZ8", "wrongAnswers": ["1.IP98T4H7WC0ZT651LD0OOY0XFRC", "3.GAPEDYFI5F1EQDM5E15XOUS"], "questionOptions": ["1.IP98T4H7WC0ZT651LD0OOY0XFRC", "2.PS6T0LJ35RRSSDPZUFIKVOVT32C1SZ8", "3.GAPEDYFI5F1EQDM5E15XOUS"], "answerLink": "WOH0ZPG9RY"}, {"questionId": 8, "questionText": "3W7LYQXZLAF4R9NXMSX1JPF2NS1LTZQG6QTZZVIHFNA5L1GAVZ63RLJE2E245RVHD3TMGFSEU6SFY82Z7", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "3.I6S9JSFDGCYQ3X40YNNG7IJEIALL", "wrongAnswers": ["1.T9JOLI75URQ05GQ40KAOIYDAPX8B9AL6", "2.AXGOCOZQU7PV3U04EOBE"], "questionOptions": ["1.T9JOLI75URQ05GQ40KAOIYDAPX8B9AL6", "2.AXGOCOZQU7PV3U04EOBE", "3.I6S9JSFDGCYQ3X40YNNG7IJEIALL"], "answerLink": "ALEFD2KAP9"}, {"questionId": 9, "questionText": "FIYXUDV8IFU9T6H14R8W7XWLZWMO9A1N20LZPER6WSDGXOL3FDQL6L00RWBW2S1O8BG20CNGYP1TEO3T512XZ41X9JZUYZO9XJV9H22TL5BGKH2Q8XR0A34SP9ECR20", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "2.MN0IX29GZJQQLSIV4AD7YH", "wrongAnswers": ["1.QUGORO0JFFUCCPXKEY", "3.K4FWYAIWF3W0BAPUHWPE8ZWK"], "questionOptions": ["1.QUGORO0JFFUCCPXKEY", "2.MN0IX29GZJQQLSIV4AD7YH", "3.K4FWYAIWF3W0BAPUHWPE8ZWK"], "answerLink": "NME1LG3F3M"}, {"questionId": 10, "questionText": "C4UII3KVZNF8ALM4CAMSUHTJA5YW39YKA9WCHMPJUEUI3U5NSG1UE8ILKHASCEE946WVTBFRCTKGZ13J24KND465B1ZGI8CVDY2IU5W3MC6H92", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "1.HQINM2H1FVCTUE2O0", "wrongAnswers": ["2.4963LO67RNWQ90ZTZ", "3.MGKWNL80HBAQFWZA"], "questionOptions": ["1.HQINM2H1FVCTUE2O0", "2.4963LO67RNWQ90ZTZ", "3.MGKWNL80HBAQFWZA"], "answerLink": "8X20C6EJ8Q"}, {"questionId": 11, "questionText": "JJ68S6RMP961OEG4WPUZ614T4S83CJVIT6UMVYZUIPTEA6586PCAPVLQT8EVUHV4PMK0Y79YDAJSJ8NXVQD3VF5OAJ4JOF69VUEWTG", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "3.Q71Y6S92YA7N8V66OEM", "wrongAnswers": ["1.O33P0222U4JQFHFCVVPHR", "2.5MN490JEM9RE8D0HS5UR0"], "questionOptions": ["1.O33P0222U4JQFHFCVVPHR", "2.5MN490JEM9RE8D0HS5UR0", "3.Q71Y6S92YA7N8V66OEM"], "answerLink": "UDIV4NBLML"}, {"questionId": 12, "questionText": "HM3EBA0NL5E68E2FV70J8MCG83NB6KQUQUSH9MF3EENK2B775BV2DNK2HO5E9YQQXNRBTN24LQCL0", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "3.DQAU9JKIQHFQ3LK8GT2HS75K3DM62UX", "wrongAnswers": ["1.WQP7C0DK2ACY18URU8ACKHKWR9ULMW", "2.ADEV6SUUFSCND1ZRE75G"], "questionOptions": ["1.WQP7C0DK2ACY18URU8ACKHKWR9ULMW", "2.ADEV6SUUFSCND1ZRE75G", "3.DQAU9JKIQHFQ3LK8GT2HS75K3DM62UX"], "answerLink": "T40PQ0A783"}, {"questionId": 13, "questionText": "IGQY0RZCQZX5ESFZD6M3KGL2KGZI6PM5U9AC65M9TJ2MZVWUWNTP7UCPHQIMT9HP9TN6551333KGZ6TN5SC55DVT20NADMU1PN4CJHWJD9", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "1.B5LUZNDHZKL8MGPFHT70HV7Z14X5", "wrongAnswers": ["2.L8FGB5HV10T7BK5UL730", "3.M3CMVO5D00GFOEFCOTBM2UXO6TLJD6"], "questionOptions": ["1.B5LUZNDHZKL8MGPFHT70HV7Z14X5", "2.L8FGB5HV10T7BK5UL730", "3.M3CMVO5D00GFOEFCOTBM2UXO6TLJD6"], "answerLink": "XCYZFY7DTO"}, {"questionId": 14, "questionText": "4RDTV3RYT08XPVSJGT7SRF0RXUV1YRD8XFPJVLLR6SWSUH54TFECV5ATUW92DSALNFGGW2XCDT", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "3.KUXPSXR03KLCUN5V", "wrongAnswers": ["1.S7LLIZ7765MPCDX17DTET", "2.M7RNK6EAZOBOGBBW"], "questionOptions": ["1.S7LLIZ7765MPCDX17DTET", "2.M7RNK6EAZOBOGBBW", "3.KUXPSXR03KLCUN5V"], "answerLink": "IT2S0Q57TL"}, {"questionId": 15, "questionText": "NTGZSOF95D83UXK2YL3XV72OQSJAXREAMHTJDO90DGED1MI6BNS2A8X0EW6MWVJRJ5O9C6M7MTYF46QFVZ6PRWSWRP43CCZCDQVAI2AKKTZNI", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "2.MV0GS1S6QL8U5JML3X", "wrongAnswers": ["1.NPT4QH733C5ADZ8XYR3BYE3", "3.0L0YFH4HYXVYWYRR3SLY1DIF048M"], "questionOptions": ["1.NPT4QH733C5ADZ8XYR3BYE3", "2.MV0GS1S6QL8U5JML3X", "3.0L0YFH4HYXVYWYRR3SLY1DIF048M"], "answerLink": "ZF1XYG7TT2"}, {"questionId": 16, "questionText": "9CAC4GNAO8SBT2PBG091IMIJ1DJJU1GNE0QYNH2X6YA60WBEC170QPZ4HN2DS2H4DYZ16DIQ24GZB0JOZT", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "3.7HEM3HC69IQNAX7OJE3RHR", "wrongAnswers": ["1.RIXAEBTYV44ULRANLC9X2NKEO8PQ", "2.VT5JGOIEE69HTU0VCMRMI"], "questionOptions": ["1.RIXAEBTYV44ULRANLC9X2NKEO8PQ", "2.VT5JGOIEE69HTU0VCMRMI", "3.7HEM3HC69IQNAX7OJE3RHR"], "answerLink": "MIF0T7ZIWW"}, {"questionId": 17, "questionText": "U45XW5GS2YXPLKAHEKPJN8H8MZETJO23QOEB4VWEMITSK4KG73ELWPFJH06JM0PM5F5VORKIEO6VB6MXXZUC", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "1.WXCR29JU9JH1RLUKMH41", "wrongAnswers": ["2.70FPRMHZUSOI29KN2QPD2UW", "3.DMSBNOGECJQRZ11EOYLN"], "questionOptions": ["1.WXCR29JU9JH1RLUKMH41", "2.70FPRMHZUSOI29KN2QPD2UW", "3.DMSBNOGECJQRZ11EOYLN"], "answerLink": "T00581UZEW"}, {"questionId": 18, "questionText": "3DB384FHW1BI02EFBNHS6KVX18AEP3UGZZIGTQIXXS38C96QZKU5JJMKXYW5OXVWZT", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "3.55K9FZOU65OTY856YGD7", "wrongAnswers": ["1.1H05DVJSCS0DT0TXJP", "2.D9UA3WDO12U6USU86HVI5GS4I0QS"], "questionOptions": ["1.1H05DVJSCS0DT0TXJP", "2.D9UA3WDO12U6USU86HVI5GS4I0QS", "3.55K9FZOU65OTY856YGD7"], "answerLink": "FIHXQUHPJC"}, {"questionId": 19, "questionText": "38XFI5LAQRG021Z1988U9A8DKMS2MQ3XMDC15MPZF1Q1TDMXO29QWSNPFS1DQZ1LXGHKAF2UXZV", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "3.AY2Q4I4N1X4X4CGJ2Q55QP", "wrongAnswers": ["1.EGO4A82IJOSKDVXD9RIB", "2.J8V33KRVEVF0KW68T4V8X7MJVE1SL"], "questionOptions": ["1.EGO4A82IJOSKDVXD9RIB", "2.J8V33KRVEVF0KW68T4V8X7MJVE1SL", "3.AY2Q4I4N1X4X4CGJ2Q55QP"], "answerLink": "F2YVXO5AS0"}, {"questionId": 20, "questionText": "REODB0XJ61E680HM7I1GAY39ULG47DOQ8WH60H0FZQVTDDVYLJU3CATPG82YQFX18ST91FH1YUY2FZT0V340T2QRLU5OASX8W9B3SBUM1X0147", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "3.DE00KWWBK4PWF3K88EST284", "wrongAnswers": ["1.5KCUSU05MORHOQL4LLDM7HRK2", "2.WPOLARIUA9S6TT514"], "questionOptions": ["1.5KCUSU05MORHOQL4LLDM7HRK2", "2.WPOLARIUA9S6TT514", "3.DE00KWWBK4PWF3K88EST284"], "answerLink": "GFSQBSRH16"}, {"questionId": 21, "questionText": "8V9W2PNGUCDTQ3DVNDCW1AYYGKP2575O7FMSE0L45SBQ55JXIJ48NYFW8K4HOUW0A7KO9RBEUFP70ALHTYXT9UAGFX2WB1IMMVEUQD9WY4599CLAPV", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "3.GQW9O9120GR07FLCNHSTK36K0", "wrongAnswers": ["1.VHWFE2LSUKXSN31ZM", "2.ETLIPIBPVJN0HH4UU"], "questionOptions": ["1.VHWFE2LSUKXSN31ZM", "2.ETLIPIBPVJN0HH4UU", "3.GQW9O9120GR07FLCNHSTK36K0"], "answerLink": "HAUXMB88J2"}, {"questionId": 22, "questionText": "KS87H2IWVCJWGMJUA7S4HHL5UCPP2A9W7OXZE3I72EMWVDVQS4EXT0FFNPUWBL5F34WXQ", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "2.GYR0E6TH2XZ3838916VZTN1JS", "wrongAnswers": ["1.4UMJIIVQL2KKHFOD3H3OC5W", "3.6WMWMIRTWI9YY41DAMCBBTE"], "questionOptions": ["1.4UMJIIVQL2KKHFOD3H3OC5W", "2.GYR0E6TH2XZ3838916VZTN1JS", "3.6WMWMIRTWI9YY41DAMCBBTE"], "answerLink": "Y9ZANK6V41"}, {"questionId": 23, "questionText": "1E0ON4RLNGKE04QOL0BXTDP24JK81AEBNK9Y8NTRO293WZ9Q99INT8HDUKEKTO75IGXWFR", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "1.16TN6DPE1FMKHBIXZV", "wrongAnswers": ["2.9VUE22H4K0NHT5DJ6AAL", "3.4X5ASWWNSIAB3TOK1HVGNE3GOCV"], "questionOptions": ["1.16TN6DPE1FMKHBIXZV", "2.9VUE22H4K0NHT5DJ6AAL", "3.4X5ASWWNSIAB3TOK1HVGNE3GOCV"], "answerLink": "50LZE17J7Y"}, {"questionId": 24, "questionText": "X4FPZU6N1AYRDM0PBLJU658YCRKYML8PG87QJ1P4MHISXA560RKKF6TODX4LRR18WQU2RVE", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "3.8RISNZJLCV5TOB3B5IWS", "wrongAnswers": ["1.2C0QS6LT1M42XRYTW1KTU1REJU", "2.L4BOOA13A1CSPCPKWPNOH6IKDF"], "questionOptions": ["1.2C0QS6LT1M42XRYTW1KTU1REJU", "2.L4BOOA13A1CSPCPKWPNOH6IKDF", "3.8RISNZJLCV5TOB3B5IWS"], "answerLink": "4CJZVQWE2P"}, {"questionId": 25, "questionText": "R0S04BXSJEOPM2KVM8GX2B6ZPZLGHK9M7KAENUSO6W9PG27GO9SQPEKWKTIRIWFQRAWH4GVVU0IDSDQ50HBMSK3XU2LFPTY8YC42TZZG5QATXGC4GGZSOQF", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "2.O9UTPNP6X1K2JQIG2ADLW", "wrongAnswers": ["1.7JLXYKSLV2TYR0KY6TAC5LS1", "3.BTDLDRRM1V7QGCXHHFOEMXDOANEDF9"], "questionOptions": ["1.7JLXYKSLV2TYR0KY6TAC5LS1", "2.O9UTPNP6X1K2JQIG2ADLW", "3.BTDLDRRM1V7QGCXHHFOEMXDOANEDF9"], "answerLink": "EPOVB9QB9A"}, {"questionId": 26, "questionText": "K4OJR58WTN8AD71R3BTHYGB7NHMGJBFZTSSNWXMLRTE9WYLHKDQI0S0CELUQULVXBD738K4SN0RBR9N4LMZ6TNH71O4", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "1.5KLABUE6MVNN2RPR2", "wrongAnswers": ["2.S8J0ZJEZSEYZRBV0V1QAL912LGUDDH", "3.02V96EKE6S72K7LUQX9"], "questionOptions": ["1.5KLABUE6MVNN2RPR2", "2.S8J0ZJEZSEYZRBV0V1QAL912LGUDDH", "3.02V96EKE6S72K7LUQX9"], "answerLink": "R3C7PQD4AE"}, {"questionId": 27, "questionText": "XQ8Y62Q4UC0HECJUA17T6K4PZPSJI0BRD6T7YBMTIP8YNKX01WQIXBO5WOB2V3MB27AK6Y7XE3NT9XGIZYGLP5Y1MM", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "3.L5ZA4ECMY16VVKBECTYTDOD6J7PE", "wrongAnswers": ["1.I4YTPY36QI0INFJ6TQ", "2.DR549ZQ1143RZ3U72PA6YC"], "questionOptions": ["1.I4YTPY36QI0INFJ6TQ", "2.DR549ZQ1143RZ3U72PA6YC", "3.L5ZA4ECMY16VVKBECTYTDOD6J7PE"], "answerLink": "GU5JS119XF"}, {"questionId": 28, "questionText": "E10XPKJDCFL4IYRZ82HYEAMVD2637I5F1K9PYOLE3QQWUNTXQDNFKCZ218Q3BTSPKETR8TAM5ROBPFWG2C4F03IIJCN48ZLA4O3C7EHDAAATVH", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "1.PTSCOTAF9YF0ZM84574Y", "wrongAnswers": ["2.L74HG84JVAUAH4H75ECGM", "3.QARDAE8A8BS5G3880NBMQMWY33IP"], "questionOptions": ["1.PTSCOTAF9YF0ZM84574Y", "2.L74HG84JVAUAH4H75ECGM", "3.QARDAE8A8BS5G3880NBMQMWY33IP"], "answerLink": "AV95AEUIX3"}, {"questionId": 29, "questionText": "TABPMVXPHMQ6XSV59N9SM2QYQVMSIGOQVYDRUM1OF6CTHU8JA6DIP3YJDSWQHXTJ063DS4CP8ZQDMY8A9GO3BLZ7S4HMX3", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "3.53J2PL1OY6W1XTCB15UH", "wrongAnswers": ["1.OITDSA09LOS4KZMOSKS9YIU4D1H15SCD", "2.DHW0LN5T3WX3OT3N2EEV5LH1OPTF1"], "questionOptions": ["1.OITDSA09LOS4KZMOSKS9YIU4D1H15SCD", "2.DHW0LN5T3WX3OT3N2EEV5LH1OPTF1", "3.53J2PL1OY6W1XTCB15UH"], "answerLink": "GGFSBWXB23"}, {"questionId": 30, "questionText": "UCCUK2U1I4NTFYE7VCDRB9ORRW7R4VCRTAAZ7WADMO5YP4PFG2LZXXCK07PIM1E1YMR8684726AB8VBTO6LSMCH0WPOJDB63ONROPI", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "1.8EKLEPLTQWX7L4FUDMBQ1UI9NSW1PWN", "wrongAnswers": ["2.IR4ZNX790F418WQAB0LJW9KXE8A4L", "3.7UE6XM2D7SQGZALN1"], "questionOptions": ["1.8EKLEPLTQWX7L4FUDMBQ1UI9NSW1PWN", "2.IR4ZNX790F418WQAB0LJW9KXE8A4L", "3.7UE6XM2D7SQGZALN1"], "answerLink": "JBZR0P2FI0"}, {"questionId": 31, "questionText": "K0AX482OTEKYBT9JKX2J3X8J46RHI9MX1C7A1HV71LS16HGQZWN8JCYOQV48JDU4KS8V6HBSS07", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "3.UNKLYJJFJZ3VOXBEQOUR", "wrongAnswers": ["1.VKII23CI3RKW43P3RG92YWQT4SZDMX0L", "2.OY82NL9BV837L0YLI9FTIKELNK"], "questionOptions": ["1.VKII23CI3RKW43P3RG92YWQT4SZDMX0L", "2.OY82NL9BV837L0YLI9FTIKELNK", "3.UNKLYJJFJZ3VOXBEQOUR"], "answerLink": "DXOAOPOEX9"}, {"questionId": 32, "questionText": "7KBKDXOL904UUSFXPIDTNXXKYJTR9VLAXKAUXWVO4ZQXM5DGRIRR3BRIPVO7EPOMU6QJCG3VRAX0NDZ6S24BDCY3EY3WWZ44WVOTFG3I708A", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "2.ESSFLP6W1909YLE6MIKWF", "wrongAnswers": ["1.2F1MR058T7NCYT3SYULMHE5NX", "3.IFSGM1YHF60EM2R15RZR8R5S"], "questionOptions": ["1.2F1MR058T7NCYT3SYULMHE5NX", "2.ESSFLP6W1909YLE6MIKWF", "3.IFSGM1YHF60EM2R15RZR8R5S"], "answerLink": "Z072Y6M9C2"}, {"questionId": 33, "questionText": "YQ2RCUSEO6HTVHQDJCUADQKK1LWTV7LPYNZV2J4CLBVDSDEYZQ4N7VM847X1BQ5VOGO63PUT4U02EN4Z3ZUZZTQHI3LMGDEFYBMIN", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "2.2C8C9MX2I2XHEMH1RIO82XDMWL0EAP6", "wrongAnswers": ["1.SSS9XPK9XP51I9DRTX38Z062", "3.J87SUZ3HZFL3852JZE36JXMGTAG"], "questionOptions": ["1.SSS9XPK9XP51I9DRTX38Z062", "2.2C8C9MX2I2XHEMH1RIO82XDMWL0EAP6", "3.J87SUZ3HZFL3852JZE36JXMGTAG"], "answerLink": "JQ09C4819W"}, {"questionId": 34, "questionText": "K24LTSSUMQX77PPO702SS94Z3YU5WB8MU4XUEELG3G6X1YEKABC3ZRMFSU3GN6ALJRSQCJIE1KRTX8SDNPFOHSJN4L0X0YJ9UPGA4MR16ZD6CH", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "2.B9HXGH7LJ7RNXFXN33CNYM9UO7", "wrongAnswers": ["1.6G7FXWMZTGKAN26Y", "3.2A0CPKRBVIF6RRL65DGZFPOJXA1"], "questionOptions": ["1.6G7FXWMZTGKAN26Y", "2.B9HXGH7LJ7RNXFXN33CNYM9UO7", "3.2A0CPKRBVIF6RRL65DGZFPOJXA1"], "answerLink": "E38585UAQM"}, {"questionId": 35, "questionText": "8FVVKOV81NXH2RUNDQI5DKOBYBVUSJVN2GEVMOBFE8KASVVYDVM3CJQGW5FWS4YU79BNTVV2H07HBC0TMWNNRCBIXFADA40Y0QLI6YP09GCBA8QQ9VSCARHI05T3C", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "3.GWB3IRX0NYFAQPSDXT9ZSIK988W", "wrongAnswers": ["1.6HHCOMX16YVQ9VOSTZ4D73XYH97", "2.687DGIPXXPQ03P55RGK5TQCV"], "questionOptions": ["1.6HHCOMX16YVQ9VOSTZ4D73XYH97", "2.687DGIPXXPQ03P55RGK5TQCV", "3.GWB3IRX0NYFAQPSDXT9ZSIK988W"], "answerLink": "1XLDV3WNIK"}, {"questionId": 36, "questionText": "LQ1X5U2T9S9LCZ8DM34CTNF9DXWZLKZX5VI0NKS3DJJKRZ0J6NIIB71N6BEOVUXR16M6TE", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "1.2T8EFTDTYPM1JDZFWF7", "wrongAnswers": ["2.7SYV3LOYT9EZOZCYW667", "3.SNGF9ESMIZ242Q2RD"], "questionOptions": ["1.2T8EFTDTYPM1JDZFWF7", "2.7SYV3LOYT9EZOZCYW667", "3.SNGF9ESMIZ242Q2RD"], "answerLink": "KHFOGFO9D8"}, {"questionId": 37, "questionText": "J4BOC5UDI1WFJRHRK9JMV8BXDRFZI1M08LNU13Q1AZFEHU9BHGTBHGB0ASFP4OFVK9T6TC5SFLD", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "2.RBT01MBI124UXU9TMDVP9CNLMVYZJ8", "wrongAnswers": ["1.ATXQWCIJU81KAOKE9BXEAYRTXB", "3.I1IR6B1KCV0416Y83ZES43J8RSQYPS"], "questionOptions": ["1.ATXQWCIJU81KAOKE9BXEAYRTXB", "2.RBT01MBI124UXU9TMDVP9CNLMVYZJ8", "3.I1IR6B1KCV0416Y83ZES43J8RSQYPS"], "answerLink": "YB3XSWGZH4"}, {"questionId": 38, "questionText": "T3I8C44TYXZZ6VGMO59IKWNBZ0FCQX8OCQ6W7O2EYJK0O4SH1EEFNSS87FZKBNDPQGTMNK8BX3XODL6CQ1WCPKFVBR5NJV", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "2.LKHQ47V74ZNR8CD7FDKYR6G1MCSAJQ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.010EA9LLJVLXOMGGWGKEEQR56", "3.57SC0EMS7B2VZRCTL5RT41"], "questionOptions": ["1.010EA9LLJVLXOMGGWGKEEQR56", "2.LKHQ47V74ZNR8CD7FDKYR6G1MCSAJQ", "3.57SC0EMS7B2VZRCTL5RT41"], "answerLink": "IULZFWB81M"}, {"questionId": 39, "questionText": "WLTT1T6N7ZVT9XBS2T0S9XPRD7JGR9T2IRVNIRYVGCCNPZBHK9I00K7IUCKPBYVONIS2KZH6IZ", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "3.HXY2QW54S1IWWTTS", "wrongAnswers": ["1.PDD4Q8Q2DAF6HUTIHBQ7M7ZO", "2.JPHFVJU8PLMKUPZ8FS3BB3B"], "questionOptions": ["1.PDD4Q8Q2DAF6HUTIHBQ7M7ZO", "2.JPHFVJU8PLMKUPZ8FS3BB3B", "3.HXY2QW54S1IWWTTS"], "answerLink": "W11IJDEI5Y"}, {"questionId": 40, "questionText": "24W2W2UA8WZIQKRZV575EDP1NSJM8ZITCYXIJYGV8BU5SDZ2W98QHLPTM9I4PT5T", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "1.1U715UAKQRHCUYONC4OS", "wrongAnswers": ["2.7JV3DZZJJS85YCQKBX6JW96Y693UE", "3.0TEZX6QAL2EQJDK2IU7M1M4H"], "questionOptions": ["1.1U715UAKQRHCUYONC4OS", "2.7JV3DZZJJS85YCQKBX6JW96Y693UE", "3.0TEZX6QAL2EQJDK2IU7M1M4H"], "answerLink": "3RHCOZPEQK"}, {"questionId": 41, "questionText": "WI976WNU6DVUUKQOKI0AIXWMSOO8DX7K2A6O3ZY0AY04PHMGSVRVLFBKUZDSF12TCKD68OAZIR0NTQ4MQW9U5DPSCELIE2Q3Q9", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "1.DCJA3DGY5G8VSYCNCQ1", "wrongAnswers": ["2.29IWSL7LBK1JCV0DFADQM38XQ2G", "3.XLRSH6CUH1JDUYJ0T"], "questionOptions": ["1.DCJA3DGY5G8VSYCNCQ1", "2.29IWSL7LBK1JCV0DFADQM38XQ2G", "3.XLRSH6CUH1JDUYJ0T"], "answerLink": "PBKQ37EI37"}, {"questionId": 42, "questionText": "V695A1RFMMVNFWK8IPQWSH9TP8HZFP68KN80OEA6OU217FNTBUL0TZ5KIR8GJTP94LVKW5B", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "3.3U0YFC83MYYBKPHPRT38B4X2MLPY", "wrongAnswers": ["1.GJMMU37HC740DKCYCGWH7RSU7", "2.6HB2IYKERUNBE9STVIINLN"], "questionOptions": ["1.GJMMU37HC740DKCYCGWH7RSU7", "2.6HB2IYKERUNBE9STVIINLN", "3.3U0YFC83MYYBKPHPRT38B4X2MLPY"], "answerLink": "9A8X31BXU8"}, {"questionId": 43, "questionText": "1MAKI69D7DR943PYUYJM1GGSWCKGATI3HINSWL29CIU1HGWW7CE4BQXY51R4OB7RU28OQZAPFNW6B2ORU011D6LJ591BZV754WGGIUC3H8V8K2R81Z", "questionCategory": "Regola 1", "correctAnswers": "1.5EQKA7LO1P36KLXDEQU", "wrongAnswers": ["2.ZOR487CLUTE48N50R", "3.3MNKZJXB7UFMN5HZPUM5"], "questionOptions": ["1.5EQKA7LO1P36KLXDEQU", "2.ZOR487CLUTE48N50R", "3.3MNKZJXB7UFMN5HZPUM5"], "answerLink": "8M8G6P18W9"}, {"questionId": 44, "questionText": "5NYZUBTHITM0TLMKWHMMUPJX3K3M4D9M3L411DMMK2EMIGSJDS4EQN5W9QWW2G0WUMDVII0MRG0TQHU6GN9TEB32DWBF51SQ8K8MPS0", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "1.EXRPPN5Z8KFY3JP15E5LFDV9", "wrongAnswers": ["2.I9QNT1HQU8F7F4JV8WY281HHL0TE5Y5", "3.E0NCIXBHWFEN16HWH21"], "questionOptions": ["1.EXRPPN5Z8KFY3JP15E5LFDV9", "2.I9QNT1HQU8F7F4JV8WY281HHL0TE5Y5", "3.E0NCIXBHWFEN16HWH21"], "answerLink": "1DGJSEFUZ5"}, {"questionId": 45, "questionText": "57PY557D38KQMA1NIVVOQM7X8NYFZM41DMQTHS357NQKUVA4UJJ85BCBTLOMISTGWYJW", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "2.3J7364HPJQLRVDS9P037", "wrongAnswers": ["1.2C7FVQZZAMO3XLSO8", "3.OAK025IAJL6E0M6YZ6W1"], "questionOptions": ["1.2C7FVQZZAMO3XLSO8", "2.3J7364HPJQLRVDS9P037", "3.OAK025IAJL6E0M6YZ6W1"], "answerLink": "74UL1LJAU7"}, {"questionId": 46, "questionText": "OMNTV5MUBFKBXS9NJ0IPTOX9AGZ2KK4QYHESC6L2W2BGKT5SM12FU5Q4I0Q8NL7G0LDG5A9XHMH3NM1KAUMC7I3SOKP64M", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "3.TW5ITCMA11LLNTNPGXKJ9O25MF", "wrongAnswers": ["1.WVSAS0HOBQM4WOFUSQVLEQAKPET", "2.0IE05U2W7RX0EZ03C"], "questionOptions": ["1.WVSAS0HOBQM4WOFUSQVLEQAKPET", "2.0IE05U2W7RX0EZ03C", "3.TW5ITCMA11LLNTNPGXKJ9O25MF"], "answerLink": "6OEQG5U3H8"}, {"questionId": 47, "questionText": "RNFCH3BF767UXCT3S56GLV15VW1WIKH3M35BU6QDJ8043XKW3ZWO6WMK6FLTB25044", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "2.L7Q6HNPYQ2B9ZL5DRT0Y6B6YWI", "wrongAnswers": ["1.64QX5GN3Q7HRT0OELP2L12Z7VW8", "3.38TTX1CQJIIG6OR0FUOZ"], "questionOptions": ["1.64QX5GN3Q7HRT0OELP2L12Z7VW8", "2.L7Q6HNPYQ2B9ZL5DRT0Y6B6YWI", "3.38TTX1CQJIIG6OR0FUOZ"], "answerLink": "ENXKLROB2R"}, {"questionId": 48, "questionText": "0YOVJMPL6ROHZWKTD3C4H3JZTZ7H0MVX1AM4DW1C7EPZ65MEYIHHMUKOZOYB6BTQUO2YW16QFWXK88G95EZI5UNTPY114R0S32SIBL1LARLK65JW0LJ1O3W6KCDF9", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "1.OEIK6ZIMR0SXCQLD", "wrongAnswers": ["2.K08TIC4Z73XJLKD241IGWLGFUW73H5R", "3.YN1LTEGALR8542TSWC4PGA386FB7OB"], "questionOptions": ["1.OEIK6ZIMR0SXCQLD", "2.K08TIC4Z73XJLKD241IGWLGFUW73H5R", "3.YN1LTEGALR8542TSWC4PGA386FB7OB"], "answerLink": "XPBJXHE73H"}, {"questionId": 49, "questionText": "P8KBER9K07REEQSWU2P6XP7ZUE1SOJB2C5KMP9VVMUFV444HKKICUWU2VR82XOVBBVH8K4RY4CYGFQ0IW3XXAFCQRGJ9C5GSZ", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "2.OLDP9FC4KFJC60M1ZSBV", "wrongAnswers": ["1.DYW95CPAEDFXUQA9B", "3.MWKGEPE4WU495Z7ZGBNHVSFK1G96RI8Z"], "questionOptions": ["1.DYW95CPAEDFXUQA9B", "2.OLDP9FC4KFJC60M1ZSBV", "3.MWKGEPE4WU495Z7ZGBNHVSFK1G96RI8Z"], "answerLink": "4X3VRVDNN6"}, {"questionId": 50, "questionText": "EVUJN7DPC1785GG6J6PIUK2M6Y8ROGOYVJCKO2ZP935IXP7KQAUJMVLYK40CQ2ZSTK65OJFA05UMYWXNRZV1YILM78CWLUT42AX2B39", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "2.IXD22DCRMQW4I3AANCIDV9PEY7", "wrongAnswers": ["1.BZ6JB96GXADEM284P5", "3.Z6SND9EPCRRIFO7O7F02G43XWA71"], "questionOptions": ["1.BZ6JB96GXADEM284P5", "2.IXD22DCRMQW4I3AANCIDV9PEY7", "3.Z6SND9EPCRRIFO7O7F02G43XWA71"], "answerLink": "COXPJMKRE0"}, {"questionId": 51, "questionText": "PSI2GYHGV2AXQU3Z66GLWNU6792UEAFME4O7O91FWCMETZ1H4BYQZJYPKVOVPJ2ZSEABC9985PEOIUTEFEL7476YUEJGJHNG00LY16FHL", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "1.XUDKSSGH7110NFMXXP1NZL894", "wrongAnswers": ["2.JJXL8WHYY956RG1VBRYOOXG5", "3.BCQYXG29TNFK78E0IXTWOOP"], "questionOptions": ["1.XUDKSSGH7110NFMXXP1NZL894", "2.JJXL8WHYY956RG1VBRYOOXG5", "3.BCQYXG29TNFK78E0IXTWOOP"], "answerLink": "U5X8QUNR9N"}, {"questionId": 52, "questionText": "38PMAR8LU3X9KSO70RUVPG236AKTYMQDE0LLQEIANQVR6K42DWU5BYY7YSM7F9LYU7LR7Z9BN86GIB5OTG7NLWR1ZQNDA3K3YCCHW52C0BN9JQYROVG", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "1.VEXBKMBQLCS49TU8MU3XK3UKYDLN4QM7", "wrongAnswers": ["2.1EYI85EEJMGSK5ETBAVREKDZFG9B", "3.006LVJHN8MTHYBQ74HG7CLK3"], "questionOptions": ["1.VEXBKMBQLCS49TU8MU3XK3UKYDLN4QM7", "2.1EYI85EEJMGSK5ETBAVREKDZFG9B", "3.006LVJHN8MTHYBQ74HG7CLK3"], "answerLink": "IXBC03ISTU"}, {"questionId": 53, "questionText": "51PTJYOJNYJ1U1ZUVLJ89KLX6I3XDG3NB5YLW5S7DJUNV5SVWQNFJ0Y75V9X9SYXUCRVZNWV86IQ2V3PKW9", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "3.NSBWRF30JTB01OYRHR2BCGXEMKMKD3", "wrongAnswers": ["1.6VNTWJ13MTRQUZ8EIKDS1MIU92NED5", "2.WZY60J4ZOQVKNZUD"], "questionOptions": ["1.6VNTWJ13MTRQUZ8EIKDS1MIU92NED5", "2.WZY60J4ZOQVKNZUD", "3.NSBWRF30JTB01OYRHR2BCGXEMKMKD3"], "answerLink": "M16TLGCWB3"}, {"questionId": 54, "questionText": "7TK194SA4S0IQF02NYMDEUT5GXWQRQULJ3EX6G878SYR3B0UNH101CJ9Z97BPNUA96DYCHNKZ8DDJXY3T2N24OOOSQ6N8CASGYNO6BWSR", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "3.ZNYHOWGJQU8C7HY3SDJ02QNJEX", "wrongAnswers": ["1.WP11AQSLQUL38DMCP6H807YSV7G3JG", "2.LMUTYCLAIK1T17WWR4H0"], "questionOptions": ["1.WP11AQSLQUL38DMCP6H807YSV7G3JG", "2.LMUTYCLAIK1T17WWR4H0", "3.ZNYHOWGJQU8C7HY3SDJ02QNJEX"], "answerLink": "ZJMO8SDD2Z"}, {"questionId": 55, "questionText": "LPCKVLMNJSY7OXFPP2BLO4UYNHF3R4EZ5KRINBFI54EZ15XDEHFW757R5BEYW82I1X93A285IL6CP426NW2B5FCPGSZ1JFABFEVI0MBRFUVHBD2268", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "1.X0UVGYXK9YIJY6TO9CLULMH67IWYKUCR", "wrongAnswers": ["2.PCZJ5TKEP1WX9ECRT3H7CITITK", "3.4E547H1DBPQTTXKEUYLH2RUVAY9UYA9A"], "questionOptions": ["1.X0UVGYXK9YIJY6TO9CLULMH67IWYKUCR", "2.PCZJ5TKEP1WX9ECRT3H7CITITK", "3.4E547H1DBPQTTXKEUYLH2RUVAY9UYA9A"], "answerLink": "Z9DWFRZIGK"}, {"questionId": 56, "questionText": "CLPQGML17ZOMUILLVQR2E0HL5UENZVP5R3STX2RRZIOJ41J5EH220BTYREM8NQ8M5SIC49KMYAD68XWKPXSP8AEHTXGA60QQGXBFTQM9EDO", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "3.8YN68Z7BRLGJCEPUHTSA2PUJA8", "wrongAnswers": ["1.G4GC8TKB62YS69NX2", "2.YGHW71F4ZETGWCEUHPZLWR0TB"], "questionOptions": ["1.G4GC8TKB62YS69NX2", "2.YGHW71F4ZETGWCEUHPZLWR0TB", "3.8YN68Z7BRLGJCEPUHTSA2PUJA8"], "answerLink": "KNCN8CSL15"}, {"questionId": 57, "questionText": "Q5OJXSP8GATL1NV09EI31SL8B2CDHG7N89LCCZ16HELS68X782PU0FUSLPLMMZDJDAESVCDD", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "1.3WTG0BS3H18UVKQTI7VADEQOGZBY4", "wrongAnswers": ["2.PZEG3F9394XPNAJXB1V8E", "3.1FVDXUSLH9OIPG4MPJ"], "questionOptions": ["1.3WTG0BS3H18UVKQTI7VADEQOGZBY4", "2.PZEG3F9394XPNAJXB1V8E", "3.1FVDXUSLH9OIPG4MPJ"], "answerLink": "FDTAJA9RVF"}, {"questionId": 58, "questionText": "MB0HL3V31W2HLDETPFVAI1ZKY2RQXBA9KUN2NGUIX8VQNVK7LDKF8WXB2PKP90VWQCLY38A2S2MFXS3N4GJ9H79YBXLQQRUJ88191OWWOFCRMQD", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "1.6O4JCW6G8MUAFID02378U50IQNRXDMQ", "wrongAnswers": ["2.YLYITUW3D046H2RNCO9FJU", "3.LAM1R9OXWHKM8CP6V4I3RKJD"], "questionOptions": ["1.6O4JCW6G8MUAFID02378U50IQNRXDMQ", "2.YLYITUW3D046H2RNCO9FJU", "3.LAM1R9OXWHKM8CP6V4I3RKJD"], "answerLink": "GB4ZVI4XTO"}, {"questionId": 59, "questionText": "QZVP4FL0XLJQY02N87UA7KPUK9W6L6QKWVXCK24ZCDOKBVP4AA79FPXUHD83VY3R71X653L5G3SLXD6HYJP9V6TE3WC8TZTKV994PBB344BHKE2KA", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "3.7NNV3SW5REIPDVEJABUF288", "wrongAnswers": ["1.PPZY9ULU438INT5JGYAM7JM", "2.THOND09ZND3L8TUO1GGSOA"], "questionOptions": ["1.PPZY9ULU438INT5JGYAM7JM", "2.THOND09ZND3L8TUO1GGSOA", "3.7NNV3SW5REIPDVEJABUF288"], "answerLink": "X1CQXSLYX5"}, {"questionId": 60, "questionText": "3ASF6U8MII09P91TE9Q7D25YM86LR8X15CJ7BMRF5TK5QLUVP6R3T0U2I50HFA5HLDT0N23ZLHOR6C", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "2.AVLVA7I13V0G3HNV2CX340GN7Z", "wrongAnswers": ["1.A47HK1NR8WHH6HH3ZACKQTFJJ", "3.FFV7DKFAY00GDRU1F5N5AVM0813ET"], "questionOptions": ["1.A47HK1NR8WHH6HH3ZACKQTFJJ", "2.AVLVA7I13V0G3HNV2CX340GN7Z", "3.FFV7DKFAY00GDRU1F5N5AVM0813ET"], "answerLink": "6TKK63O2AF"}, {"questionId": 61, "questionText": "MHJWW6HRWWJ7S1CA4E3CGHQ812H0W0W9VMUOLB94U2JXO72HCHWCI0JAEBD95VXQABVMC1ET1LCK2TJSTVTH9", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "1.32GO5JT0YROUYE613OGPA", "wrongAnswers": ["2.B3KT20U08BIXLUD4ZQ4VCJ2GE250UV7", "3.7JCR83JOCJLIS6QQ2A78HG32WZVRXD"], "questionOptions": ["1.32GO5JT0YROUYE613OGPA", "2.B3KT20U08BIXLUD4ZQ4VCJ2GE250UV7", "3.7JCR83JOCJLIS6QQ2A78HG32WZVRXD"], "answerLink": "W5A26NMV8R"}, {"questionId": 62, "questionText": "GBM6S6ZUVX57PFQHN7E4MOX2EQ90YK70FHXQHKT4CVO7LTJ463BJBBFTL3QD091BH", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "1.LM0DZOBS0TTWT26Y5G", "wrongAnswers": ["2.WXQKULZFI8NL7MZRJK4DG98SOLN7PX", "3.IMHRRBL4WLP3BFRL75WHU0ZIYEIC"], "questionOptions": ["1.LM0DZOBS0TTWT26Y5G", "2.WXQKULZFI8NL7MZRJK4DG98SOLN7PX", "3.IMHRRBL4WLP3BFRL75WHU0ZIYEIC"], "answerLink": "99KZJQEV15"}, {"questionId": 63, "questionText": "TJIR8FUBYR57EH7BA6KXTTNN3Y962MWJ5MZBJAUD57PEF9EOQOPPNAWU03X7V7XVDQ431UY4EI17PCV83D56NUWCDGQ87LPT29ENPFH56EHQXP9", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "3.SX7JNEAAQGZT2QLSNYGL4", "wrongAnswers": ["1.ZUQ71FZ2B8L05G3UMRZE49T", "2.HONJF1E55TN8S9TW2TH77HJJZV8MI58"], "questionOptions": ["1.ZUQ71FZ2B8L05G3UMRZE49T", "2.HONJF1E55TN8S9TW2TH77HJJZV8MI58", "3.SX7JNEAAQGZT2QLSNYGL4"], "answerLink": "SC8A9CW0BG"}, {"questionId": 64, "questionText": "RE0PQUK47JNFWRU2UALX5GS519SUBW1ZRBYK0EZ67IDBQL2K3K6CQ8WYE1HSNX07DTLS4SGOS3HYOZO9C86", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "1.2J7GWNXQYSYGDW4YBFBVDIN", "wrongAnswers": ["2.96329I6WDI1HGXG3R", "3.76TGQXO927L9XK6SMR"], "questionOptions": ["1.2J7GWNXQYSYGDW4YBFBVDIN", "2.96329I6WDI1HGXG3R", "3.76TGQXO927L9XK6SMR"], "answerLink": "3NHB0NWPQH"}, {"questionId": 65, "questionText": "37Q465928SU4BCWGU6FK0NATO2R2QJYEOTS37XYGA9VAH7ZKSR1KS9ORSRWVL1G1LKG8YW7LRSDMKPO3DKWJ5PMHJ3M52WA", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "3.V1IGXDILGGVET3XR4X", "wrongAnswers": ["1.5ASE41RDJM01M2VEYE9QIBNI1C8", "2.VSIG21JRW5E2IJI3A9W72NUW61BI6QTL"], "questionOptions": ["1.5ASE41RDJM01M2VEYE9QIBNI1C8", "2.VSIG21JRW5E2IJI3A9W72NUW61BI6QTL", "3.V1IGXDILGGVET3XR4X"], "answerLink": "7CP3VXLR6A"}, {"questionId": 66, "questionText": "89ZZWEP7FFMG0IQKRPEELFJT4W6UW9BQSSOX0DA3L2G7LYMJXDY6MR6971RGBI0IHEQL9NSTVD38I8M3JMW3UXWUZ118IOTH8P3OLH1QRQOE5SO2", "questionCategory": "Regola 2", "correctAnswers": "3.JFG7PT7V74A9T4ZCGJ35G2UPMI", "wrongAnswers": ["1.YEGO9D0XJG281B981KC", "2.O6MOPL0EO2VT3FGSM4"], "questionOptions": ["1.YEGO9D0XJG281B981KC", "2.O6MOPL0EO2VT3FGSM4", "3.JFG7PT7V74A9T4ZCGJ35G2UPMI"], "answerLink": "VX5TLQL0RV"}, {"questionId": 67, "questionText": "RCSO1AB2ZNTY0XLQUKENKHVIJT7GI0LAYRMGIXHHK51ABTYRG2Z2R147YVQE8NWNABQCANUN4Y7H9ASVNXMVJ8II1HK83", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.7GMWZ5WTOFMY7JUK675FNG", "wrongAnswers": ["1.0S9NIHGVQL6YWUZQWEKSXZLNGK13", "2.X2SS7ERSPCDBN7BBNB2QVT7"], "questionOptions": ["1.0S9NIHGVQL6YWUZQWEKSXZLNGK13", "2.X2SS7ERSPCDBN7BBNB2QVT7", "3.7GMWZ5WTOFMY7JUK675FNG"], "answerLink": "S2VUEDKINU"}, {"questionId": 68, "questionText": "OLZO5SNIANXY3G8868HVWV7R6X0Z6GCGNHNG3YTUNZ70BGXSXFAHYQ2ILAMKNOHBCNTYKFA277QZNNNNAFA4PE0HBRFYGL0LPA5S9M9CLD2O", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "1.A1SJ49MX9597WR0OZM468ICS4AB0QH1", "wrongAnswers": ["2.Q9Z4EDDV6RGFTGTDOSWSXSPM", "3.UE1DDY97EX2AS1N8OK3TILQ2"], "questionOptions": ["1.A1SJ49MX9597WR0OZM468ICS4AB0QH1", "2.Q9Z4EDDV6RGFTGTDOSWSXSPM", "3.UE1DDY97EX2AS1N8OK3TILQ2"], "answerLink": "YPMM9N02L5"}, {"questionId": 69, "questionText": "E2BRA85TUQ5A248D92YV80DPVQK7BXVZ350V7EOZBY7UB92Z42XBN45F2PH1BSFP75F7PR514GNMNO4BQADCP4YCLDI6JBFU33IR16HV", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.QZ2T16TAVGH8A3LY92L5HB49EJ9U", "wrongAnswers": ["1.BSYAEJ5CLHA6TXV4KDD7KTE", "2.D03LKET23FA6KFWJUTSX5DF3FXH8U01"], "questionOptions": ["1.BSYAEJ5CLHA6TXV4KDD7KTE", "2.D03LKET23FA6KFWJUTSX5DF3FXH8U01", "3.QZ2T16TAVGH8A3LY92L5HB49EJ9U"], "answerLink": "7MX9B91YP5"}, {"questionId": 70, "questionText": "S047KHU6WT2MBKWOCVHK7VA2JUEEYDL32FAP41GNY2VLT28YDEZ8YGFBOESA6LLTAY88AC710J4BX49MU8Y208C", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.5KD9MRNFK2RTF8LCXAZ7ITNDKD", "wrongAnswers": ["1.4OBO9LOKU35FRBK8W666SZ", "2.LPBRWS1OFIVVAJCFNWJ9VE82RR2V110X"], "questionOptions": ["1.4OBO9LOKU35FRBK8W666SZ", "2.LPBRWS1OFIVVAJCFNWJ9VE82RR2V110X", "3.5KD9MRNFK2RTF8LCXAZ7ITNDKD"], "answerLink": "3OUXJYSSNG"}, {"questionId": 71, "questionText": "U59F4LLCFEWCMEVZ59LYYEGQGR9HHCL0CJHFGII21CB5GXI6YCNKIX3LFQFI5LQLA73KBA028IL3OX4OE5JBT86J5AC7BEFRKKQF1TA2ZI09VTFE9PMP18Y4", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "2.XY6IOBD783OHOAV8", "wrongAnswers": ["1.AJDD0TVH8JFNA2FKNSM", "3.RKNQQ4E7GO2B2DPX5TAMJXEF"], "questionOptions": ["1.AJDD0TVH8JFNA2FKNSM", "2.XY6IOBD783OHOAV8", "3.RKNQQ4E7GO2B2DPX5TAMJXEF"], "answerLink": "SDFG921QSC"}, {"questionId": 72, "questionText": "QPSTDZU3PHPK8XSIMWLQW0T687DI0BKSMSZPGOW9YD5RTXG3YDXBJ60ZLFHDR5ES4DK1V3F90HI8VAGENYY7BH7DN9HJUF56GC7IUN", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.2JW1GDUS7OUQNBE8XM77Y8", "wrongAnswers": ["1.ADW059UNXPAVHBHM", "2.0VZMLRG3Y94XY3ZY504I4A"], "questionOptions": ["1.ADW059UNXPAVHBHM", "2.0VZMLRG3Y94XY3ZY504I4A", "3.2JW1GDUS7OUQNBE8XM77Y8"], "answerLink": "IWBV4AEQV6"}, {"questionId": 73, "questionText": "5OY4IWELPAERJA4MA8U5DORORZBE4FVW449LOG9FSI2SWK4897H78DWP6A4UKQLXKAUI78ODDRDJDOUVRNEXA5E74X5Z40B5PTMGIUD", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "1.JXHEAZKRPS4F7ML405XXG", "wrongAnswers": ["2.26J3L9Z8Q7509EM4G6AHLEKL0VNYK", "3.8J9IRTRRBKJVUPW9QM01"], "questionOptions": ["1.JXHEAZKRPS4F7ML405XXG", "2.26J3L9Z8Q7509EM4G6AHLEKL0VNYK", "3.8J9IRTRRBKJVUPW9QM01"], "answerLink": "1F92QOFH35"}, {"questionId": 74, "questionText": "W02W851HCMXGKE1ZQ0SD4ZTKYB7W5IMLBXZWW8LO9SHWWF3TNQF46134YVAGUU9XK5VL75F3N4930HVM6N3H", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "1.XT2XHKQ8HNOIH9VVU98Q3YD390T4", "wrongAnswers": ["2.K2H1U5SYYDUBIUXYAZXDNHC", "3.78FDWRHCIJACEFGNPXG0FG5PZUASQU"], "questionOptions": ["1.XT2XHKQ8HNOIH9VVU98Q3YD390T4", "2.K2H1U5SYYDUBIUXYAZXDNHC", "3.78FDWRHCIJACEFGNPXG0FG5PZUASQU"], "answerLink": "C529SEM9Y3"}, {"questionId": 75, "questionText": "ZQFFQDM8YFP90BXKL6BEUED4TONSIEKW0Q98QWMMX5V4GJPDFGQ2V2OTCXHRKQEQV00Y845JHEHPARAAYRN7Y", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.4XU9KCPG30NUV1UT3TQPI2BE70GVGKG", "wrongAnswers": ["1.UFYTYPTQW7UR1230P8ECQYGA6CHW5", "2.DS28M6MSZ34AGTD8Y86WP06T51"], "questionOptions": ["1.UFYTYPTQW7UR1230P8ECQYGA6CHW5", "2.DS28M6MSZ34AGTD8Y86WP06T51", "3.4XU9KCPG30NUV1UT3TQPI2BE70GVGKG"], "answerLink": "QMAPLBN64W"}, {"questionId": 76, "questionText": "GICGHQRT87LJQDY11R8CEXR0P3EK0FAAI08J10W6SBK5ONJB94BMNMNRPQLSDHSB0NI2", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.8O283WX20ZEW1W0M8243KJ5I", "wrongAnswers": ["1.T12JWTF3HIJXV2Z7", "2.GT00KANRSC9ASFD69QU"], "questionOptions": ["1.T12JWTF3HIJXV2Z7", "2.GT00KANRSC9ASFD69QU", "3.8O283WX20ZEW1W0M8243KJ5I"], "answerLink": "66GZDNHAYA"}, {"questionId": 77, "questionText": "G1ZXA6QAV5BU38H55D90BDX2C2DQ444ZQPZSJ05MRVVPWSWKAQLN1UO4LHBMXB5CTNL04ZMNM9383H30SSW", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.8XPIC6JY3EK2K62NTW856AA", "wrongAnswers": ["1.BO9AJEPFW67QSFZGX", "2.MWWS84J1LXQBRFTGHEJP"], "questionOptions": ["1.BO9AJEPFW67QSFZGX", "2.MWWS84J1LXQBRFTGHEJP", "3.8XPIC6JY3EK2K62NTW856AA"], "answerLink": "E6RV4Y5DG5"}, {"questionId": 78, "questionText": "IELD18Z30VHISAXNB9KDT5624KUINAQPNLUAW5RIOXYOXN6JRWNJASE3KH16EPLGHOP92A4NQCFIATDAXES1HWZQFM8DXY7O65B1T3TYO8", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "2.MP9FF48H3ANHZPEAYWMICMJ2VM2O", "wrongAnswers": ["1.IIPX1T39S457CPF90ABX3N", "3.O6SRY831TD4JHMHV04K9BPTCN"], "questionOptions": ["1.IIPX1T39S457CPF90ABX3N", "2.MP9FF48H3ANHZPEAYWMICMJ2VM2O", "3.O6SRY831TD4JHMHV04K9BPTCN"], "answerLink": "1ZZAY3QOH1"}, {"questionId": 79, "questionText": "BRO5GLTZYSVTJMX37PB77FLP3UC339PLINDOHNU4WLLWNRK9BJU376J7PIFK1XALNNSXIKPJ1X6W6P2PTBVOHM3WXW7RPL6SP563GRC93B4V58H5H92YRN8R", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.1E2OPSXTZOV3QQ9PU", "wrongAnswers": ["1.PNYN823S1DPTE8XNFXM5X0P5EAJWP", "2.JZ157S566BYHNNOLIZ4FP7U"], "questionOptions": ["1.PNYN823S1DPTE8XNFXM5X0P5EAJWP", "2.JZ157S566BYHNNOLIZ4FP7U", "3.1E2OPSXTZOV3QQ9PU"], "answerLink": "93BPITSQZX"}, {"questionId": 80, "questionText": "BQZ7F0OP5FKPYEIF0HPQHOV1CA0B0T0CO3PA08OSWG9B8Y7D7ZS3DDR2AFD55U8Y1VRQ59NZ506S0", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "1.BM45HGMK7ISF2CM8VH", "wrongAnswers": ["2.GG9LALEHZX2UIH6ZB", "3.1GVJCXUSGC0X9C4QIMV9N4PXA"], "questionOptions": ["1.BM45HGMK7ISF2CM8VH", "2.GG9LALEHZX2UIH6ZB", "3.1GVJCXUSGC0X9C4QIMV9N4PXA"], "answerLink": "U8KSWZHLEF"}, {"questionId": 81, "questionText": "TSSWUQZYN6Z4B6LO4HICT6KKOJJPN7P06DGLO8Z5TGJQUZUDE5MN7C2W8DMXDNSPXO", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "2.IDEQSB66ZALPY4KFNWOH4S0HKW", "wrongAnswers": ["1.BOETABEQODW27KWZBRY1RRH5B7YB", "3.EY1AHAOOIZAMWG7X1"], "questionOptions": ["1.BOETABEQODW27KWZBRY1RRH5B7YB", "2.IDEQSB66ZALPY4KFNWOH4S0HKW", "3.EY1AHAOOIZAMWG7X1"], "answerLink": "05JPN32UBE"}, {"questionId": 82, "questionText": "NOL0NLXRKZZDE3BVFV1CWGM9P8WID1T68PZZ1ZM4XY5ZGCKPVVM9G0KUKCN2DJDZNT7V657OL97W9NKP56MYR", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "1.O990FW3MCL0T8H8N2AP0GANMS05YU44", "wrongAnswers": ["2.L3J19GI8F3VE6NHVF06", "3.BRV9HXT9JCQUAFGVSRUQ4T"], "questionOptions": ["1.O990FW3MCL0T8H8N2AP0GANMS05YU44", "2.L3J19GI8F3VE6NHVF06", "3.BRV9HXT9JCQUAFGVSRUQ4T"], "answerLink": "CII99ICK8D"}, {"questionId": 83, "questionText": "73T3KKERA06V5A3CWIC5QLGB9L4XIM64FT313EVH3GNYCNHFXR3VF79FF4FDJQRN2UCOO6C2ADKG52B6GKFTHGX", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "1.PRV7A89Q17Y9QZ15QBC", "wrongAnswers": ["2.SO5C7BIJIHJS7YIOO5DK47O", "3.V6FJ316MIYTMTL3VNX54X7CL"], "questionOptions": ["1.PRV7A89Q17Y9QZ15QBC", "2.SO5C7BIJIHJS7YIOO5DK47O", "3.V6FJ316MIYTMTL3VNX54X7CL"], "answerLink": "ZWLJU7H2VU"}, {"questionId": 84, "questionText": "T77H809MEI04KFUGWXN6KEJ88SRLKZFBOBLFC3E3IKA64NLENYXUJ3Y0J6H3C68224N0HNQCPYKBCWW504QMRLHMNR34ZQCFTMRVA592FI9BWKQUAVX8", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "1.T0ZNGOQ9UYQY9BACYF39AN0H", "wrongAnswers": ["2.ZZ1TINHVE817YOP6V5PZ2U", "3.O0DDZYBRG0CXCBLSES823PXX6J"], "questionOptions": ["1.T0ZNGOQ9UYQY9BACYF39AN0H", "2.ZZ1TINHVE817YOP6V5PZ2U", "3.O0DDZYBRG0CXCBLSES823PXX6J"], "answerLink": "PK3P57BKFR"}, {"questionId": 85, "questionText": "PIUM68SOAVA8K8XEM8NB65ASO24E1K5TGZF6N5JGLPFP4LCJ6MFORTXIKE86FRT22X95Q67LVA6A67KL", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "2.ILUE0P5W8KKAOAK7", "wrongAnswers": ["1.QLK2JP2UNCEBRLFET1S68SF0D", "3.9E91GVZ4SWAIOV9M2ARCNNEYCAIYQ2"], "questionOptions": ["1.QLK2JP2UNCEBRLFET1S68SF0D", "2.ILUE0P5W8KKAOAK7", "3.9E91GVZ4SWAIOV9M2ARCNNEYCAIYQ2"], "answerLink": "5JDTR284UP"}, {"questionId": 86, "questionText": "196WP7BFIIN6JXURIDX46F2REVAS1J5UB11LW4MU9EQBLELIJ9LV1LSXKE2SVBDF4VLD7THC45K1USQ6GVJE9EK2RHKPBWKQYQJ62HQIGXAVFSJ", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.Q943U9Z7738MMZST9W", "wrongAnswers": ["1.VZH7VYP0TSWFVNN9Z", "2.DFTZIR36G1IS4GE4IEFHN7A3"], "questionOptions": ["1.VZH7VYP0TSWFVNN9Z", "2.DFTZIR36G1IS4GE4IEFHN7A3", "3.Q943U9Z7738MMZST9W"], "answerLink": "X67VAYQNQJ"}, {"questionId": 87, "questionText": "B0079WG0FDB1BPLUZO2BVL0BE25S0XYFTE7BRGGQSH2MY2AQBHY2I9WVWRI6K51AHUHB3SZXIH6ZBK849PGZBRDW7SUB98OBJEAPD8Z1X56O2O0", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "2.CLQ0F3MMHL0JUKT2USWVCYMP", "wrongAnswers": ["1.KEL3X1OWL1VL85U5", "3.608RYR25P4JZ6ANUPL644OME"], "questionOptions": ["1.KEL3X1OWL1VL85U5", "2.CLQ0F3MMHL0JUKT2USWVCYMP", "3.608RYR25P4JZ6ANUPL644OME"], "answerLink": "9OG0FTKHLY"}, {"questionId": 88, "questionText": "LW7CASE75U6OA9Z6UNCGOYIW346YCN5RA5EP5CA0RFFE2PMMT1A0FJ9V6Y8BLZM3QB1F8497ORRF22UNYTZXS21FVBKQI", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "1.JTPDQ1KOE0AZM7ZMZGX", "wrongAnswers": ["2.WNV9ZM7JQLBJ4HDB0W7AIPF4HE", "3.OL1E37HOH2TE4UV82BU4SC"], "questionOptions": ["1.JTPDQ1KOE0AZM7ZMZGX", "2.WNV9ZM7JQLBJ4HDB0W7AIPF4HE", "3.OL1E37HOH2TE4UV82BU4SC"], "answerLink": "6N4W705W8Z"}, {"questionId": 89, "questionText": "47Z7S4VB8VB4CWPSFUU1LWFZE504U5Z9Z8NXUU9CMK9RRTSBRTVPT7SNN14U1PNFT5KQKFEQHUIP6MW7HUAVDPSR03S3B", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "2.QUMLF9KBHKNESFAOVJKR16", "wrongAnswers": ["1.NAJV8HZF9HO8Y5LZVN7L8MJXTNOE6DEL", "3.A8TB36HSZIO80IWNLCRC"], "questionOptions": ["1.NAJV8HZF9HO8Y5LZVN7L8MJXTNOE6DEL", "2.QUMLF9KBHKNESFAOVJKR16", "3.A8TB36HSZIO80IWNLCRC"], "answerLink": "WBL7YPFVKG"}, {"questionId": 90, "questionText": "OWNBJEYLHPWRSQYTZHC5LHCSWX0V50R1P9XN1HXH8Y7IKE0FEW23M2Z7CICPP0L3NISOAVIBCJ87026PXKRUNN6T", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.IOXP03DPZO7PFKRK", "wrongAnswers": ["1.WD2PQQT1NO3W7SRGE", "2.WJ0OWVAKEHWPBM08FYCKM4XZ"], "questionOptions": ["1.WD2PQQT1NO3W7SRGE", "2.WJ0OWVAKEHWPBM08FYCKM4XZ", "3.IOXP03DPZO7PFKRK"], "answerLink": "5EBT5UV8M9"}, {"questionId": 91, "questionText": "OJL6R5QW5IQFSEAZGBPNQ41IT5NP6N51UMN19K8MG4L7B178I2EU49FG68KAUN6RUVE6GKAB21", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.4RRHCAIH3TN6S3O2E2", "wrongAnswers": ["1.95KQENULA6CUKZPQM3VNOHF7J", "2.8J7OKABDO8ANAGVCSDV7ZW1FWPLDMG7"], "questionOptions": ["1.95KQENULA6CUKZPQM3VNOHF7J", "2.8J7OKABDO8ANAGVCSDV7ZW1FWPLDMG7", "3.4RRHCAIH3TN6S3O2E2"], "answerLink": "M12M4TLFJS"}, {"questionId": 92, "questionText": "TPPTI6Y7YSSMXILB3RW4UM9P78YWK2UQ7AS46JZJSZSQNYR76PN5UD4JIMD43U0LSV5TC6L3XLP8KE97GGTV2WZB92PF9C3I9B18DN7W4", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.7EGVB9GDMCBEL1QBBW", "wrongAnswers": ["1.8M7HPEZDK4Y599NZMABGEUY", "2.JPZ7DJSOGD2PEERA9X0YMMQ1D5"], "questionOptions": ["1.8M7HPEZDK4Y599NZMABGEUY", "2.JPZ7DJSOGD2PEERA9X0YMMQ1D5", "3.7EGVB9GDMCBEL1QBBW"], "answerLink": "XVJYLI6BTJ"}, {"questionId": 93, "questionText": "HEY8GGE1KVGDHS3JFHZ7SFH4JJQZEL0ROGZISP28BI4DT3Q5QJ51DIVGSN4VNFMU5K3UUB3N14KDLZOONRQCDGHJ46GJY64KVFJZ0LHLOQDD", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "2.RU8D9W38IL8T9BZ22X", "wrongAnswers": ["1.795KEH9CLR6IRRJ6MUIFVPPHECYX5S", "3.O3CTJJZA1BSCHV4A4RDP5G94U7EVEEG"], "questionOptions": ["1.795KEH9CLR6IRRJ6MUIFVPPHECYX5S", "2.RU8D9W38IL8T9BZ22X", "3.O3CTJJZA1BSCHV4A4RDP5G94U7EVEEG"], "answerLink": "JLH147SEG8"}, {"questionId": 94, "questionText": "7EOTFSV7SH9D4JGK64X8AXP1G29JJIZ57RES3AOA44LZY34R9X4O0DTYIRELVI1K5MYFFM0XYJX0PZOFMHVODK015QKFUHAKBA71X1W3CF8YNJB37N1MP", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.RVI7HU3P25WF3UGQ278GUOFWFNYKR", "wrongAnswers": ["1.7WDWA7HGID2AMGUY0Q1L7O6SRNH", "2.OQVPDGS5XWRV92VP2"], "questionOptions": ["1.7WDWA7HGID2AMGUY0Q1L7O6SRNH", "2.OQVPDGS5XWRV92VP2", "3.RVI7HU3P25WF3UGQ278GUOFWFNYKR"], "answerLink": "NU2JVXAO5Q"}, {"questionId": 95, "questionText": "E5LGVWSTLEWO4DWHG9QT0F73SJ2W9F7MS7QNRAKNTAJM9BD376LEA4CKEDZG2S6U5O9Z7C10SD6ANWEDHEK94ED3AAM4JILSEN4V4ISGATBPZLW", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "2.DDMCA4KBN7VVQWNRB8G6SJE5527V85", "wrongAnswers": ["1.3SY84XVA71KCHJX183EBYE7", "3.DJQUHG9W73OFLTCV0EB6ZEHONJID"], "questionOptions": ["1.3SY84XVA71KCHJX183EBYE7", "2.DDMCA4KBN7VVQWNRB8G6SJE5527V85", "3.DJQUHG9W73OFLTCV0EB6ZEHONJID"], "answerLink": "C0677TTWE2"}, {"questionId": 96, "questionText": "U6AOKW9HWOJAB7V5JTNHBKV5N6CT4XQBO347LVKDD4TZMBSQOBXNJUDZ1FBVO8Z9Z5UCU5MVQNL3TCXJ0IQRB4Z71N0SK", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "1.2EVYOSR58LXR44HBXQQGLZU", "wrongAnswers": ["2.ZSMP5D8WMV4FANOYW98", "3.4TRR9LH2EPA89GF43L2J"], "questionOptions": ["1.2EVYOSR58LXR44HBXQQGLZU", "2.ZSMP5D8WMV4FANOYW98", "3.4TRR9LH2EPA89GF43L2J"], "answerLink": "HY8OG7LJBD"}, {"questionId": 97, "questionText": "DQ1FMEO1LLQMF02S8U929THP2F2ATIZMDVSTDKRBQIFFQGCLBBU6VRVHF1AR6IHSFWG1A8CF5YFN", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "1.4N9KHU7IDEK45TS70ROWER7TZ", "wrongAnswers": ["2.XN2F776XBLMSGQM4SUQO", "3.8Q111J4QW707F71RFIQE1ZBNX"], "questionOptions": ["1.4N9KHU7IDEK45TS70ROWER7TZ", "2.XN2F776XBLMSGQM4SUQO", "3.8Q111J4QW707F71RFIQE1ZBNX"], "answerLink": "J0P0HL0XQU"}, {"questionId": 98, "questionText": "LPPHEWQZOKLPCYKHY1PO82MVI8537E556VDC75812DBTL9TXVGNMCYHF0GAAPDNAOC4K59FR1MVN", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "1.P9M88OYUHAD6GEO3KKHV3E1", "wrongAnswers": ["2.Y8KRJZWQBWDH8TCY5DR3KMQ", "3.AXM1JAND4MZEXX8EOVTV1"], "questionOptions": ["1.P9M88OYUHAD6GEO3KKHV3E1", "2.Y8KRJZWQBWDH8TCY5DR3KMQ", "3.AXM1JAND4MZEXX8EOVTV1"], "answerLink": "8E2YBOHOT1"}, {"questionId": 99, "questionText": "287VBX0ATSWWH71V1C6NJYUBO1145O0DB8C6V8Y1RLBFNDQ2P0V2H5RC0GFOTJGT4HKVDTYQRU9", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.VUB5CCHQF33X4Z77S1X7X0XUH4", "wrongAnswers": ["1.71GKJ8G2T2K8I6JD5WVOPJ4", "2.0HKBYGJWD4JCKAN7HJTIM3YV"], "questionOptions": ["1.71GKJ8G2T2K8I6JD5WVOPJ4", "2.0HKBYGJWD4JCKAN7HJTIM3YV", "3.VUB5CCHQF33X4Z77S1X7X0XUH4"], "answerLink": "DM0BQBKYNG"}, {"questionId": 100, "questionText": "0UMD278WS0CTQJYVLO5JYK33PMHA0VZUSDP7HT9KNRJZI4DB2CG7ZAMVTUGWPNWATLYMB2B6UUWU83XMAZYBDIW9M6IRN1O9745YT7AAPDC1QV7E", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.EXZI6W2VJMMZ690DUAGZFSEYH5WRB19S", "wrongAnswers": ["1.G58765E9XPO9UPE9JDUD6IBIW", "2.ADSM4DTHC0O8TBZ2NIWS"], "questionOptions": ["1.G58765E9XPO9UPE9JDUD6IBIW", "2.ADSM4DTHC0O8TBZ2NIWS", "3.EXZI6W2VJMMZ690DUAGZFSEYH5WRB19S"], "answerLink": "UJLMT0N779"}, {"questionId": 101, "questionText": "QKX6HG97UGTCW39O2B27FLG7YMOP7V0TQ478GC3XKSU59O4J2F83VPER8AC3MO3JI94", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "2.XSNBEPGE7S6BH6VKKQVCFO", "wrongAnswers": ["1.7ONFFBVLMXT5A15X4042H7I", "3.B68J9V05ZBA0HQ47W6ADXYASMQN6"], "questionOptions": ["1.7ONFFBVLMXT5A15X4042H7I", "2.XSNBEPGE7S6BH6VKKQVCFO", "3.B68J9V05ZBA0HQ47W6ADXYASMQN6"], "answerLink": "2GH9MY2T69"}, {"questionId": 102, "questionText": "LH1F4NQKY0MHI2JPCC7ETNNYI9998BOTZ3T56HAGUS419TT8Y15QO3CIQMSZOJ687NM9C06U400QU7SHOGVF8MWWA59MWFR256G9Y1D4TQKDE7JO3LXFFI0E", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.L5QW0SIMP675BPNXEWBO9MG649", "wrongAnswers": ["1.VLW3ADSNNFN4SM1DGNSJE1Y08J5", "2.5S85G5Q54V8UBQE5TSK7PX52RY"], "questionOptions": ["1.VLW3ADSNNFN4SM1DGNSJE1Y08J5", "2.5S85G5Q54V8UBQE5TSK7PX52RY", "3.L5QW0SIMP675BPNXEWBO9MG649"], "answerLink": "8R8AZUL9IO"}, {"questionId": 103, "questionText": "PWCZYQVP3KQIFOVON5BEKOY8L8YAXOW2RVFULFVW8DX3CTFW0T2U478WSJREJ4F21YDCGMG9KQAUV6XEPO", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "1.JFXG2082QM8AZ2A7FVVKDH4MA1T", "wrongAnswers": ["2.G2UXK4KVNCK7GQV6", "3.H3PTPFKGA3211RTTAD24"], "questionOptions": ["1.JFXG2082QM8AZ2A7FVVKDH4MA1T", "2.G2UXK4KVNCK7GQV6", "3.H3PTPFKGA3211RTTAD24"], "answerLink": "6NIR7GQAQ9"}, {"questionId": 104, "questionText": "6LSSCVI98AP84WH9S5PCSXRRJIQ35KAEV53KEO8VXWTU3419QI0Y8ZB943QKWV6WY88XN0FFOQDM3BKLTYHE2IFNDCWX1F4QUNKG455Z6UOKFPX5VRN", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "1.LLPI3I8C86S8NYC2I1JQ", "wrongAnswers": ["2.2VR0JK5INQAOOBM62", "3.EM04KEGOWYCNZ5AWRXGRNNA67ZT"], "questionOptions": ["1.LLPI3I8C86S8NYC2I1JQ", "2.2VR0JK5INQAOOBM62", "3.EM04KEGOWYCNZ5AWRXGRNNA67ZT"], "answerLink": "UKXGLCYODU"}, {"questionId": 105, "questionText": "1J81Q02TL150IYMIANS3EHNF7Z4GR83UIF48OF2UVQ1FPD9KT8I6EAYQ3N0NSM6380HMGEPBOJYCBNE071FHY6I2JM3CWTQ", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "1.NC0I04BZEGF54HNM653FS", "wrongAnswers": ["2.9DR7XQ6AAFZJ110UZ4PJTZX", "3.JWLWOIZ9YRU4LL29K"], "questionOptions": ["1.NC0I04BZEGF54HNM653FS", "2.9DR7XQ6AAFZJ110UZ4PJTZX", "3.JWLWOIZ9YRU4LL29K"], "answerLink": "49GQVTN84A"}, {"questionId": 106, "questionText": "6T5MUZV1NMSZXA1AR4X9XLHTN8CXHUW8ZJZ1VM6NK5TGCYQD56U0VQU9YT9KN3PZNAREA37STAW09KZTTR2SWQK6", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "2.O9IX4BWDW9U72LQ56J", "wrongAnswers": ["1.ESMF6YXFYBUXJA382AOQ8", "3.XMHKELRKIOS85GMNCNJ"], "questionOptions": ["1.ESMF6YXFYBUXJA382AOQ8", "2.O9IX4BWDW9U72LQ56J", "3.XMHKELRKIOS85GMNCNJ"], "answerLink": "RS3Z9JBMNO"}, {"questionId": 107, "questionText": "12QJ3QX49N0WYEIWW7BI9Z2EWDLSN1YALJTESW4MZ8VMG5NU6EEOFVR2UBO300EBBDE9UG044RCS5F0VG", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.UJCQVSMLX0LJY12XBCLNXMN4D3OS", "wrongAnswers": ["1.8CDUZN8JJ5NLR6Q7EQ", "2.R818BHSJM25BSHAVEWYTF4HGGCOF"], "questionOptions": ["1.8CDUZN8JJ5NLR6Q7EQ", "2.R818BHSJM25BSHAVEWYTF4HGGCOF", "3.UJCQVSMLX0LJY12XBCLNXMN4D3OS"], "answerLink": "HDK8SHEM5O"}, {"questionId": 108, "questionText": "2N8L0GKU1NI1LGQNYBKDPYVLA9A32Q55GB3AMRRSAPUJHPK1M6WMRFKN919S30OBA57YJOOVJLG9S6ZCUCNOS6RVW16BKUX0HGFXKZPF5", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "2.PNSL355YO2FSA8EF7DC8S5QF7VGV", "wrongAnswers": ["1.5V00DU0Y7WPZK3L33ZNX6M2KIUM", "3.CI44ZD4TJEP3HOCL2LTGZQFL8F1IC7U"], "questionOptions": ["1.5V00DU0Y7WPZK3L33ZNX6M2KIUM", "2.PNSL355YO2FSA8EF7DC8S5QF7VGV", "3.CI44ZD4TJEP3HOCL2LTGZQFL8F1IC7U"], "answerLink": "H9HUUCEIJK"}, {"questionId": 109, "questionText": "YDW1NJH62ZKT37NG5EFL6DWDI2LETHMIDZ2W1H0ALOVYRCUZJJFAC6ANMZLKP3A23J9EC2791GKXCD7FPZ8YLACCO9KCBDDUPXNVQ9G4GMFQL7QZ", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.6U2IE4DYJJTI7US6K71K1HU6T7YEP7DJ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.F5GZKV68YAHTKUL11EH", "2.8DV6EZ7R6UMF3B3JX7VYA13CV8ZCYIOF"], "questionOptions": ["1.F5GZKV68YAHTKUL11EH", "2.8DV6EZ7R6UMF3B3JX7VYA13CV8ZCYIOF", "3.6U2IE4DYJJTI7US6K71K1HU6T7YEP7DJ"], "answerLink": "9GXQ8OB2RX"}, {"questionId": 110, "questionText": "BD3EDLCP6H7W94OU21YM1XNRSM9PVSL96WRKN23R78JNIYGK4Z1Y1WF8N9E0FX8IFDC1", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "1.Z1AYZZTF9IY3MSN0WH5MCSU7473U97DR", "wrongAnswers": ["2.JN3ICK0JZG0U7NA5", "3.58G7MBFO62COMU500NDZVOSYHW"], "questionOptions": ["1.Z1AYZZTF9IY3MSN0WH5MCSU7473U97DR", "2.JN3ICK0JZG0U7NA5", "3.58G7MBFO62COMU500NDZVOSYHW"], "answerLink": "MGUEO28ULO"}, {"questionId": 111, "questionText": "LHFZT139XEYJKEPY413OI292G3VY6CDCGEE8Q8ZX5JU160UUXMFUG6FT5OWUSVYYLLOGVBES87BTXXEX771BWDXI8RSX", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "2.UIYF848WV04C89FLK", "wrongAnswers": ["1.8U58BCW4X7G9LIIDJBGKJ89PN0Q457T", "3.WMU8R1PNE9MMGGHW7MR4M3R"], "questionOptions": ["1.8U58BCW4X7G9LIIDJBGKJ89PN0Q457T", "2.UIYF848WV04C89FLK", "3.WMU8R1PNE9MMGGHW7MR4M3R"], "answerLink": "LSKY4CSIV3"}, {"questionId": 112, "questionText": "S4ITW0DTOAHGY3DLLRVHBXA052JH47X629GZXX5OKY9SFOM6CITLYHES9QQPRX1PIBHKQ3ZTKWM2L7D8EFLNTJOV7AOHM1WQ9Q4WGCENN4K8YWRTD", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.FP6IOMOQZ17PBGRT7OXG0XDA", "wrongAnswers": ["1.UPIQWPK5HIDYYPR6I4LQ4RN80VYQ67", "2.4MNBTC1LVGTR6A5NVXJR"], "questionOptions": ["1.UPIQWPK5HIDYYPR6I4LQ4RN80VYQ67", "2.4MNBTC1LVGTR6A5NVXJR", "3.FP6IOMOQZ17PBGRT7OXG0XDA"], "answerLink": "B71PSW6AVI"}, {"questionId": 113, "questionText": "JTJ4NXFSO1D1BY2HIZBDHIMR6MNGJM02A0FR4U3NRTH8UDALF8RDOTWPCJD2UPMQSCMNCWOWW13AGA2SUZHJ1K2NO58J39QX2R24WGT2TCHUNFM7VVT", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "3.SEB0RRRHB50FJKMH", "wrongAnswers": ["1.6W4FBSYEDCIL06EFX4AUC9QQ", "2.ISZ3DJQQZEAQIEH1GQ3XP"], "questionOptions": ["1.6W4FBSYEDCIL06EFX4AUC9QQ", "2.ISZ3DJQQZEAQIEH1GQ3XP", "3.SEB0RRRHB50FJKMH"], "answerLink": "ORCY9MNSQC"}, {"questionId": 114, "questionText": "ADZC5WPRNRIRDBXUFCPLTJ9052XGUIR2XFGECW9UNLT1QDTMLGB41LU38D97HKFMM9IZU4MBCAVSBQOO496IAM5RCVQ5ZPASVJCCIZ1WANANH", "questionCategory": "Regola 3", "correctAnswers": "2.ZTGYMFFZGZMGUHURDYTX8", "wrongAnswers": ["1.8QJBPK4L8RWMDD7396", "3.RX5D6X96H0WU9WX7C"], "questionOptions": ["1.8QJBPK4L8RWMDD7396", "2.ZTGYMFFZGZMGUHURDYTX8", "3.RX5D6X96H0WU9WX7C"], "answerLink": "OYI8AWR8OL"}, {"questionId": 115, "questionText": "9IGXSDSBGHO7QVZI3LOW7QVXW6UP9AVQ7BCPKJXW85EIFFTGQ28DOBKY3CYUMVXBDE509GYQIBKSK5DRQQY213F1J8TRWFSSXVG720MZIH9D9CTL13W8HP", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "2.SJK876RPEUDLQLW499RS", "wrongAnswers": ["1.JYQ4IV4V76PBUQVPHD2WVZB1XYJCH", "3.IQQULLOKRMLEM1HEA9BJD8BS3"], "questionOptions": ["1.JYQ4IV4V76PBUQVPHD2WVZB1XYJCH", "2.SJK876RPEUDLQLW499RS", "3.IQQULLOKRMLEM1HEA9BJD8BS3"], "answerLink": "AQR0GEWGAZ"}, {"questionId": 116, "questionText": "6TCWNQRR3XEO4VR1WPWBQ0OC4APAAIUUUQ7Y0W7LD3C62I3P0WPS5CU7LPJBU622MZXA4OYZGRDM6CPU8MIVUTU4U1TJS3Q5TE8WZ2VYQ9", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "1.CQNPA7I1A9FQG5U2J7", "wrongAnswers": ["2.Q5XJI7EY69WSI84PU2K6", "3.8U1ABDYFDFFIKDRIIT"], "questionOptions": ["1.CQNPA7I1A9FQG5U2J7", "2.Q5XJI7EY69WSI84PU2K6", "3.8U1ABDYFDFFIKDRIIT"], "answerLink": "EH63KX8Y5O"}, {"questionId": 117, "questionText": "R5I9DZFAW19IAX902WDUMU6Q5ZW8CVKD54R9UVUYER0808KW92AGILXSF02OCBCDKYT57DAYMXM7KIR1", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "1.4EWERBRIRK5UY1DJY50VVX1HEJWY", "wrongAnswers": ["2.KK0QG78KI79TPAKIJM", "3.QEAJVFQ4LG369NS9E3GF052B"], "questionOptions": ["1.4EWERBRIRK5UY1DJY50VVX1HEJWY", "2.KK0QG78KI79TPAKIJM", "3.QEAJVFQ4LG369NS9E3GF052B"], "answerLink": "D9QDP3ANOG"}, {"questionId": 118, "questionText": "Z3RPRQFAKDSDZRE0D9V6OFDZYENDFA0X11RBPGAQN1G5XHGL1OWZFWI8LPG00WHTSS650EBWK1AC111K5EJ24U5429UM0ZF7IMP42Q6QTYTWSN1Q9NH4A4T8ICW5TFH", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "3.8YRGCH3XTZYY3MKTX8L06JPJAR", "wrongAnswers": ["1.2RDX86CZ7MRD8GKREQC7VZ7YWKS42X95", "2.TNQQKVNUR28SCSLK3N3NFMM"], "questionOptions": ["1.2RDX86CZ7MRD8GKREQC7VZ7YWKS42X95", "2.TNQQKVNUR28SCSLK3N3NFMM", "3.8YRGCH3XTZYY3MKTX8L06JPJAR"], "answerLink": "P03XXBCUMY"}, {"questionId": 119, "questionText": "LFL1NBKNLB7H342I9GUGHT5ELTRXTW7BAJI9BCLWQ03L3D5YWQS9YQJR8S0BL936GVBL0TWJ1VUJXEMSWARHSQIRO8YIVQ8I2NF83C4R6T9YL5I7FPH23PH30D", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "2.11260HYLYSMNDQRH7WY9KR0S1", "wrongAnswers": ["1.FGDYWSCTVXQTA1QNK07AKY11", "3.TMW9DPVRPLOEQ8CI"], "questionOptions": ["1.FGDYWSCTVXQTA1QNK07AKY11", "2.11260HYLYSMNDQRH7WY9KR0S1", "3.TMW9DPVRPLOEQ8CI"], "answerLink": "6NOXDZODZ5"}, {"questionId": 120, "questionText": "KPXUMF8VCFHK76EZJZ2VEYAAZFDWUDIPZVXNVF2LW6T4HWWQY56VK7A8BDPZPC65FTM41MPG1MT", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "3.TNKKLFJXZH5F4YXI2P8", "wrongAnswers": ["1.FHSWDBMJMOH7CWS281SYH8KY", "2.20OO9Q8JW62Q3A9V7X"], "questionOptions": ["1.FHSWDBMJMOH7CWS281SYH8KY", "2.20OO9Q8JW62Q3A9V7X", "3.TNKKLFJXZH5F4YXI2P8"], "answerLink": "GOTHEFEJHR"}, {"questionId": 121, "questionText": "7MN3M34EQGEMDQLUK0IDG8J3SYK8JLWASTVDP4KZPYQN63EZYBCQNA4AQ0UG1N9IRUKU75M86564PEU", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "3.VGVMH4QAVB61YWVXZ1IYGLA0645XSG9N", "wrongAnswers": ["1.3J09Z3KKOC1ZQ6IAJ1O1B", "2.MVQFDX5KMTGI19LR1AICPFHMN2D1G"], "questionOptions": ["1.3J09Z3KKOC1ZQ6IAJ1O1B", "2.MVQFDX5KMTGI19LR1AICPFHMN2D1G", "3.VGVMH4QAVB61YWVXZ1IYGLA0645XSG9N"], "answerLink": "H0098GVWU0"}, {"questionId": 122, "questionText": "G8H1BQWALZTAITGPY7JTAC48E72KFRII53PDZWKU5JU19TV18M4HFMQAF7SCPTKTZ2YWFUTHJVB4WEHH1BMA7WE9WSHHCQE59CVD6M", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "1.T5CZ4RNPHX0D2CGLGWQ47XI21", "wrongAnswers": ["2.7WY03UVGB7X0OTFGJYOK7", "3.I553CVP05Y3BHZSL"], "questionOptions": ["1.T5CZ4RNPHX0D2CGLGWQ47XI21", "2.7WY03UVGB7X0OTFGJYOK7", "3.I553CVP05Y3BHZSL"], "answerLink": "PLBEDI4AGO"}, {"questionId": 123, "questionText": "2TLFINFDLWVX5BJWKGXKCFWAR366SISS3NPYF82VWYFCYAQWCJWHDZUFIPO5OZF6JGHQ109CV44GR9RDP2IZJBGQV070AXS0RBVYWP8P0QYU0MDXJ0L4GI1", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "3.0X57BMSCRUQBSZF7S8869014JNOS31", "wrongAnswers": ["1.PDV6MVJFJ2TIHYQP66E", "2.D03H7H7ARGDJ5TIH16PDC"], "questionOptions": ["1.PDV6MVJFJ2TIHYQP66E", "2.D03H7H7ARGDJ5TIH16PDC", "3.0X57BMSCRUQBSZF7S8869014JNOS31"], "answerLink": "4XA4FKK4Y9"}, {"questionId": 124, "questionText": "ZN5HY52XXLWX233YIUXZ7OW858WGO9TY17BCVTPN3Y73FT705D766SB0QZ8KVYFHPWEO44TW62ICFZKLPDCY0WWQF3NG7YY2YI2LA5VN6Z7BQK", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "1.Q9MA9NDNRQXZ69BZDV2FAJ", "wrongAnswers": ["2.ZYNFUTYGIAIVAMWNZIMLD1XY", "3.NHMVEDLH5BPAGVS73T3A6MM2DDBD8"], "questionOptions": ["1.Q9MA9NDNRQXZ69BZDV2FAJ", "2.ZYNFUTYGIAIVAMWNZIMLD1XY", "3.NHMVEDLH5BPAGVS73T3A6MM2DDBD8"], "answerLink": "YO7YMI1B6E"}, {"questionId": 125, "questionText": "O58EA1D499K0D13MSL14V0FVRJ32P4BAE254E7RFQ28CE5R8QRMB16B3SLFX4TJBEE8TM6D8N7Z52TDZ4U2IM34C8YTW4O6JB", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "3.TO30BLI6XQ469L7QQIA2AFBGAJKGI1L6", "wrongAnswers": ["1.CV94ME8MFEHEHVO8F5", "2.O533O5FY3VSTGVS21KZ09A"], "questionOptions": ["1.CV94ME8MFEHEHVO8F5", "2.O533O5FY3VSTGVS21KZ09A", "3.TO30BLI6XQ469L7QQIA2AFBGAJKGI1L6"], "answerLink": "F8BDWMY3AY"}, {"questionId": 126, "questionText": "2SVAD3JVUMBST2P1DZEGWPXEBQD1NZ8HEEHVHZ0OWR4APC28FCSXCO6CISKAUTIC8AQBRR34VRT4QSJKDUQF04364ZONLJ6V", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "2.2GMZXDQ674VMP8YBZCX6Z3U1M", "wrongAnswers": ["1.ZYZYYUBKP4QQDBNB67BUAT1K", "3.5NV6N8VVGJLSLSICAM"], "questionOptions": ["1.ZYZYYUBKP4QQDBNB67BUAT1K", "2.2GMZXDQ674VMP8YBZCX6Z3U1M", "3.5NV6N8VVGJLSLSICAM"], "answerLink": "OB3Q2LBLBB"}, {"questionId": 127, "questionText": "JKWVUS2P9MYPPXCJZFHL795JZT9I44VMU5V76ZFPEKZY7RP0IXX74A4JMNA73M4CUUF3YBZZW80W4K6KDUB12OGB32EYI3A4KDM4M2EXPMYLOU", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "1.5AGVG0ZZOM6N5AIQSOUG0M", "wrongAnswers": ["2.Y00VUCNMHSPK4AAV2OF37IJODGS", "3.IRPLUFFEROJ6TWHGXGI0J0EX"], "questionOptions": ["1.5AGVG0ZZOM6N5AIQSOUG0M", "2.Y00VUCNMHSPK4AAV2OF37IJODGS", "3.IRPLUFFEROJ6TWHGXGI0J0EX"], "answerLink": "FKKSIJLB0S"}, {"questionId": 128, "questionText": "FO3T87SN77WVGE9V4D4FCEVPQF7I85S68Q1RGS2ZFZSGHH222HV4OH42A9X6LA2YA", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "1.5NIV134GIDQ8LBZ6N", "wrongAnswers": ["2.0K4FJ7L5AEQVXJIBQ0EXVP2BUZDX", "3.S0VY0FJYI8DZGW7D6Z91O8L"], "questionOptions": ["1.5NIV134GIDQ8LBZ6N", "2.0K4FJ7L5AEQVXJIBQ0EXVP2BUZDX", "3.S0VY0FJYI8DZGW7D6Z91O8L"], "answerLink": "KJV416HZ8G"}, {"questionId": 129, "questionText": "S3HYAOR8HX14SGSUQANN1A3RC89Y3VEPYGM9PJTXEIBMIU5WX8OIG15G3CBQMMC5MJILXLJCS0O619BLC4R7SJV2Y28XNNRQJGGTMQBFCXIW7FQZQ43F", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "1.LM44SMJKEPKCVYTN9QKS2DAJVMONP2", "wrongAnswers": ["2.ETA7NB0BV3UGZV9TIJT", "3.OJLMKBOI9HZ5BMZMKSSE0JODNPG"], "questionOptions": ["1.LM44SMJKEPKCVYTN9QKS2DAJVMONP2", "2.ETA7NB0BV3UGZV9TIJT", "3.OJLMKBOI9HZ5BMZMKSSE0JODNPG"], "answerLink": "LJWLVL17YR"}, {"questionId": 130, "questionText": "7W4C53LYE272HW95M9WCLFNH1DPC4N1C0BPSS458UUX7ZUCLV0ASH92XC4CBCOHEI899T28E3Q23LXQA4RWV63KJXVCDVSJKGXBD44RYBS4XRKV9V7O5OWAP9", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "3.SFLI3BERIECIL06H09", "wrongAnswers": ["1.KJGQNUEUQ3FVA2LO2ND62", "2.Z1EKNUH6EB5MGJKF9M9"], "questionOptions": ["1.KJGQNUEUQ3FVA2LO2ND62", "2.Z1EKNUH6EB5MGJKF9M9", "3.SFLI3BERIECIL06H09"], "answerLink": "FR9Z0WLVF2"}, {"questionId": 131, "questionText": "OTP9RDBDGHGO8MJODI8WKEPJPZCZNLQTZVSVBUSB9KSKEDBNOJAFAAT4RPOKCRYVGU1S7416H963AAQ1SOAGN5M5ON3X3C27M6YDVBMGTB", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "1.WFYF1RUUFPJ1BFBWIVL9K", "wrongAnswers": ["2.T84S5NANHNWO16LD5", "3.RN4YCOX95HOVXI03XVQE"], "questionOptions": ["1.WFYF1RUUFPJ1BFBWIVL9K", "2.T84S5NANHNWO16LD5", "3.RN4YCOX95HOVXI03XVQE"], "answerLink": "VR5FF8OZC7"}, {"questionId": 132, "questionText": "XQ3DQK2094DH24S4EXDMUE0AZ4MU3MVQ3I2QYZBEIVQXXRBNZJUXH9D917FSS90GVAW6OL3CY3R7AHLS0V8SL7GSBRWBG8LW195IAZ1LE2NSSA0SP2544", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "1.F8D6D76OK8O4NHN4OHDIHVHWIQO", "wrongAnswers": ["2.9NYVHTLT4ICLH5IGE36L34", "3.9ZJPAH2W7PYWF3SXUYCGKLTDUU8IVQJU"], "questionOptions": ["1.F8D6D76OK8O4NHN4OHDIHVHWIQO", "2.9NYVHTLT4ICLH5IGE36L34", "3.9ZJPAH2W7PYWF3SXUYCGKLTDUU8IVQJU"], "answerLink": "PW2E08BBBZ"}, {"questionId": 133, "questionText": "ZEBKQF4ZAEGA6IOY15LW01YUBCFBEM80KFWYOS7X3QKE7PPOML3EW4ZRH2COL5CEGYMSE3MCRMNYGG92JYP7F38DWO1GRLE4FO2EMG72DGYTBGKBJO01078TD0L9E0", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "2.G92286VG613XZ02HNZ00M", "wrongAnswers": ["1.4DUL59S7U5CQZCXF1ETOMKAV15E811IF", "3.FWEG7FZCD1S5Z8XR40CV6AS"], "questionOptions": ["1.4DUL59S7U5CQZCXF1ETOMKAV15E811IF", "2.G92286VG613XZ02HNZ00M", "3.FWEG7FZCD1S5Z8XR40CV6AS"], "answerLink": "MAO4TKOC7B"}, {"questionId": 134, "questionText": "2V48S0QRJO1N6PJLQRRIX8PNISRUD1VBXJI58TOEHZI75UVY0CQH8UL91ZET3AEFMAY94DG2M9WF9HTJHXGOGHQUMA9RNM9E4O6JAH75FDU7U2GVG8OZSWIEGQ", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "2.0XO5Z4YJ289GC96XUTC4SA4X", "wrongAnswers": ["1.BSLPCS679HHLBGXVEDJZ5B2OTN", "3.Z377BES1X9ORNFJTPY"], "questionOptions": ["1.BSLPCS679HHLBGXVEDJZ5B2OTN", "2.0XO5Z4YJ289GC96XUTC4SA4X", "3.Z377BES1X9ORNFJTPY"], "answerLink": "GZAUM5IP00"}, {"questionId": 135, "questionText": "HQYZMP3RPP8I2EINXXQLXX42E2KIFZS6QGEQ6QQKQL5DBPS068NRG5235IR5WMHEVM1HWTWI8DX", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "2.2D7GXS8PI4E89RLB6UPC16P9K2X8SMO", "wrongAnswers": ["1.1NJLO8W8V9ZY3349XMCJE", "3.DYF65B4R6F2FL6DR8XKRO"], "questionOptions": ["1.1NJLO8W8V9ZY3349XMCJE", "2.2D7GXS8PI4E89RLB6UPC16P9K2X8SMO", "3.DYF65B4R6F2FL6DR8XKRO"], "answerLink": "B2YHJVZ0GA"}, {"questionId": 136, "questionText": "WH5HGWYV0M6CHBS1TK4RJ727EXE6R5FAL75JXKGC47P2Y8JJT6UEKUMVKESGYDDFG1UQHE4K6KF47FMZG", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "2.33VTQ6XHEJYMZXUHHWONVB", "wrongAnswers": ["1.IXA19ZX2TL5N1J4NLZS153E", "3.2W4SRK0JG8D93X01SH4GELPL"], "questionOptions": ["1.IXA19ZX2TL5N1J4NLZS153E", "2.33VTQ6XHEJYMZXUHHWONVB", "3.2W4SRK0JG8D93X01SH4GELPL"], "answerLink": "N4UTT1RUV8"}, {"questionId": 137, "questionText": "PK6W3WG87JNU1M7FSZDTH342MVK1EPDTQV3JAJIN6V9KSQ6A1E9W5AAH49TXZW4A7QFJF657G4P5ET41GPSCC49G2YVP8DM1UMZC2PSBCWGGT26HAWPACIZAVE94", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "3.8350SYCDWGY8EK1LFMQLF0M0", "wrongAnswers": ["1.V48JODC24X2I268Z", "2.XST5HEPSNPZAF06LVUECPB"], "questionOptions": ["1.V48JODC24X2I268Z", "2.XST5HEPSNPZAF06LVUECPB", "3.8350SYCDWGY8EK1LFMQLF0M0"], "answerLink": "SSVUJQEMLP"}, {"questionId": 138, "questionText": "9NX6M5ZMZDFT8YD1EHK80A8J7TP5AYBB43S6T8VRHF6JOM81KL4G2NM6OIBS6EYCCHSKAW5EM7BEQ91NQ0MVBM6QQ1GREPH", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "2.7LVY2MHTIK9KXJ8JTUWZQY9J", "wrongAnswers": ["1.AZLW5XDLKNM6KI4CUOBL1UCK2A", "3.W4WUZBY9KTKU64Y20K"], "questionOptions": ["1.AZLW5XDLKNM6KI4CUOBL1UCK2A", "2.7LVY2MHTIK9KXJ8JTUWZQY9J", "3.W4WUZBY9KTKU64Y20K"], "answerLink": "OP7SO66JEJ"}, {"questionId": 139, "questionText": "N141SZH6BTJB1QSWKW9GHLV19P9WJ1PKWBRFXYEX4WKQ461CBFUR1H5N27OGO3O7", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "2.L98FOCLZ7TK0YFX9XF43D9HMFLQP8BZ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.QF8N15UKJFNR2YF7PJ", "3.3F1HPAQJX3NXWYHKOM351ORC"], "questionOptions": ["1.QF8N15UKJFNR2YF7PJ", "2.L98FOCLZ7TK0YFX9XF43D9HMFLQP8BZ", "3.3F1HPAQJX3NXWYHKOM351ORC"], "answerLink": "KQVKPRSAAI"}, {"questionId": 140, "questionText": "OH8829H9KSVV8T79OYTUGDO3LDF01D5PXV6WTYNWI1I7FYT2SQ7YE8SZX8Q4WC2QYIPK0G5SCLT5C7CCT0NR9ESFH929YHU4I66QY95CUYBW2KTA2XGYEODOYY8HV9Z", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "1.R3MLLFCY68WBY6VRH73", "wrongAnswers": ["2.W0IB1O9YVFNZX0PTZ6RV", "3.2997A8HC4VUN143T"], "questionOptions": ["1.R3MLLFCY68WBY6VRH73", "2.W0IB1O9YVFNZX0PTZ6RV", "3.2997A8HC4VUN143T"], "answerLink": "DH8T5EXHAI"}, {"questionId": 141, "questionText": "11PBG6FCR3E0VDYPTR925LRSZC91AGPAN38BZ965D134K1IV07IS3UVNRLLHB0BJ0JIRQYTZIEYLAJ30I3QDMQQ5O3U6A22XKDCJI7GMIDIX5YZP7NX", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "3.GF38H5YWTKGMOZUEF", "wrongAnswers": ["1.UQGOHDEYM8AV1GZ1C0EI0MB4BRP0", "2.N0OD22E9LYRYVMHJ30Y4X"], "questionOptions": ["1.UQGOHDEYM8AV1GZ1C0EI0MB4BRP0", "2.N0OD22E9LYRYVMHJ30Y4X", "3.GF38H5YWTKGMOZUEF"], "answerLink": "HXK26KO2AG"}, {"questionId": 142, "questionText": "IYRIJPOG3R18VJNAAZOCB0ANXZSK8UVH6JN9W174BKQLPK8H711DAX3D68V3W4W568HCTOF6VI7KQRATK1JGF8KFDAI", "questionCategory": "Regola 4", "correctAnswers": "1.3AQXHQGO7EU4NZLNC3K8", "wrongAnswers": ["2.4CGPKX0K6LIK51Q5PBM1OKO8QKINLRCW", "3.MK4NX56WRFEB6767LLY"], "questionOptions": ["1.3AQXHQGO7EU4NZLNC3K8", "2.4CGPKX0K6LIK51Q5PBM1OKO8QKINLRCW", "3.MK4NX56WRFEB6767LLY"], "answerLink": "VS17BI5FSY"}, {"questionId": 143, "questionText": "P4YDN3ZEQT1CJY69D2KEPASJQC5YMYP5JK5B25LK8ZZGGL1UV7VUG603N9GJVW1PHRAMYUF2U835NZJKGRD5QUEZZ21", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "1.56L89P5947W15ED2RX1RRRWF0PH4L", "wrongAnswers": ["2.YGTQFDZTNLGXL90TI95A3YCI1LM", "3.F4FIWQ078FTRC84017HAM5803ZZI0R54"], "questionOptions": ["1.56L89P5947W15ED2RX1RRRWF0PH4L", "2.YGTQFDZTNLGXL90TI95A3YCI1LM", "3.F4FIWQ078FTRC84017HAM5803ZZI0R54"], "answerLink": "RIQ9ITIWW0"}, {"questionId": 144, "questionText": "86MOQ0TSDIDQW2XY1HE6IEPGN44M0Z20BTZBF5IC6KCQVRGAK7M750E337BC8ON53LRPQP", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "2.10EPNIX8P5N6NJ3XRRXO9", "wrongAnswers": ["1.SOWSMS65LRRK3ZLXNR70M", "3.XDT15YJ5AXCTS7WN7T4P44NVIX"], "questionOptions": ["1.SOWSMS65LRRK3ZLXNR70M", "2.10EPNIX8P5N6NJ3XRRXO9", "3.XDT15YJ5AXCTS7WN7T4P44NVIX"], "answerLink": "5LD3PQQSBC"}, {"questionId": 145, "questionText": "PRESRPGSZLK5CHE3PAJXLI59P0U31KH8RP34FKZEF68C2T8XOR0HLCDHA3WG9RMDMINJ7VHD1YINGNDNJELA6HXRTSSXL8XCD1BJPPZRH", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "3.2ALV6MKO7QO2BS54", "wrongAnswers": ["1.PSC708YVZ0MQF3RH8EZK07CKL", "2.GQ14C1F30FP7JL86BOYIRV"], "questionOptions": ["1.PSC708YVZ0MQF3RH8EZK07CKL", "2.GQ14C1F30FP7JL86BOYIRV", "3.2ALV6MKO7QO2BS54"], "answerLink": "AXL9WL8GIG"}, {"questionId": 146, "questionText": "1H218K8BAXXAGGRCS2LX8VO8VDSN452MLPQF9AV931EAAEFBXM2ZPATTQXJM4WEQJAOMTELQZUO7TDG", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "2.H6UZAQJ9DBCDPJPNEMVYD", "wrongAnswers": ["1.2HAO0RSNL3176QQN0PS9J0SLFJP24L", "3.NRD93OWZ25F8KZ2X5AGG"], "questionOptions": ["1.2HAO0RSNL3176QQN0PS9J0SLFJP24L", "2.H6UZAQJ9DBCDPJPNEMVYD", "3.NRD93OWZ25F8KZ2X5AGG"], "answerLink": "P4I5DWKM2K"}, {"questionId": 147, "questionText": "TBS2PXXAC9SJJLU9VVSH0OXV9WJ4XTI2YEC18GXO6EFWUQNMDEJG5QHI1KDM5DSFZRPY1D8TX2HZ8OPEQEK3FAR6VHNNQZ", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "1.YF5472DNN4P173UZUKZUYZT9BH", "wrongAnswers": ["2.G4BJ7M900DLNC7VJ", "3.BF33GTASNXYLMLNLQJN25BRNCN184"], "questionOptions": ["1.YF5472DNN4P173UZUKZUYZT9BH", "2.G4BJ7M900DLNC7VJ", "3.BF33GTASNXYLMLNLQJN25BRNCN184"], "answerLink": "BCCGRB3U9S"}, {"questionId": 148, "questionText": "OS3F8Q1NVIIBMVO8MLZ85UDCLCLTEZB1BUI4HDQSQ9WMTNCAIJVA5CN4PG7LJPW90PWT0Y6WRS9YK2WWDJIUP", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "3.2VHSNNN4ZMD5WT1EMY8EJ0JTWOH1", "wrongAnswers": ["1.E3WD9ED2CZSF2ZMT8", "2.EHJGTQ7E0V0RCRXNFPVAWI0T50W"], "questionOptions": ["1.E3WD9ED2CZSF2ZMT8", "2.EHJGTQ7E0V0RCRXNFPVAWI0T50W", "3.2VHSNNN4ZMD5WT1EMY8EJ0JTWOH1"], "answerLink": "R5S83V7VRB"}, {"questionId": 149, "questionText": "JZ6MD4MJ63BAJ2MMLP9XOR1F16I4HR4SS97TDQWFJ8NVAK0G2NYQ3AY3D6UGXOCVCURPC9NMUD81ZIFIAXUJQG126TFMJJF9TP8EF6A9S9SXBSNO", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "3.DD8RTPRVOGR3TZDY68", "wrongAnswers": ["1.B7ON75AXCJ6SNYU4O", "2.SAI7BQ5YPOK884DSQCKABUQRF7NKWRI"], "questionOptions": ["1.B7ON75AXCJ6SNYU4O", "2.SAI7BQ5YPOK884DSQCKABUQRF7NKWRI", "3.DD8RTPRVOGR3TZDY68"], "answerLink": "4LN4EZCCI3"}, {"questionId": 150, "questionText": "SCKV7HE3ACBUW9547SLXLHMM1STBODOOXG9E6N47M13JTETCMT09GSTUE7FYNVVX7KK48VOQV217N5U71846QWGU62F13CG4QQ", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "2.ETAGNOKIYFBNQHZJS1", "wrongAnswers": ["1.PSU44RJ752AKR9Z56DDB", "3.63UOC29AH19IDZI5QUCPIRC"], "questionOptions": ["1.PSU44RJ752AKR9Z56DDB", "2.ETAGNOKIYFBNQHZJS1", "3.63UOC29AH19IDZI5QUCPIRC"], "answerLink": "B63VWXURZR"}, {"questionId": 151, "questionText": "96LD8VQTFT25CXS7PE8EXJ962QH64HJH2ODCHGIMLJQHPPCREBI6J1TE3Q5P41ZQ15PAGBZ3JUMZM5Q9VUR3MD3OUEOM5K4N63", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "1.K2TESDTF07L7EWT04XN06I", "wrongAnswers": ["2.WWMGSMGMSWY9PTZ9E7UEWVLX7CE", "3.7SRQ2LA66E3SZSGLWSYNGEIAFXVDJ"], "questionOptions": ["1.K2TESDTF07L7EWT04XN06I", "2.WWMGSMGMSWY9PTZ9E7UEWVLX7CE", "3.7SRQ2LA66E3SZSGLWSYNGEIAFXVDJ"], "answerLink": "QOVPMNSX2V"}, {"questionId": 152, "questionText": "080HN8CFTJ48QLZ9RRCYMC8BEM770B4ULLSE7RZGNKPIE2K5WUIPLLU3O9HKOPW17USDFXG444IV4MR1MR2EMDUGKWDO3BE4BBHQLIXNLFN23RP7C2WSW4W0L", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "1.08J41H2WLBGVM6F388CP", "wrongAnswers": ["2.DNVIQ5A6RBSD4KXDI55MH38", "3.RCONS4U358EFNGUY2P6Z9U9QYPGZK"], "questionOptions": ["1.08J41H2WLBGVM6F388CP", "2.DNVIQ5A6RBSD4KXDI55MH38", "3.RCONS4U358EFNGUY2P6Z9U9QYPGZK"], "answerLink": "6FWWXMDVX5"}, {"questionId": 153, "questionText": "K1A8BHFH8S8G4QPEZC51ANHGN5MMYF9XB5C4MBY8Y4F88A8F3B3YN3LZ508K24JWN2OOZDDV0GTOU8MVKQAZUO63DI6LG82DROT4JZD1S66SPT80", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "3.WDVYLM4Y76TO1DJI3P9FB23U16UW", "wrongAnswers": ["1.H18ICBVJFMOZTH8OBB9MNQ3W", "2.SUV7L60RWZP9D5G0PI3YJVNUIJDZO"], "questionOptions": ["1.H18ICBVJFMOZTH8OBB9MNQ3W", "2.SUV7L60RWZP9D5G0PI3YJVNUIJDZO", "3.WDVYLM4Y76TO1DJI3P9FB23U16UW"], "answerLink": "GRB0QNGHVX"}, {"questionId": 154, "questionText": "EEZVW6LEKUTMTMPSZAY5ASMXNGZ81EJWAZZ0H4CC8H02BHO9WOJKFIV6ER6OGWM0VRQ0U6P9899IYT", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "2.AW4XUQF29QWJ3D9XPY0SY4HY", "wrongAnswers": ["1.N6PJ1FK5ONJVVNCZKY1AB5EF", "3.DP424H1SSSI1MFQ82C4"], "questionOptions": ["1.N6PJ1FK5ONJVVNCZKY1AB5EF", "2.AW4XUQF29QWJ3D9XPY0SY4HY", "3.DP424H1SSSI1MFQ82C4"], "answerLink": "SUMVFJRXHR"}, {"questionId": 155, "questionText": "FL34C9D3KCD37WGOOSAE066FPZAFNJAVI9T4S2DE8V6PAAX88E3JL1MLOL2I088ZOQLNNE1A230KNCD8V9OIC7WRRE2JGZPKUBZNA468DX5WKD2JTRMMZZAGWPX38F", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "2.XVWD6HZI27JQX7NG90Y", "wrongAnswers": ["1.V1T0058007OB1QJCEZP7", "3.LT6Y0ZJ5T9BBACDIDDNRPQ2M8MA41"], "questionOptions": ["1.V1T0058007OB1QJCEZP7", "2.XVWD6HZI27JQX7NG90Y", "3.LT6Y0ZJ5T9BBACDIDDNRPQ2M8MA41"], "answerLink": "KQNBGJMYHC"}, {"questionId": 156, "questionText": "LWENPCJ4628W3S5I1GVXNRURLUOFQ0CY6JIEM7L6PM6NAM9A9BGXU5IE0GM7PRKMEH", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "2.AEBXJ73ENIBEKOK0RQ5SGSTN97Q100O", "wrongAnswers": ["1.QZEO63RZJEWLB0HCOO8E35", "3.RMDZT6ZOS8EOUTIDMV1DARK"], "questionOptions": ["1.QZEO63RZJEWLB0HCOO8E35", "2.AEBXJ73ENIBEKOK0RQ5SGSTN97Q100O", "3.RMDZT6ZOS8EOUTIDMV1DARK"], "answerLink": "C3J8QCDAP1"}, {"questionId": 157, "questionText": "PHZODYIHUQBJ0XL847H1O0MDTUZ2ICQUGGK3UNA0XWUD5GYEFKVWSY1TER4UM40ZACXKKCRN19KKO2C3A558B1NROEF1MUVNTHK7QFQVI", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "1.W68ESAQ523DLEXV2RFN", "wrongAnswers": ["2.XK9L5RA723VTJM5EVYADKSU2NW6PSC0", "3.CMVKA6ILNAYJPI6N6"], "questionOptions": ["1.W68ESAQ523DLEXV2RFN", "2.XK9L5RA723VTJM5EVYADKSU2NW6PSC0", "3.CMVKA6ILNAYJPI6N6"], "answerLink": "WOZLRA1F6F"}, {"questionId": 158, "questionText": "8QQYE8KLC24OZ5YEOTHW8S5TJTD575OY0FI29VABC47XO054PO92JBVSSYYJOPW4TTBBAOJ", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "3.C2XQ2NF3F1Y3GVCGZCAWG1LD", "wrongAnswers": ["1.FCNCQ47WLY2KJ9ZJ5BFZ696DZV9S", "2.S4082LR1J4RMM08X5UJPSMALTPBE36"], "questionOptions": ["1.FCNCQ47WLY2KJ9ZJ5BFZ696DZV9S", "2.S4082LR1J4RMM08X5UJPSMALTPBE36", "3.C2XQ2NF3F1Y3GVCGZCAWG1LD"], "answerLink": "1PQMMKHTGY"}, {"questionId": 159, "questionText": "GRKSVI1ODTFYTVUHV86IEOYRFZ4OOAIMLQI9RNY75X1D2NZ2DJRI7TNA07SJ79I9ZRJUYWA9HNMHS33", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "2.IFW69JV3B6O3O4DN278YU88V7S", "wrongAnswers": ["1.BDG3KMFPQU1M4VJCJ2XZ", "3.OTGOOS1GV479XUOZK7POJ"], "questionOptions": ["1.BDG3KMFPQU1M4VJCJ2XZ", "2.IFW69JV3B6O3O4DN278YU88V7S", "3.OTGOOS1GV479XUOZK7POJ"], "answerLink": "EDSEPFRAON"}, {"questionId": 160, "questionText": "MFZD5KF0ADDVHGVCS30330DGB41SAMZKMK7SWYQM0OZ1EHPK5AY1ZD7TTRQL5E4FQ8HV4PE38CG9GBGQZHHWCZS", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "3.FI1PCMZB317LZ0Y6CKE9M6OYXOSLPBD", "wrongAnswers": ["1.0O9MR8J30KI7RL9OLJ5KDYPIQF18", "2.NQX1RCSIZ1SATHE70"], "questionOptions": ["1.0O9MR8J30KI7RL9OLJ5KDYPIQF18", "2.NQX1RCSIZ1SATHE70", "3.FI1PCMZB317LZ0Y6CKE9M6OYXOSLPBD"], "answerLink": "3ETW84DTI9"}, {"questionId": 161, "questionText": "VVQ19TYK7J1NCQUJC8PGAE9RMRO93FAJGTO4L9BD82SYS576Y86A2C65S6EAC85GWSUBE5PC475ZFI7581C6D", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "1.SGP5VZR3FO36TGEBR", "wrongAnswers": ["2.TDUEGS6MJEF3OBQK71E0IQD", "3.P8HXDLC7NB5SYQBTC"], "questionOptions": ["1.SGP5VZR3FO36TGEBR", "2.TDUEGS6MJEF3OBQK71E0IQD", "3.P8HXDLC7NB5SYQBTC"], "answerLink": "2FTKFT4X2R"}, {"questionId": 162, "questionText": "V8496VCT267XFDMLJLKQIN7BUY198SPG0D0A9LZKN62P2KT3MCZJ45O8T7VG980886WXOO15ICPXCRWDR07QP1I", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "2.L6IK3DED3CZEWT9D1A7V0K70X1CG9", "wrongAnswers": ["1.QGSINT0A2Z78TSNR2BWTBL5H5", "3.HLU42GRGGA6CXWSS0QWG"], "questionOptions": ["1.QGSINT0A2Z78TSNR2BWTBL5H5", "2.L6IK3DED3CZEWT9D1A7V0K70X1CG9", "3.HLU42GRGGA6CXWSS0QWG"], "answerLink": "JPIGVLP8TD"}, {"questionId": 163, "questionText": "4I3QKORHH70I6R2GCR7860LSD4RKM1T3QWK76KM3TFD979H3UK0S07XVTKYDFMF4BW1EFL8DUU1OH9EMSXOQMU9RO36QYAH9Q72ZKTGG", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "1.B18G2HKCT9PBWD6TSADAMMZXP", "wrongAnswers": ["2.8LI6XBJR4VEJXGCK6CYL38", "3.27JBQ96AVED40MT51FSTCI"], "questionOptions": ["1.B18G2HKCT9PBWD6TSADAMMZXP", "2.8LI6XBJR4VEJXGCK6CYL38", "3.27JBQ96AVED40MT51FSTCI"], "answerLink": "8GJSGYB0Q7"}, {"questionId": 164, "questionText": "BVZ8836XZOGT5QUZJ4RJRSBRR22FANMKRRSVIWSLXREG3E9VKW8BGUCQ2PLO7JV3SI9JXQ1S48KGNOBG6GURQF6VMS5IPASAKLC97N8G7HA8N1TNBZP0UFM", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "2.EHIB4927KLFXLK2SINC7", "wrongAnswers": ["1.U13MAFL0NSBL9QHCIND", "3.KWBVS851Q8R81LJVP1P4RU2NG2"], "questionOptions": ["1.U13MAFL0NSBL9QHCIND", "2.EHIB4927KLFXLK2SINC7", "3.KWBVS851Q8R81LJVP1P4RU2NG2"], "answerLink": "4EBFEGCBFT"}, {"questionId": 165, "questionText": "HAKHX5TYN4SE6CNDP52TUP68LC1P0MB8WCYODQRXREV2TTS6IXTNPL995Z2G30HSQFPAHJL2DZ7LWJP9OQ15T0QQ22USLIDFW50R0GY9FETYZ9TSP", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "2.01PXYMR7AARFLYVVWRZAXJQ646PXFT8", "wrongAnswers": ["1.O8A49AXJHGUPGR6I", "3.65HQBU0G2K4LTF5EIB5H"], "questionOptions": ["1.O8A49AXJHGUPGR6I", "2.01PXYMR7AARFLYVVWRZAXJQ646PXFT8", "3.65HQBU0G2K4LTF5EIB5H"], "answerLink": "DH3TA8T6WZ"}, {"questionId": 166, "questionText": "KOLLGC5Z00FHCF0IRRNHWV0N6BZK8N0MC4G8DLL1DEKE1OJZRYC8LH4M1YTVE2JNC5U2OUOB28HI3W72QKDQJYZVDAX7YJS55CVM6C2K1ANQO40GPS", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "3.V1JF5LPDMLNEZ3WAGMDBA8H", "wrongAnswers": ["1.YFHOV0XI29DSI3Q1JJVDZHWYW7MA3O", "2.GG4O2LM7MRDQNTXENLV95ARW84GO2K"], "questionOptions": ["1.YFHOV0XI29DSI3Q1JJVDZHWYW7MA3O", "2.GG4O2LM7MRDQNTXENLV95ARW84GO2K", "3.V1JF5LPDMLNEZ3WAGMDBA8H"], "answerLink": "GRIJJEF0HO"}, {"questionId": 167, "questionText": "8U7EU46DMVQ8KD4NEJKWO82TBMCJCTYN7LPNLR9YYNFA849815YPBOZ239NZ3WQOICEMY7H8G4HDHCHEEZN0O9VU22EEP4G", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "3.HZCQK9P899BPX1LYRZZKPFL3", "wrongAnswers": ["1.G40W1SV2TM52CW1V7XCZOHJ9HX", "2.2REWFXIM7HPXJPF03QNJ00G"], "questionOptions": ["1.G40W1SV2TM52CW1V7XCZOHJ9HX", "2.2REWFXIM7HPXJPF03QNJ00G", "3.HZCQK9P899BPX1LYRZZKPFL3"], "answerLink": "HERUNMNA1Z"}, {"questionId": 168, "questionText": "SN1E1EULLUPH9TDSBAPS5L7QM2ZWIQWHR2Z8BP02Q7A5FZ6BJPTKC25CB82F9LVOU7LSEX59Y779J8", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "2.IV0W5A6OETCKA1V85O0XVT7JCP72J5WS", "wrongAnswers": ["1.7BKFDU64EKNUIPEWEHZ1", "3.637YBAV07YO57HFWBAE870K0BP9M6BT"], "questionOptions": ["1.7BKFDU64EKNUIPEWEHZ1", "2.IV0W5A6OETCKA1V85O0XVT7JCP72J5WS", "3.637YBAV07YO57HFWBAE870K0BP9M6BT"], "answerLink": "IXGBYDDWF0"}, {"questionId": 169, "questionText": "81LSFCOTOBN5V1BJAYP3JYGQVZNWGYO0LL7WRK2CTNMFKLL1112AQ1KS00R1FWQTD2YVWB2MFDS94LG8JVDVPQ9GMVBE", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "2.E0U5DFRYHJKMCKQU6E9I65QL841DKD6", "wrongAnswers": ["1.SBMDK3YCEXXR5QCATMH0JH4Z", "3.UJ1EJIH9PUK318LAM95ELFT1"], "questionOptions": ["1.SBMDK3YCEXXR5QCATMH0JH4Z", "2.E0U5DFRYHJKMCKQU6E9I65QL841DKD6", "3.UJ1EJIH9PUK318LAM95ELFT1"], "answerLink": "PJDQ9HTGBB"}, {"questionId": 170, "questionText": "IM01OWX0B3QZNCZGHOSGUS5CAWAUYW4JG719TR6B02M1NKMVOYWVKBQD0JP17Y4UN72X3ELTD", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "3.GMIYIMFLW7ZE25VBCCCAY0US1IIRCV8", "wrongAnswers": ["1.JDJKC6B6ZZLO183GFXCU73EWW6", "2.4MMDRK8VBOZ7K9A0Q6KW3L1A"], "questionOptions": ["1.JDJKC6B6ZZLO183GFXCU73EWW6", "2.4MMDRK8VBOZ7K9A0Q6KW3L1A", "3.GMIYIMFLW7ZE25VBCCCAY0US1IIRCV8"], "answerLink": "LUTRV7RNKS"}, {"questionId": 171, "questionText": "RSAHC47UQK1Z9QX6978BP6CV0Q3106B53AT3RP8K7HJEO7KE5VRYX13MZ6LEU030651W1SIKXEPV3X6S2WNRNFAYCPB79731O5HCZ94PSZBF8CGARJWFGD9", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "1.JQXHF6ES5V7S59F70OX0VRH", "wrongAnswers": ["2.PVJAN316VG90HUZMEVYXRR9", "3.4AIZJHLC6KKSH80GOHTDL2QTJ9I2"], "questionOptions": ["1.JQXHF6ES5V7S59F70OX0VRH", "2.PVJAN316VG90HUZMEVYXRR9", "3.4AIZJHLC6KKSH80GOHTDL2QTJ9I2"], "answerLink": "W7WS1WHAVR"}, {"questionId": 172, "questionText": "TB1NVPXDYQHXF64UYO9JDD0QPAQ3TFSQXN581USGO6F73HYBH8D153ZQUWNI0QKGXT", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "3.ZHNQRRCEPTMU9JKBYGR", "wrongAnswers": ["1.J0XPVHOUH6UTEJ0CPW3M4RM17WGM8X15", "2.95RLUSFZB8P9MR1FCZ"], "questionOptions": ["1.J0XPVHOUH6UTEJ0CPW3M4RM17WGM8X15", "2.95RLUSFZB8P9MR1FCZ", "3.ZHNQRRCEPTMU9JKBYGR"], "answerLink": "HQAO2PKDTU"}, {"questionId": 173, "questionText": "FABJVKIC6PO6YZ5IQQE1NS28A11YQA0WI8VBEG9H0AVC627RHJ94MJ5N0DQ6RVOORZYQGK31H1D8QT8WHKIFXXCH2L6TTT5QZXBG1I", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "1.IZO996VP9LESREADEFI6XO5P45HM4V", "wrongAnswers": ["2.T902TDIRMCA4E7ZJ5BLJ25RJQ3F64O7", "3.84R6Z46IRXJEY8O2C82NQRCGNM4"], "questionOptions": ["1.IZO996VP9LESREADEFI6XO5P45HM4V", "2.T902TDIRMCA4E7ZJ5BLJ25RJQ3F64O7", "3.84R6Z46IRXJEY8O2C82NQRCGNM4"], "answerLink": "74UXZA9KWI"}, {"questionId": 174, "questionText": "RK9O14QHGO1F0T5NM97R26PLS0F06Q4HMCO4Q2JJ3P2SD1QHHAA70OUYABQAR6UL9XB4O96L4PB2HOWR28H2IDPCEQD0P0X9PA0U963HUH389D24", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "1.17SM2SY9V42OGUNZ6Y09NCK2YM8F", "wrongAnswers": ["2.RRN2NI51HW6KP8R5RUEMFK7S", "3.S4YSC6AJP7UZEJ6TA55XVWRC6"], "questionOptions": ["1.17SM2SY9V42OGUNZ6Y09NCK2YM8F", "2.RRN2NI51HW6KP8R5RUEMFK7S", "3.S4YSC6AJP7UZEJ6TA55XVWRC6"], "answerLink": "ILOLD02D3S"}, {"questionId": 175, "questionText": "GTMS9FPLUMX8H8AKSOSFMV2VMLQRXEMGDB5DQJC5BOGS40C06OLIGOVXLGNYHCNJCSC0LQPEGZ3CJM150JID", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "3.6HW302XHSNWGI8IKV3LC6BTNJ3", "wrongAnswers": ["1.YJ8823G1TC0E4PXVDK0GRQU0BI3", "2.33KX632SXGC8CHGPR0OM18BEVN32BBCF"], "questionOptions": ["1.YJ8823G1TC0E4PXVDK0GRQU0BI3", "2.33KX632SXGC8CHGPR0OM18BEVN32BBCF", "3.6HW302XHSNWGI8IKV3LC6BTNJ3"], "answerLink": "7NI7V3GP2L"}, {"questionId": 176, "questionText": "GX3C4MFQCN9NSUV1Y22KHWM95226Q5L8SBSFNQGA80NJ232WOIMDEW2IRPNMBC4CFK1RXFVD2IFD1Z21LSSJJEF", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "1.C1JQPQK768GWBEJ2Q", "wrongAnswers": ["2.L7LDU9CFRMJTGIJFUF9F9A832", "3.I5EFK8OZ1B4PG92LLQSBDUBVLI5"], "questionOptions": ["1.C1JQPQK768GWBEJ2Q", "2.L7LDU9CFRMJTGIJFUF9F9A832", "3.I5EFK8OZ1B4PG92LLQSBDUBVLI5"], "answerLink": "BIH41HYE24"}, {"questionId": 177, "questionText": "3RNWJZVJS0FAI3DXN47RHTDRZ9VKRABPW5BLH86HJ2F9WWM4YSSI60HL1ROKBE8M3HK94KO5I61Z96Q3QZV6085NVKN", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "2.WRT3RECQTWS5U9HQTZJ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.RIWQHT3U4PVB0B93D5G2V9XM2H7UEDA", "3.HR5WABMHRUMNJ1ARZM7BFDQWVG6SA"], "questionOptions": ["1.RIWQHT3U4PVB0B93D5G2V9XM2H7UEDA", "2.WRT3RECQTWS5U9HQTZJ", "3.HR5WABMHRUMNJ1ARZM7BFDQWVG6SA"], "answerLink": "2P8MY48PUY"}, {"questionId": 178, "questionText": "EXUIW4SDXCTVTNSBSCQXN5W0DXAWZBMLKEYIH2VH6YWQ6Z2ZDZ9GHTP6K7VMXQZM8VNACMXPPF03GOJQEDFL7B64SLXDCVIUURQGJR07TQY51T45WYWO", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "3.JG3E99PJ1IV1V0SWBFIDH7WSQXM", "wrongAnswers": ["1.JMIO6EZ23O96JJ2V7MEULYM9UV", "2.CPNB0H1HQNKJDBX3EDSL1"], "questionOptions": ["1.JMIO6EZ23O96JJ2V7MEULYM9UV", "2.CPNB0H1HQNKJDBX3EDSL1", "3.JG3E99PJ1IV1V0SWBFIDH7WSQXM"], "answerLink": "IT95PMXUUI"}, {"questionId": 179, "questionText": "V5B3TBAO9IA353XESUPIPUV5V6V2I4QMZD2L1YJE3M3OD8SNEXVRE3FCFAQ5WW8OKEUE3FIOKIFGLHG", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "1.XR7IL8V0O5KDG7AJNXXPYCUZ81MB5UYA", "wrongAnswers": ["2.C5JSVQ5YVTFPH9GKJYMWZ2QD8THCN", "3.MSNFDUWCLB9NQUA3G"], "questionOptions": ["1.XR7IL8V0O5KDG7AJNXXPYCUZ81MB5UYA", "2.C5JSVQ5YVTFPH9GKJYMWZ2QD8THCN", "3.MSNFDUWCLB9NQUA3G"], "answerLink": "3YH5JLCSNL"}, {"questionId": 180, "questionText": "SNOAJX9ZTTCZLCCA98J6XKZZSRLRXHL5B0ZS06AMO6NRWTBO7GKD30KA7911IVVSP5C3YPC93TW29TWVRHF0GO0JD33", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "3.ASKU3KVWXQE59A5XROJI304", "wrongAnswers": ["1.TTT0S4ESG61IQRK971Q2R4", "2.9DWYPRMZ27X6CU3DUJ"], "questionOptions": ["1.TTT0S4ESG61IQRK971Q2R4", "2.9DWYPRMZ27X6CU3DUJ", "3.ASKU3KVWXQE59A5XROJI304"], "answerLink": "JA4A7TE6EH"}, {"questionId": 181, "questionText": "SI1B6SQ1I2OIPIQUB277CSHFCIXGUQBLAZNEHNRIA2NBG8UCE04T38YRXGYEEYAEXN1FZ3YTV6QPL9F1QNAMMG5O454D2L3LOHWWNSZ5FSGWPAR7NRKCWF", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "3.BMI5IH1CY51S8MHMXJ4DZ0F", "wrongAnswers": ["1.EP2BFNAEPSJ9VNBYE72VQNQ404U8", "2.8YS8SYNM2YXJQMSYNKKSIDH2N47QDOB"], "questionOptions": ["1.EP2BFNAEPSJ9VNBYE72VQNQ404U8", "2.8YS8SYNM2YXJQMSYNKKSIDH2N47QDOB", "3.BMI5IH1CY51S8MHMXJ4DZ0F"], "answerLink": "DWHGPR0NPU"}, {"questionId": 182, "questionText": "KOMG7AFJCKFQQY20V0J4P1LPILZ86529VG1W5OZHQ2OS6P4DEAFIK40GYULLJUF4MTOY7Z0YILCCU065FTR45EM", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "3.VEGW8097BARKSNHRFN62QF1NB1ZV8X", "wrongAnswers": ["1.9NMR8R17QS0T5Y5M9W6OE5NXPL", "2.SW0BN7YPAHGPG4O83Z94FWCW"], "questionOptions": ["1.9NMR8R17QS0T5Y5M9W6OE5NXPL", "2.SW0BN7YPAHGPG4O83Z94FWCW", "3.VEGW8097BARKSNHRFN62QF1NB1ZV8X"], "answerLink": "4F1NA69SZZ"}, {"questionId": 183, "questionText": "UWJLGW43DF4KIYKFXCA0BCWYK28ESOOXCU4MMMC9K2JLREO34V1Y9SL6EXRE6ESIMO1VQUBSF1SO2WH2PTY62I39Y5ZEFZ", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "1.7K6YURSXBHKNJ6EXIVYPXUNGWOW1MP", "wrongAnswers": ["2.7PKPUY7QSGCQHSJ3AOWR4QQ4DVL", "3.BWVLZX08YU86R3TZES2JHD9DOHM8IL9"], "questionOptions": ["1.7K6YURSXBHKNJ6EXIVYPXUNGWOW1MP", "2.7PKPUY7QSGCQHSJ3AOWR4QQ4DVL", "3.BWVLZX08YU86R3TZES2JHD9DOHM8IL9"], "answerLink": "B568UA0XHX"}, {"questionId": 184, "questionText": "74KFIB55UN4YVBLL14R3ZCOETWT2A9F2ED1SO4MC6U5970EYLR7W88R24DCDV63NPJQOTWLIQFEWLSIJNKFBUYOYPXAR52S80TLVKM6C4", "questionCategory": "Regola 5", "correctAnswers": "2.2VK0UDCIH23FFBRS", "wrongAnswers": ["1.9K1DQZRZS5RF60YITPKLIJ1QK6SA3IE", "3.0XAAW1LRYCAEU6D3XM4JK3MMM62"], "questionOptions": ["1.9K1DQZRZS5RF60YITPKLIJ1QK6SA3IE", "2.2VK0UDCIH23FFBRS", "3.0XAAW1LRYCAEU6D3XM4JK3MMM62"], "answerLink": "OCSWRUFB4Y"}, {"questionId": 185, "questionText": "20BXN50NSJ76099J687VQVCQ5AHHCWBIBM65D5SWM3ZNIYQ9XX88HZ9X4AD0RQGXJVX7JU9TBZYTKJN1VXQFR43C3CNCQ33KNZM1XRSU3Z0PEIKQJXRS4URL", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.QSF5113FGTDI1YRRAKBLIA355MNI0W9", "wrongAnswers": ["1.3CW9I7LIQA8OZTJTOPBWFPYYLUNS", "3.87GCPO0P31SV98CHP1SD0OU"], "questionOptions": ["1.3CW9I7LIQA8OZTJTOPBWFPYYLUNS", "2.QSF5113FGTDI1YRRAKBLIA355MNI0W9", "3.87GCPO0P31SV98CHP1SD0OU"], "answerLink": "8WBB1BGHRH"}, {"questionId": 186, "questionText": "HN1F42TT8E4PIJNCW41ZNCTCYTKXZ3O43MDUVQLOISMHIOG058Q6NDEINK6P7BQCGKW98Y9KJYN2ELHQ3EI2P5TA1GI2T13MWH7BI51I9", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.7QRQWGO8ESXTLSO6CIHOTYIQWI3CAJA", "wrongAnswers": ["1.DU4SO5X8W7BADRXVYV75BYY5H", "3.KYHOI0DP0X6MG6UWSYMZ15"], "questionOptions": ["1.DU4SO5X8W7BADRXVYV75BYY5H", "2.7QRQWGO8ESXTLSO6CIHOTYIQWI3CAJA", "3.KYHOI0DP0X6MG6UWSYMZ15"], "answerLink": "KU8RCGNW5D"}, {"questionId": 187, "questionText": "2UOOR88EGZPZYO69EKPRS81JSHRF2J3P1THOGPN7XV6XUF55YR0Y2MK39D71BSOI7VIANG3O7BYSYH4JX3U4MPJUCUR8GP5VJOIW54CE5QBUOEEJTS0OUPW4B7T14", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.QYVM91K8FBIOQWR7D2U4C2GHOTU", "wrongAnswers": ["1.OFY7XLPX5GYLE59GGMKLR2UFG", "2.6B0BDECCFMPAY8YFG"], "questionOptions": ["1.OFY7XLPX5GYLE59GGMKLR2UFG", "2.6B0BDECCFMPAY8YFG", "3.QYVM91K8FBIOQWR7D2U4C2GHOTU"], "answerLink": "6QQUCZNXBL"}, {"questionId": 188, "questionText": "TQCE0USXGXURLCFXRSRNPR2TKNMI5ELV3CTXOKRZFD6PFI5VVA8D0DMA0X03O36MSU86F01A1EASXFCCY2HCS2DME6IDG18CH1QLJXYJM2QHHKS7O", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.NJ368K63ITPV7IXU40SWN8IJQXLPJ24C", "wrongAnswers": ["1.W38JNDTHT7T3UXGIXQE4U6", "2.SJG1LE26VJBYG9MH9BA"], "questionOptions": ["1.W38JNDTHT7T3UXGIXQE4U6", "2.SJG1LE26VJBYG9MH9BA", "3.NJ368K63ITPV7IXU40SWN8IJQXLPJ24C"], "answerLink": "KN069QXFCG"}, {"questionId": 189, "questionText": "1YRN2Z5KO4X68ZGZZCY6486RN7JXWG1J1Z3OU3CYF68B3J98G1K1JC8KRLYW3LVBUD96Z8FVP", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "1.2907T3BYTVVS7E6D8", "wrongAnswers": ["2.EOBF8UTKEGE30ZHIDV1KV8F", "3.KDYBAR49KWE9HV1RQH06HJ613XQ0"], "questionOptions": ["1.2907T3BYTVVS7E6D8", "2.EOBF8UTKEGE30ZHIDV1KV8F", "3.KDYBAR49KWE9HV1RQH06HJ613XQ0"], "answerLink": "JQXNQCLIWC"}, {"questionId": 190, "questionText": "NNG1DOB59WJR2EWG88I5GXYJT9WDIR9V0X3JQ6X8AYDTDNYG78LCQA48DCTBJ6PIG88UX19F3UD4U6UTSL7417ZA5HHJ9AVXQ5DYULH6T3703TZW7W0SBQMXEL", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "1.BRPZMAXJUBPOJK8VDZ3LMCR0G7B", "wrongAnswers": ["2.FADZZUS1YW5HPVJV5ZCELL", "3.SKTH84Q53JJXG9NT7AU7ZE092VIQO7O"], "questionOptions": ["1.BRPZMAXJUBPOJK8VDZ3LMCR0G7B", "2.FADZZUS1YW5HPVJV5ZCELL", "3.SKTH84Q53JJXG9NT7AU7ZE092VIQO7O"], "answerLink": "VQRN75GYLB"}, {"questionId": 191, "questionText": "J5T7CDDELY4WTBWWJL26E8WM1WH38NIJLLRONUAQX0WBIPOARYIDHVYLQE6UBE3BGQIVNP7AIAAGQW4EW3TI4RW3JJNGC2", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "1.WMNL9Q1P053KZWSX3ZIART14Q0", "wrongAnswers": ["2.TBFV39XBVSE33C3X6", "3.YIUVQ618JT1WM7ZXRY"], "questionOptions": ["1.WMNL9Q1P053KZWSX3ZIART14Q0", "2.TBFV39XBVSE33C3X6", "3.YIUVQ618JT1WM7ZXRY"], "answerLink": "WD9DLZW3YF"}, {"questionId": 192, "questionText": "LR06R2GU8O9SZK7JK628AUBW514GSL0DKI5ZBSU37JJ8AEPVVVR09L18CMFFM5HPP359DXKKCWJEZUE5G", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.R64VYFI01FOB357FS0V9", "wrongAnswers": ["1.RTC882CM0GIZWYT8LL6MKP22", "2.ERMQBUDDNSADM63YTQ4"], "questionOptions": ["1.RTC882CM0GIZWYT8LL6MKP22", "2.ERMQBUDDNSADM63YTQ4", "3.R64VYFI01FOB357FS0V9"], "answerLink": "UDM7O0LTS1"}, {"questionId": 193, "questionText": "U777K58YQL4E1K09IVSUNC9877Z0BRN5CR49PO8P869ZM8OEFGESL2S22IE88APQTAXOTD9F", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.LKRN1ANFW2WENUYINQ0WS886QMC6DD7K", "wrongAnswers": ["1.O6XORFIO6BSL3AAL8YP99TQ6", "2.UOFY5Y3PN5W3RY1EOCI2XBX"], "questionOptions": ["1.O6XORFIO6BSL3AAL8YP99TQ6", "2.UOFY5Y3PN5W3RY1EOCI2XBX", "3.LKRN1ANFW2WENUYINQ0WS886QMC6DD7K"], "answerLink": "F0PI0271GG"}, {"questionId": 194, "questionText": "7JK0Z924IA6H677PWJKNFMM547ACGRN1HGMMQL7BAFD5E1A2HXXR34L32PV1AU2R4F5AH6EC9BJNX0ZKD1OVRY26D", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.2XRTH78EALO203ND3", "wrongAnswers": ["1.TGYYCDXK8OOIG66IY5IETGGYTYLQA", "2.XM975WZV3D6RUH3J"], "questionOptions": ["1.TGYYCDXK8OOIG66IY5IETGGYTYLQA", "2.XM975WZV3D6RUH3J", "3.2XRTH78EALO203ND3"], "answerLink": "FP5TXSNX0B"}, {"questionId": 195, "questionText": "47BE9U2UFKMGUG50GO018TG1191RIKZP1M9E87UAVUKCDQLCDO7DWW76EPPJJWBY3OFRGH3IYHGOAZVA2SKCQGM33V", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "1.TQ6LE03PN0SYJ7K73U7EZI9YQS6LBCLY", "wrongAnswers": ["2.UURRAKUP3UM0BISB3", "3.J3JLSYLRNXWPJQX2S7EXTVV"], "questionOptions": ["1.TQ6LE03PN0SYJ7K73U7EZI9YQS6LBCLY", "2.UURRAKUP3UM0BISB3", "3.J3JLSYLRNXWPJQX2S7EXTVV"], "answerLink": "4VXTCUB2TY"}, {"questionId": 196, "questionText": "Z1Y5BYEDECYXCYBI9J802YHPYUZ1QOLLK8Q8UIV6HRZDOCYBU5J9RDKB2898OL89AY2EKJLDEFJERXPMPKGJYRTO3ZOQ6EJVYHXGI6D5SUNEZ2RBGAV511MIDBS5T0P", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "1.ZSTADUTW8JKMOU7H8K", "wrongAnswers": ["2.VNLVSB99M2A5R6XF9ZYP7", "3.CV6OAYR8PHLW8ADD"], "questionOptions": ["1.ZSTADUTW8JKMOU7H8K", "2.VNLVSB99M2A5R6XF9ZYP7", "3.CV6OAYR8PHLW8ADD"], "answerLink": "T1WIKKR19K"}, {"questionId": 197, "questionText": "0RIA12G43CO414P0EOAUMAENTMMJRLSKZTDLD36XC9FWOYPUN4HS5Z28TMBSGI0Q5ZQY0A6VUW92TGL4LELFKMEF0R7UIJP79X2PCGQOII1SOXP3E730BYT75G4", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.LWRSU0932TDZOUP9ZFG", "wrongAnswers": ["1.YDP1W71TJEITDQANDN50VO08", "3.WGQIY6T930D5QXNR984FRADJP"], "questionOptions": ["1.YDP1W71TJEITDQANDN50VO08", "2.LWRSU0932TDZOUP9ZFG", "3.WGQIY6T930D5QXNR984FRADJP"], "answerLink": "RO0I1VX4VZ"}, {"questionId": 198, "questionText": "RBLUCU0LAX1ZE3RI6HP360ZJ70UCZMA7LV20Q39CAKNB10FG3IE74EU8R01JFNUU9PGS5IL", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.9SGDJ0YXDBZ284YY55JU4JZY4", "wrongAnswers": ["1.40ND2L6PZZ5SML7MR1", "2.SKCKGCSNU81WQE5EO"], "questionOptions": ["1.40ND2L6PZZ5SML7MR1", "2.SKCKGCSNU81WQE5EO", "3.9SGDJ0YXDBZ284YY55JU4JZY4"], "answerLink": "GTSMK91YWH"}, {"questionId": 199, "questionText": "8J0GUA705BQXHSHD42FP9Y1BB4AMKONF94A1K6WION0WM3O5YJM7JBOWND5VUO1HHFAM0WMGC1TUFH9DP9SC37TPSRDXTGXPCID4NB19AS5WROY8VTJZK3X25HVH", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.HKX3LH3B39XISBCZ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.I2X591Y1R2DAJDSU1AVXM", "3.1ZNAUCWDOA0J0S5DG8IQBJN"], "questionOptions": ["1.I2X591Y1R2DAJDSU1AVXM", "2.HKX3LH3B39XISBCZ", "3.1ZNAUCWDOA0J0S5DG8IQBJN"], "answerLink": "BZPRDO55Q6"}, {"questionId": 200, "questionText": "YRA6IFJ328S6GAP39PUGSRNFHFUL40WLL3KVGEFOZOMPAD7348HAL4A6WVCPFX2YBA3RNTQITSH1GGLF51MDC1UWKASIQXYC10VU2Y", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.NO0IHHXRHNN2LJJ8N", "wrongAnswers": ["1.9O4WY9F609PVOVU8FJ4KKY1", "2.WFCIP39BSSSA7S6W329XJBV"], "questionOptions": ["1.9O4WY9F609PVOVU8FJ4KKY1", "2.WFCIP39BSSSA7S6W329XJBV", "3.NO0IHHXRHNN2LJJ8N"], "answerLink": "MD6VQVETJY"}, {"questionId": 201, "questionText": "D8PQOB9HL0C4WJ3V6IJ2YIPXAOC1L5X1DX1MOIPASPJIMRRUXY7BWJ75NPF0YHP2W1RHJYM0OQ7YZDK0JU3WLITMNM7YKDH7ILQZ6XWSN5ELP5R", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.OLN70TJ5PJ1Q8C3DTPH4BKTQ78", "wrongAnswers": ["1.ZQLE42QWTRJRHL89PVPKTYUTCU2", "2.XT8G17NEVF0VYGKKOA67E5MHWRFI"], "questionOptions": ["1.ZQLE42QWTRJRHL89PVPKTYUTCU2", "2.XT8G17NEVF0VYGKKOA67E5MHWRFI", "3.OLN70TJ5PJ1Q8C3DTPH4BKTQ78"], "answerLink": "52VRBE8LKK"}, {"questionId": 202, "questionText": "Y4088ESZ27QI7X7IMIU69AYMJS0D5NSB7EF8Y4YJ8VHESDHSMDOP5XPS4XCBDK69VH43SMGHFCQOZOXBAMKV21Q27VVY6JQKL9QPPYAST9ZN9", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.X7RE5MT3GKGGT1LWAV", "wrongAnswers": ["1.S9DRMIVDC4179QSCKBTBBP6", "3.A8SREODRQFWQ3XVP346L6U0XQ"], "questionOptions": ["1.S9DRMIVDC4179QSCKBTBBP6", "2.X7RE5MT3GKGGT1LWAV", "3.A8SREODRQFWQ3XVP346L6U0XQ"], "answerLink": "IKTCR2ALFJ"}, {"questionId": 203, "questionText": "D9X82JVR1WSUKQBTRQWBN1WV46WN4V2UAO69YTW11LQ4RHJEMGEDZ0NR7TII4YBU6CSIEP5WDXFYWT6U7NVX5XDLJY4CSMUPWGHV9", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.65491XQ44NG58T4DTZKP1O7UK", "wrongAnswers": ["1.AKSR8YQCTUBQT0E5TH075", "3.BN1JSV0965IHC5Q94B9KOSM"], "questionOptions": ["1.AKSR8YQCTUBQT0E5TH075", "2.65491XQ44NG58T4DTZKP1O7UK", "3.BN1JSV0965IHC5Q94B9KOSM"], "answerLink": "YK3K5TJD3D"}, {"questionId": 204, "questionText": "09VQ133VB9USLCEPQ8QMUFR2U3XEWG8KW681G80DXUMLRQFPD094HOPSHUF2J6PUZ37K2EX7L289AAZARKTCWE9VMFNABMS9SU4PCP2803WUW1IINF", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "1.TH8AZMIHKE6RDZHRGT4", "wrongAnswers": ["2.S64GV54LJNS3F0ZNMGJ6MO6NGPW22G", "3.XYPAENG4CK4EE6VT73ARX298UUE"], "questionOptions": ["1.TH8AZMIHKE6RDZHRGT4", "2.S64GV54LJNS3F0ZNMGJ6MO6NGPW22G", "3.XYPAENG4CK4EE6VT73ARX298UUE"], "answerLink": "RA8WBSZAF1"}, {"questionId": 205, "questionText": "363TAL39LZT2I2IEGVBQGOGRQ02S573HI6H0VXM5KYOSEJ3SBEHC69OSK9Y6OET97MTZWZ7WR1VZ7PF07LBSJ4", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.SMYX1U4C7VNDPIZ82XQYIGPNE8UPH", "wrongAnswers": ["1.3Y2KYKWG5BHMGZM3LTSPRQJ049", "3.N7HQMAFYL3ROS5KZFMNRO8TK36"], "questionOptions": ["1.3Y2KYKWG5BHMGZM3LTSPRQJ049", "2.SMYX1U4C7VNDPIZ82XQYIGPNE8UPH", "3.N7HQMAFYL3ROS5KZFMNRO8TK36"], "answerLink": "4W6M9LALTK"}, {"questionId": 206, "questionText": "8ZP1NH8JBIDY8TV6PQO3N3HRW3HGZTK7SIMZK80MWY0SN8B0L5DKODMD1LNEYMWOZRZK9AGRA9FJUWP49MXXNTODCET0Z4LBP4Z8P2VQJBWK1ODZ11D98YC5QSGTB6", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.BECDKJBMUD04OJM1XLVMPNCPWWW", "wrongAnswers": ["1.UQ3YZELZYR6O9Y53XLL7279ED", "3.RDM1DI5I2RP0LXHVP0VSIKDSYTI0"], "questionOptions": ["1.UQ3YZELZYR6O9Y53XLL7279ED", "2.BECDKJBMUD04OJM1XLVMPNCPWWW", "3.RDM1DI5I2RP0LXHVP0VSIKDSYTI0"], "answerLink": "QY85WGDLY4"}, {"questionId": 207, "questionText": "ESOS4ZTOCEHIFFOO8QUZR8BWR2NF9G1DSS23TMTQ0FEHT207RSMLUH335AU7U8PXJ6ZWVWKO5UTJW5C3AJW8URD1RY5IE", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.3FMRLZZPN6VNF0J9WJDYYSP", "wrongAnswers": ["1.OQY0NFCXEZ49LYR4RL37DIB", "3.R86TGXFTOXZ80JRMF5LVMA28ZP8UI620"], "questionOptions": ["1.OQY0NFCXEZ49LYR4RL37DIB", "2.3FMRLZZPN6VNF0J9WJDYYSP", "3.R86TGXFTOXZ80JRMF5LVMA28ZP8UI620"], "answerLink": "DLTI9DYIWU"}, {"questionId": 208, "questionText": "DMPGRG0C7F2A99DI7EYH8UE61HHXCIS05TTD1UG6U9NPWLKN0SHALLO433HXGNTJOTSFP1D7UDJDZQ2VB43Q41NQ8ZKN2R86NXEYO6Q8OL3H6Y7XR0QTQLQG5", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "1.CMYT1LAC7EPNM55N8JL3OX6BZDMZBIY", "wrongAnswers": ["2.5D4FM90PF2MTP5UJEZ0QC3YX4E", "3.VVSNHYTS773XXGTC204A2FIRXE4IM"], "questionOptions": ["1.CMYT1LAC7EPNM55N8JL3OX6BZDMZBIY", "2.5D4FM90PF2MTP5UJEZ0QC3YX4E", "3.VVSNHYTS773XXGTC204A2FIRXE4IM"], "answerLink": "IE2ZYQ6PFN"}, {"questionId": 209, "questionText": "X3YRY6O1OHULAVZUHBD1AJJDCJDYVITMAM6K28EE4B1ZG8D4XJ6MRF36F9FPBBM9PNNAXVL7ZRJJ8RY4XN7VBAY", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.JH7NZTPU2FH4MF6LTF", "wrongAnswers": ["1.9EEWPIBFRZCOY9DTLBAFG", "2.YNNL47NN3E8NW2BP62HBFIUZ1"], "questionOptions": ["1.9EEWPIBFRZCOY9DTLBAFG", "2.YNNL47NN3E8NW2BP62HBFIUZ1", "3.JH7NZTPU2FH4MF6LTF"], "answerLink": "JYWHXIY7KP"}, {"questionId": 210, "questionText": "KABVZJ034Q05ZQ14S2KMD3P8D6LQH73JLKE1LD9JGAUMZ3ROX08MQ08S9JSI6UI4", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "1.DIH17Z1K6LP77EIPD8I1CK8WSKJ", "wrongAnswers": ["2.C56FMD234S7K52CZ8ZJYJIJRP", "3.M1FC7ZG4UROOW19WZ5ZFQOFDDMKBP5"], "questionOptions": ["1.DIH17Z1K6LP77EIPD8I1CK8WSKJ", "2.C56FMD234S7K52CZ8ZJYJIJRP", "3.M1FC7ZG4UROOW19WZ5ZFQOFDDMKBP5"], "answerLink": "3U24NCNPVE"}, {"questionId": 211, "questionText": "IU1Q3TGNJAD7K15P7179OM955X4DZ7YY376BSOCITRH50PPA91FR9QXLUJZD1B9RUKHAJFAX4CUL870JJ1HCRKPG1CV0EQ9C", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.YP3GHT3CTAXXC5A00PE", "wrongAnswers": ["1.SMLK1UXNKB2CCSU2KK", "3.ECLJDJY9C9YLALBY4LRC1Z"], "questionOptions": ["1.SMLK1UXNKB2CCSU2KK", "2.YP3GHT3CTAXXC5A00PE", "3.ECLJDJY9C9YLALBY4LRC1Z"], "answerLink": "XYWZ9GTIN7"}, {"questionId": 212, "questionText": "3CGXC1S42SIPDSAVVED812PUI6A4ESZLL4M2B1KH16R9PY396BZWMSBQUH4DVI8CK97KO8BLONQW6LWX3VOG", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.1XRIAMNRTNWVJXH8C6V2", "wrongAnswers": ["1.I97YCX9LQYJKR1320WVB3Q0S8O2FD", "3.ZEVIFB9OMURY4T0EIZ2ERNZ"], "questionOptions": ["1.I97YCX9LQYJKR1320WVB3Q0S8O2FD", "2.1XRIAMNRTNWVJXH8C6V2", "3.ZEVIFB9OMURY4T0EIZ2ERNZ"], "answerLink": "2XODEQYYEP"}, {"questionId": 213, "questionText": "LTW4ET0XLIPO0JVL5VJP2MUM2NQFN4LPIO847BY6XYLJ2LVZ17844R2VMLHE9181A8UQGR9DF1NV4T", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.CGPPBX1DXIPVCBGEM11RBWB1Y3", "wrongAnswers": ["1.19M9WU6RCR9A1GA9LH5Z5H0FHFUG3RF", "3.A53ACUUT5V01A2QG4AJDC7"], "questionOptions": ["1.19M9WU6RCR9A1GA9LH5Z5H0FHFUG3RF", "2.CGPPBX1DXIPVCBGEM11RBWB1Y3", "3.A53ACUUT5V01A2QG4AJDC7"], "answerLink": "Y6D7W36OFO"}, {"questionId": 214, "questionText": "IF4P06DITYN0RC826UN1KK0QHXLBC39EK7KI7IEUWB6KA8C290BLWQYML64J6LSJG7DLOF4JXVFXO16KN41MHWGWN680HYBVMF1CH6GEZCWF5TA7RSDRF", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "1.4GSLABLC5VEBH2O0B4NXXOK0", "wrongAnswers": ["2.SORSYUJ815HLS60P1I60", "3.ZYZ4OFB0IQ8UVZDR70"], "questionOptions": ["1.4GSLABLC5VEBH2O0B4NXXOK0", "2.SORSYUJ815HLS60P1I60", "3.ZYZ4OFB0IQ8UVZDR70"], "answerLink": "I65UOCXJD6"}, {"questionId": 215, "questionText": "YYSMFO8DRI4YA9BXE5AVK0D1S38IJ0B1GHD4559RGDPBFAZ3QHFV7S4JMMJCN84DPH2XUT9GDMEKGC7EB42YLXBUDGX9MG7", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.PAT85EYWDQ51DR0QA7HBT4", "wrongAnswers": ["1.L544DUMCLDGAV6O1TOSUAS3VZO", "2.K6GG46Y0DDQQLV2LRBF3CTUPSL"], "questionOptions": ["1.L544DUMCLDGAV6O1TOSUAS3VZO", "2.K6GG46Y0DDQQLV2LRBF3CTUPSL", "3.PAT85EYWDQ51DR0QA7HBT4"], "answerLink": "LJLEBUTJN7"}, {"questionId": 216, "questionText": "DM5NM25SLEKHQA0IU8X3EDTB6P4OS1782TNRZYJ4XB91XU3JRQ2YU7ODMSR0MXRMY6SQAICLHJE59JDH2GH1DA2XZBYPRQ", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.YWOKPMGMAH269RQ3H", "wrongAnswers": ["1.O90W5YNQQNADKJHSS6M7", "3.T8GYAE51M48YFL6PEJJ8BYPOZFU4"], "questionOptions": ["1.O90W5YNQQNADKJHSS6M7", "2.YWOKPMGMAH269RQ3H", "3.T8GYAE51M48YFL6PEJJ8BYPOZFU4"], "answerLink": "6NX7HW43SN"}, {"questionId": 217, "questionText": "YNG600FA3BD2V694UYKS6321LC52GPVHRXA7NHA8IIDUZ1LC5C5V4NYGKGKWLJH40X147GQ6NCTN0VRK083K2FWPDW013D", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.EPALAMZDKEDECPPY8U", "wrongAnswers": ["1.GVFLG1G0LQMMBN3JGW", "2.5C76COVYX7VQJ27Z4Y66IFQ4Z"], "questionOptions": ["1.GVFLG1G0LQMMBN3JGW", "2.5C76COVYX7VQJ27Z4Y66IFQ4Z", "3.EPALAMZDKEDECPPY8U"], "answerLink": "THN1ILV6W1"}, {"questionId": 218, "questionText": "RFNGCTZQ4O88SVNG8709LKAW1248ICKOXN6LQQ8UU1CUMU4JKL4N41ICXYPS17L1AV", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.QZFV2WLCVJDBTVX6UH", "wrongAnswers": ["1.FVLQJWZBERKCD0I8WRUH1JYHMG6", "3.T33DZEBN89CIFGQNTV"], "questionOptions": ["1.FVLQJWZBERKCD0I8WRUH1JYHMG6", "2.QZFV2WLCVJDBTVX6UH", "3.T33DZEBN89CIFGQNTV"], "answerLink": "NB2MN5LSI7"}, {"questionId": 219, "questionText": "B8NQFNBRP8VVJNTZAFTL81J5A9KM2DPMEIL6LUJQJ6TB5T2RISCQIMVWHCIYB2M4P8UD6Y661DIVWYG4O6R0M946Q6", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "1.37VAXCI54Z2J5HABOP2P3OICB5XTIBM", "wrongAnswers": ["2.2LRA32MHSE40B8DZX24", "3.H397N36DLPT7YIXBP50D4"], "questionOptions": ["1.37VAXCI54Z2J5HABOP2P3OICB5XTIBM", "2.2LRA32MHSE40B8DZX24", "3.H397N36DLPT7YIXBP50D4"], "answerLink": "12TD48ALFU"}, {"questionId": 220, "questionText": "1M7799GKN9Q5W7PA1ZI093H6ACU0XTDAYM83PNU4ZF30XKWHKCLALHF5EALH1WC5KM8O5DIEAM2N7KNLZB84BLW1EP4E90M", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.8QZ5BLZK23PA83VI7L4S0K8OE5", "wrongAnswers": ["1.6P1EPXYBXND5PYDLR2Y9QW1FIW7LC", "2.HX374USIV14L4OOAV"], "questionOptions": ["1.6P1EPXYBXND5PYDLR2Y9QW1FIW7LC", "2.HX374USIV14L4OOAV", "3.8QZ5BLZK23PA83VI7L4S0K8OE5"], "answerLink": "X6OGFYIISM"}, {"questionId": 221, "questionText": "AK97QPBDQLKGV90X0YDOJPIG5S7KW4ZOJQQKBMVL4TFV87JEP407V4CB75ZIUOJQTNG4CU692AOY5HSB27R2I", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.0TM0F61YSF44MBBC8X8AQKW80M62J", "wrongAnswers": ["1.IKQRWIKXLJQ9G8WQSMKAU6DIVYDLY", "2.DN228MGJ164TV987QS47EA0R2DBGJHX"], "questionOptions": ["1.IKQRWIKXLJQ9G8WQSMKAU6DIVYDLY", "2.DN228MGJ164TV987QS47EA0R2DBGJHX", "3.0TM0F61YSF44MBBC8X8AQKW80M62J"], "answerLink": "INXCJ3HGKZ"}, {"questionId": 222, "questionText": "4OZHRALSFQQOO4M650HDBKRWUM6YMNQ1SRTAMWC76OQG4LVSWVYYRTWWWVDUC0CYFWHYZC54D2", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "1.TUYHF9UEZCYYAIPOU", "wrongAnswers": ["2.CKFXN7CKBM8RRLM1H5P", "3.OLUOW10J3NJTPWMLGZCSE51"], "questionOptions": ["1.TUYHF9UEZCYYAIPOU", "2.CKFXN7CKBM8RRLM1H5P", "3.OLUOW10J3NJTPWMLGZCSE51"], "answerLink": "8PIH983B2U"}, {"questionId": 223, "questionText": "3WT58KB3S21TNM4STEXPV87AMMPHNMZR4MSTP1AL66I8LNMY3R72JOYT8XM13Q1RW7FXS7SQNS5D5HTVJYUJZET8RH9PH0SHZQNJW2TNI4SSQ9ICLDYKCHM3", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.R8EZ8X1SF729CBUB7ZIICDNUK", "wrongAnswers": ["1.M6VTFSSOD0E9NNIR", "3.1YR6CAQY21XXL27PCVMZEZSQO8KA2WRX"], "questionOptions": ["1.M6VTFSSOD0E9NNIR", "2.R8EZ8X1SF729CBUB7ZIICDNUK", "3.1YR6CAQY21XXL27PCVMZEZSQO8KA2WRX"], "answerLink": "BWNZIINYSH"}, {"questionId": 224, "questionText": "ZUNGAFZ9S7WR293ZX7CEG7TL3RX4PZHT2SM1FBOVJB6IZYRGZP3IMVJ6LHWPCET0EEOJLLU9EOAK", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "1.I30KL50X2PDFZNFK85UYHY4IUL7", "wrongAnswers": ["2.UXRK7VX3M3D40UYLU4B4VOJO4SR5D45R", "3.NAFOAJNEPXD2N6KTX1L5"], "questionOptions": ["1.I30KL50X2PDFZNFK85UYHY4IUL7", "2.UXRK7VX3M3D40UYLU4B4VOJO4SR5D45R", "3.NAFOAJNEPXD2N6KTX1L5"], "answerLink": "IZ4GXAPK10"}, {"questionId": 225, "questionText": "C17DFF2UFGF5VJ2MKZRYUPHJ35179AFRIBW3A2TWCD2SUA0CGO256O83JX53W44M6XZS2NKEJUNFMB1WH", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.0ZF64S5F3USMHCKUWADNLMR6D00IZ7", "wrongAnswers": ["1.5BN1JQNCK0O39BS5SPZO82ABW523", "3.GAKQY97U81RFZ0CI2CSLKM9"], "questionOptions": ["1.5BN1JQNCK0O39BS5SPZO82ABW523", "2.0ZF64S5F3USMHCKUWADNLMR6D00IZ7", "3.GAKQY97U81RFZ0CI2CSLKM9"], "answerLink": "5NAZ4Q2GS1"}, {"questionId": 226, "questionText": "58MA8GSHSPCMWJCM5IJA8KELOZZ0DX8WZGJIS6BCHX5PRTJ2ADR4EQFUOEK8EX4TO64XS0MWTEBG9", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.C3IY5QGIJFQGR4RJ1", "wrongAnswers": ["1.8CE30W93NXOIORROVDQX6EO", "2.BT29FEK02FWO2XLT7HL04GI1OH0SY6"], "questionOptions": ["1.8CE30W93NXOIORROVDQX6EO", "2.BT29FEK02FWO2XLT7HL04GI1OH0SY6", "3.C3IY5QGIJFQGR4RJ1"], "answerLink": "Y8MRSDI2AG"}, {"questionId": 227, "questionText": "4VCV621YKD9G59YDGIRJO2X25K0SS2B16OJCJKSAZ4HRDQ6T1BQOZIP5V2D18PSQ2FJVL399R4ZP9QCQZVABRN30KUZDXRKHM4F0", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.AJU42FIMHJ3OIF7T9EI7EZ1HDUC", "wrongAnswers": ["1.GP48E4VZM6PPU5EM93", "2.LX8NVCYJMI6YXIQB5278Q8WEFXV"], "questionOptions": ["1.GP48E4VZM6PPU5EM93", "2.LX8NVCYJMI6YXIQB5278Q8WEFXV", "3.AJU42FIMHJ3OIF7T9EI7EZ1HDUC"], "answerLink": "VQQE79L2VC"}, {"questionId": 228, "questionText": "ERSB9MNLPCR40K557K2UO2YST26WGSS9GTWL8I9VA9OKA1JFBJYIEKL94FB3QVN97K8KW3OFGVP30C9UP8X5QC", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.P680XEUXBJZBDG5ZPLESYUE5TPE7V", "wrongAnswers": ["1.62RE5TQIXZUKNIN2SVWKBL38Z", "3.6TIWKVT7I43NRAVMAJHNV9NP"], "questionOptions": ["1.62RE5TQIXZUKNIN2SVWKBL38Z", "2.P680XEUXBJZBDG5ZPLESYUE5TPE7V", "3.6TIWKVT7I43NRAVMAJHNV9NP"], "answerLink": "ZOLW5LV5FP"}, {"questionId": 229, "questionText": "OSNS6RURMANAT8Q2PF1X5ZHJIKLG5I1213ZOIO6W0PZNKKPXPMXJ802N2BG2R8RME3CUVJ6KK9OXAEG", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.WP62ONEGHKLRM7E73C4C0QULIX63HT", "wrongAnswers": ["1.FHKJAC65C60ODPASFP", "2.MKQAPYF94EU3H8YC3"], "questionOptions": ["1.FHKJAC65C60ODPASFP", "2.MKQAPYF94EU3H8YC3", "3.WP62ONEGHKLRM7E73C4C0QULIX63HT"], "answerLink": "21NHT22KJL"}, {"questionId": 230, "questionText": "Y9FOUTNDWL4201DGGTOLDCT7K7SH1ECXIIL7BDPK4T9UF0LE5IDENRXX8WHTUANMGMQC64KLWC5VDTGPM4N0", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.YKDH8DJCIVEF0YDLZ9VPQFNZA1OM", "wrongAnswers": ["1.YGKA7ALFKJHIU32X33OLYVYWE1WO5DI", "2.I36GVEPHFW38RWNLZ7F0W"], "questionOptions": ["1.YGKA7ALFKJHIU32X33OLYVYWE1WO5DI", "2.I36GVEPHFW38RWNLZ7F0W", "3.YKDH8DJCIVEF0YDLZ9VPQFNZA1OM"], "answerLink": "P1AS1I33AF"}, {"questionId": 231, "questionText": "Y8R7ZUBZ7KKZL648AC9EQBXQFW1WNETT7BDIV6TL4BZRDAZGKU6K7NB4QRO1NK3E5YYNY4X8UIL9WZMLF9Z0JFWBDXI6ZUL6OMMJCDVPM1HQBT4GBGA8HP1YB39", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.A93756I06OG5TG5H4KHZRFE5NN7BGT", "wrongAnswers": ["1.QYEYWAHTJUZ7C8H3", "2.EYH1GZA7OJ4F9YFILR0HMCZK2FUJ"], "questionOptions": ["1.QYEYWAHTJUZ7C8H3", "2.EYH1GZA7OJ4F9YFILR0HMCZK2FUJ", "3.A93756I06OG5TG5H4KHZRFE5NN7BGT"], "answerLink": "NEJCSGR9W0"}, {"questionId": 232, "questionText": "MRBUALYT0191MW700APUT9E59V5EVFS00YRRQACKL7P3EIXI0LMB6HEVUU3D6FVNTYQ4MFGB7LAL3QET0TKGI1ULC7FG2NJVALXFA43AAX77RLUH2EE", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.1XW8N7O25PXL7PITMR", "wrongAnswers": ["1.N6UDX0RGII1DMYMUK", "3.ZD46EX41EWON82QZXXQK3VCJFL41IC"], "questionOptions": ["1.N6UDX0RGII1DMYMUK", "2.1XW8N7O25PXL7PITMR", "3.ZD46EX41EWON82QZXXQK3VCJFL41IC"], "answerLink": "16K4T61RQY"}, {"questionId": 233, "questionText": "PUM53COWSUGN0G49NSUGR8GI47NR2LYY4RG3A3QJ8RO5DKBIVCQQU6TVI8BSZJNQ2NTC8Y", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.MU4JWKFJ6J2VL66G12PE7NOO8DAU", "wrongAnswers": ["1.KPT4DK9IGIX3K2JD", "2.RB4T9UNLJ7DDZ9YT1YOJG7PWAU23T86"], "questionOptions": ["1.KPT4DK9IGIX3K2JD", "2.RB4T9UNLJ7DDZ9YT1YOJG7PWAU23T86", "3.MU4JWKFJ6J2VL66G12PE7NOO8DAU"], "answerLink": "W8U17WQQ63"}, {"questionId": 234, "questionText": "4ZM5PMA18GSCXGDPFK35UZS43FXSREOS9JNOK1YDNVD5KORXJHWGLE3VYCWD4BWI0Z9PZWU", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "1.O58YCUNAK32K9VWW9JCNU0A21D", "wrongAnswers": ["2.2KNFDZ8HBPPZF6AE419Y5KWL6VA7", "3.M5B4V2SLAMW3V94CE450BXKNTB7FIM36"], "questionOptions": ["1.O58YCUNAK32K9VWW9JCNU0A21D", "2.2KNFDZ8HBPPZF6AE419Y5KWL6VA7", "3.M5B4V2SLAMW3V94CE450BXKNTB7FIM36"], "answerLink": "5KZ5BDLUEY"}, {"questionId": 235, "questionText": "S8HNWSEQ9AGUUKUI0OP7M1ECLHV60R1C26E0Q346246TFO9LOV0M6HV16BCYSCHYT20886DKU9TKFJIO1SUZT6W3AI2R6KLIQ", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.QEMFVBJHZPENUNX0VTS6XTKV2UBMHGJP", "wrongAnswers": ["1.R5VOE5QHTKSAMXETH198R5YV3V2C0SQ", "2.3Z7UBKPRXPKKCED3EW1"], "questionOptions": ["1.R5VOE5QHTKSAMXETH198R5YV3V2C0SQ", "2.3Z7UBKPRXPKKCED3EW1", "3.QEMFVBJHZPENUNX0VTS6XTKV2UBMHGJP"], "answerLink": "8688ISDJMI"}, {"questionId": 236, "questionText": "GFY4LY26O34UXTOXNT7NKM7BMFYXR8Y1QXLP2JLULWMCSEV91B1GKBXH37BANNHPQBMTB28NOJ0S2SD5H0H89E0T2D0UZP7BFL5N64YWP6SJ23U5BQ7E59LLEIFBONH3", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.7E0X3IGKG3DLWMLD8V8", "wrongAnswers": ["1.FAYPHLT0ELOJFXCWRNQANV7JNQMQLED", "3.FDTO7FQHA47QW98Z4EYCV3FUOYYVEH"], "questionOptions": ["1.FAYPHLT0ELOJFXCWRNQANV7JNQMQLED", "2.7E0X3IGKG3DLWMLD8V8", "3.FDTO7FQHA47QW98Z4EYCV3FUOYYVEH"], "answerLink": "I7R6ASIWX3"}, {"questionId": 237, "questionText": "YUYQ4XKFZSFDV8MHRI1PEK1B68XBCX3DKC4G1P4FKPRQATBKG3XMSYUCUGWBBMBPWIX36L4UIDC6R6T7OMGRN0Q3IP74JHW2NA8WHVIS7J70O373FM6", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.V1MJ31E0KSTFF9T26A32YNNOS6P18", "wrongAnswers": ["1.LJ74576VQ9RIB4N9LMP", "3.Z7YP091J3FM5SVNL"], "questionOptions": ["1.LJ74576VQ9RIB4N9LMP", "2.V1MJ31E0KSTFF9T26A32YNNOS6P18", "3.Z7YP091J3FM5SVNL"], "answerLink": "IGPLQ66KJ3"}, {"questionId": 238, "questionText": "QCC5V1WQ8U683N8UITFLOK6BQQIN3TJTR37ZFTLLYG36OFUBTMC5LKUT87XYZ10ID3UQ03X", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.OD5PK7E76D66YUX8RWJVX77NV3NC", "wrongAnswers": ["1.7QZ2JO05L3ZBY4SU0B45KPATZZL7N", "2.9ODF7VKNTI2MX1EJPHR56Q"], "questionOptions": ["1.7QZ2JO05L3ZBY4SU0B45KPATZZL7N", "2.9ODF7VKNTI2MX1EJPHR56Q", "3.OD5PK7E76D66YUX8RWJVX77NV3NC"], "answerLink": "FPPOGBN8K4"}, {"questionId": 239, "questionText": "JX3CX256FLSAOBWMAX8V3UT4BO7EY5LBY2JWOPWA54Y0VZMX42DCTGRVRSBDJFRF7A59MUSWFTQQRFSC", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "1.C224XZVMI9NSEQ5JU8LBEE0I49U4", "wrongAnswers": ["2.C2UD45D3YP5CLUTMUKENKC9CSQDK6EOZ", "3.JI10B2ZVXFGCST7M8W1C0QIN"], "questionOptions": ["1.C224XZVMI9NSEQ5JU8LBEE0I49U4", "2.C2UD45D3YP5CLUTMUKENKC9CSQDK6EOZ", "3.JI10B2ZVXFGCST7M8W1C0QIN"], "answerLink": "QXN8DDWTO3"}, {"questionId": 240, "questionText": "8BOONU2O5ZUX2T9T76I4OOPPSZDW4V5729CNWNRZTNN5OJDZG71QCYHKKVAJOLSNGYUMBOUKUIHD8OQZ5K", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.VB1E7K3PDHYX4ZFMFDCMKGSX7OX5CN", "wrongAnswers": ["1.3QYJLRKJ0H3HS447AKJ69UNT7MYTWEC", "2.DAB6X9J8MTBG2B3LO"], "questionOptions": ["1.3QYJLRKJ0H3HS447AKJ69UNT7MYTWEC", "2.DAB6X9J8MTBG2B3LO", "3.VB1E7K3PDHYX4ZFMFDCMKGSX7OX5CN"], "answerLink": "Y4VEB6FOTJ"}, {"questionId": 241, "questionText": "VM7B39R57C05C19SGKZ9L2IG9GEWH73L3JPJ1A5RN642G81KIY6IGFYAXH4L39EX9G01U9GPTH5M", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.DDIZM6K8ZBP9C45NIZFQELRG843AUSX", "wrongAnswers": ["1.NXIOGW8RKGFWBOVHUTVSWBXS8QIABB", "3.YIM9473IMTL7WH1OR5R"], "questionOptions": ["1.NXIOGW8RKGFWBOVHUTVSWBXS8QIABB", "2.DDIZM6K8ZBP9C45NIZFQELRG843AUSX", "3.YIM9473IMTL7WH1OR5R"], "answerLink": "MRMQ71TTZV"}, {"questionId": 242, "questionText": "LFNUILZ4LD2QP7OJLPUUDRG67N6TDIU7PPUBMYBTP2LRIBMUAHQUQJGZ9AA3AX7DTH01V0GA1VXXP6N463IMFDNARG7D7ZXRIX9QE2BSB3VRQS99ZLNMR1CIVK", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.FD4GCI2QWG723Y8UI", "wrongAnswers": ["1.TJ9URQM7BX2718N4C", "2.RD12Q2D5YXAZQHYZABGG"], "questionOptions": ["1.TJ9URQM7BX2718N4C", "2.RD12Q2D5YXAZQHYZABGG", "3.FD4GCI2QWG723Y8UI"], "answerLink": "PU0VTAK1ND"}, {"questionId": 243, "questionText": "48OOLAIK2TPQCH1O3AYAWKCW62R5MOB97WRFJSR99K2CR5LSMC5GM9I3WF0S4Q9YOGDX04VAL5L73GB4CQ0TLZL11F", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "1.TDV9NMYFI6C5U1QL0BNV", "wrongAnswers": ["2.SBYW27WSXYT44KMFQWAKO0NJN8", "3.RY2C40G3VV1W9JCKAR"], "questionOptions": ["1.TDV9NMYFI6C5U1QL0BNV", "2.SBYW27WSXYT44KMFQWAKO0NJN8", "3.RY2C40G3VV1W9JCKAR"], "answerLink": "FAT0SEY85N"}, {"questionId": 244, "questionText": "Q4AGI9LTMGSIIX2N530HFS9UTVM7HYLYLBHDDGQ44FAH8673VFGV6ULVB9SLCHOWHWS8LE4GGHQH439DVGKCIZBLKD5D33X", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "1.UOYX48FKHYSPZGU3GRLEWWAWL3TBIM", "wrongAnswers": ["2.72YQCKV3MEORRK582RLFY0SE0KF6Z7", "3.Q47PC27O6F799JEYTAI8TKM"], "questionOptions": ["1.UOYX48FKHYSPZGU3GRLEWWAWL3TBIM", "2.72YQCKV3MEORRK582RLFY0SE0KF6Z7", "3.Q47PC27O6F799JEYTAI8TKM"], "answerLink": "20K5Q82QT4"}, {"questionId": 245, "questionText": "H0T5R94XJZKOPLUR4HKUMOHA7X1SWIHOOEELSDXN8AG0VMJ9BODM6XIJWKXC7HR57MV9CIQ2CLIYXMBP6TF20VUI5IDGOB3GL0IQD522WHXRGFHAOJK9Y", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.OWTJFQ2RGX4SEZ49MRHUZ2JS3NLEJ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.2P11VO1X5Y06OG5UVT", "3.SMPWD3BRPA4NHMCF11"], "questionOptions": ["1.2P11VO1X5Y06OG5UVT", "2.OWTJFQ2RGX4SEZ49MRHUZ2JS3NLEJ", "3.SMPWD3BRPA4NHMCF11"], "answerLink": "ZH6AJ9GPG7"}, {"questionId": 246, "questionText": "XHA2CHOQKA00PAEEDPZ63T04BXS4JEYCUGRHW6PV6CTWES780SYIS777CQVC5IFYZPT71L4HOEPHOOM9I7ABVS2Y53TK8HSVKZ30BWE6BW", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "3.H77LT6H2US07Q69FC9ANVKZM7EXYMK82", "wrongAnswers": ["1.5UPEGF4IF4K0N5HQMKD51DQNNZ9", "2.U29ZN0S09PG6UZE0PHW86321"], "questionOptions": ["1.5UPEGF4IF4K0N5HQMKD51DQNNZ9", "2.U29ZN0S09PG6UZE0PHW86321", "3.H77LT6H2US07Q69FC9ANVKZM7EXYMK82"], "answerLink": "3LR1O6KPLJ"}, {"questionId": 247, "questionText": "KQQEXRSYBWFM5MRCKJMYVIT0UAZ4NZ9ADG1PFNS6FGA631D1PMAO2SNMTIL077PKXWYQ5VI2SF4XT65SLB2WHVQ", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "1.DKTZVGCNLUDUMN86FW98FI", "wrongAnswers": ["2.OQPHTG55BT2AVP639XMB1D07Z8", "3.C44LG7Q4APM3D4J9J7CXPGUCWFE"], "questionOptions": ["1.DKTZVGCNLUDUMN86FW98FI", "2.OQPHTG55BT2AVP639XMB1D07Z8", "3.C44LG7Q4APM3D4J9J7CXPGUCWFE"], "answerLink": "MQ0ENYW0CZ"}, {"questionId": 248, "questionText": "W5CTLHV709TMG0HKJS6NDEWYM634WINOMICGJ76MOQPKY0UOZEHX61416KUX7AZHH3X8A3C1QCSQ4SIQUUOLR9LMUXX86TD0YLUZXULRU9", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "1.W851AU3EXQG3TFDLDJEEU", "wrongAnswers": ["2.05E9JZP3Y6MODZWRHC", "3.GW3RLIQ9UVKOYSTXSI"], "questionOptions": ["1.W851AU3EXQG3TFDLDJEEU", "2.05E9JZP3Y6MODZWRHC", "3.GW3RLIQ9UVKOYSTXSI"], "answerLink": "PNZTLI29HW"}, {"questionId": 249, "questionText": "CUENEPHX13EPWUOD260NTU5I63FEVYT1CRICHUXAL18A7CMUEZWXLBCYFDAPDWKFWFO0A0J1TQT2UJ5WEXH98YK", "questionCategory": "Regola 6", "correctAnswers": "2.NK9BEQJ5XFFTRJG36KG8OXZAQO9PA", "wrongAnswers": ["1.OJKQ7RXYYPLJTUNTFJ92KUYZ", "3.V9MCQVFO2AK013D63ZSQHZE"], "questionOptions": ["1.OJKQ7RXYYPLJTUNTFJ92KUYZ", "2.NK9BEQJ5XFFTRJG36KG8OXZAQO9PA", "3.V9MCQVFO2AK013D63ZSQHZE"], "answerLink": "7F25W0P1C0"}, {"questionId": 250, "questionText": "ZNEQ8YLHWXGW6PR22ACWCYO4EUM39GGX1Y7U71Y6ZI0J9UG90Y7IFT4TFUCY7G88Z4FKEXQ8JT69EJSIGNJ1ECJEYDECN78MF3GQL3VINZ2Q", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "1.QT0K3MXABY7KS0QBG", "wrongAnswers": ["2.LIHTJEAKD1RQM2MWPPXY6S00Q16AC", "3.ZSET1U7FJ85GW8HUTRZN3LRVH2242B0"], "questionOptions": ["1.QT0K3MXABY7KS0QBG", "2.LIHTJEAKD1RQM2MWPPXY6S00Q16AC", "3.ZSET1U7FJ85GW8HUTRZN3LRVH2242B0"], "answerLink": "2SQAVFYQX8"}, {"questionId": 251, "questionText": "XF0EHA6EXKI60ASD2R5CY2Z5GH05ZB5L99JEPP2QRCMBLYEI311RQ7FUHM9NYG5LDVCABKMPOUENR2IC8VT89O8Q09ZOZK9JFSGKVH17KVAIXWX9GKZKF1JIQDD32MKC", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "2.9MOAHL4V0AXC5R1QAU6TRJV2F", "wrongAnswers": ["1.YTLNVOYQMO0MFBTJ7", "3.DEF2JLYACRS0JC9KWV26YN3"], "questionOptions": ["1.YTLNVOYQMO0MFBTJ7", "2.9MOAHL4V0AXC5R1QAU6TRJV2F", "3.DEF2JLYACRS0JC9KWV26YN3"], "answerLink": "7VQ6323IR6"}, {"questionId": 252, "questionText": "5EHD2OJMU67O3RYUO6G3QY6K5KLURH01NR5TYSLAJSH07ORXTE6RDUQOVT2RWJYQMAW7BQKZB9MZR7OL12X2ABM59MBA5", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "2.LBQ97NP5ZGW5GNCO2CGHT7X6LZRCUOWS", "wrongAnswers": ["1.Y7B7QEP7RI3BZXZHASOEP5J", "3.ZXOQ000YRJ8KNRNC4E8V"], "questionOptions": ["1.Y7B7QEP7RI3BZXZHASOEP5J", "2.LBQ97NP5ZGW5GNCO2CGHT7X6LZRCUOWS", "3.ZXOQ000YRJ8KNRNC4E8V"], "answerLink": "3ARBWWU94U"}, {"questionId": 253, "questionText": "I1C9XEOM7BYL6NYGMRJQMEC5BQSAW35B54C1KI2HCAWRWIHLP8M5BFSE4GYAL14UWB9PJFZSC8SAZU7AWJ4U72Z1OSLLSMCIN4LTSM", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "3.AMXTB3TNKXCLT1KVF15QXRPD4TID55", "wrongAnswers": ["1.GK1A1ACRMGYHLPUOCS8CMFK3S2IPV6", "2.FGV6XQKG6FL4J70KZYGXZZH9TZXLAH"], "questionOptions": ["1.GK1A1ACRMGYHLPUOCS8CMFK3S2IPV6", "2.FGV6XQKG6FL4J70KZYGXZZH9TZXLAH", "3.AMXTB3TNKXCLT1KVF15QXRPD4TID55"], "answerLink": "COLD9D45OM"}, {"questionId": 254, "questionText": "VJTDZ5ZAM9YW6M2W6YNNR7DQE4ND5R7J13JEUI5I8NTUBI12799JIG4D55VJ6WHSODOSOH7OSH87W0DJUQ5MQ44FG58NWNY", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "2.3SCE2ZR5GE7A99EZSHJN", "wrongAnswers": ["1.R8A3OEYV9H56D79K8", "3.ZZBVTHJMB27VYYV475Q"], "questionOptions": ["1.R8A3OEYV9H56D79K8", "2.3SCE2ZR5GE7A99EZSHJN", "3.ZZBVTHJMB27VYYV475Q"], "answerLink": "G4KV1GSIV0"}, {"questionId": 255, "questionText": "DOL7819ZZ0Y17RUZ8B3V4DCHQVOX4DIAVUK92E8FEH9DFPK6SGUF310FD8QYGOTV64RGCMME9370RJVGBZCQZUBDJZN04A5QXZO4G7LCALUDTK3U2XJCW", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "1.UZ9LFBNAJED4JIEFXIE78K7MW9TE9", "wrongAnswers": ["2.XHT0ZKO33OINV6KPJGV2EKS93GRK", "3.H12YZHDESV8BV5WLN6DQ8TXK0H3W"], "questionOptions": ["1.UZ9LFBNAJED4JIEFXIE78K7MW9TE9", "2.XHT0ZKO33OINV6KPJGV2EKS93GRK", "3.H12YZHDESV8BV5WLN6DQ8TXK0H3W"], "answerLink": "W5261JC388"}, {"questionId": 256, "questionText": "SFNWO4FQA8EAI69X4CX08NWLDKHCTLVPE3P5VCGFHWT1KTSR4T6PXYNE9WF3J1MO4F34W1XK56V8WGY9ZLBRVIPND15TMZH8OK8UCG5GAYEK9LLL4MKCI41JJ", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "2.CMDGG5XBHYGTM0VKTACL4R1WEH3H0K4M", "wrongAnswers": ["1.EYAAQVZ1SFY7J5U9DU5OWIYSFDF", "3.GGOZFZ8H3U6U1LGXNB4JKT"], "questionOptions": ["1.EYAAQVZ1SFY7J5U9DU5OWIYSFDF", "2.CMDGG5XBHYGTM0VKTACL4R1WEH3H0K4M", "3.GGOZFZ8H3U6U1LGXNB4JKT"], "answerLink": "EHYWO6E4G1"}, {"questionId": 257, "questionText": "90M2ANVNT93J5QXX7DVDYRCP15CFNXBA8P59ACY833ENY6W123856BOKAGO5N2K8P1VMPLQRTH5331NM7SDUIHXO32Q46L6EAL1K", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "2.APLLLP310RTE2B3QRUTPXFB", "wrongAnswers": ["1.XU795E7UYF77XDY58ING1KKDY", "3.OFHM146TZZ4GOBTSW"], "questionOptions": ["1.XU795E7UYF77XDY58ING1KKDY", "2.APLLLP310RTE2B3QRUTPXFB", "3.OFHM146TZZ4GOBTSW"], "answerLink": "JJE59F8667"}, {"questionId": 258, "questionText": "7E92OHBMB6UW9RU2R7TNFPAF07DYD5M74VJF5H5NZJNV25NSWCTWOITAEKPK2YQL53QIFIPO5TRHWPXQ9I827SGH1IZQ4H3NUOVKJTKPGLP98NCGP4JIJEBKSV", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "3.SDQAY6QCFS0X1UT4084BEYA5SU9K0", "wrongAnswers": ["1.E0SBKKKO09U3PYSLQ3GQGQL", "2.F9GH92LK0MJMM7NTFQH32PD30G"], "questionOptions": ["1.E0SBKKKO09U3PYSLQ3GQGQL", "2.F9GH92LK0MJMM7NTFQH32PD30G", "3.SDQAY6QCFS0X1UT4084BEYA5SU9K0"], "answerLink": "63OCITU09V"}, {"questionId": 259, "questionText": "HPM8ZLWPO5CK90Y8E8DO1I426O2S1BWJ8MXCMTONIZR6J6EJ9Z45BU586I8538IWZIBX479YGRDY6WI85ZA2UVEFORSBPU0", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "3.C1EBEZTLAPJJO14KPHU7C", "wrongAnswers": ["1.V87MKCVDCYU8Y6TZVJGIUX1EDU6H", "2.NTJOA6ZQ5W6ZJQQ2YJSNE4MS39GEU5U"], "questionOptions": ["1.V87MKCVDCYU8Y6TZVJGIUX1EDU6H", "2.NTJOA6ZQ5W6ZJQQ2YJSNE4MS39GEU5U", "3.C1EBEZTLAPJJO14KPHU7C"], "answerLink": "QKR66ITU5Z"}, {"questionId": 260, "questionText": "XCXRXX8PKZUGO2ZZ7SBJVLGT8UH3VENUDOH5LVGZZ9QZMZ6KZSJJ6SNFQAR675ID51HBOEB3SMSY8PYXRP1D3P51IPTOZ", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "3.VQUCELBYNJNEIZD4ER", "wrongAnswers": ["1.H1OJ5NCT05W7N99LQX936", "2.3V9AX1GAUQO4ID3ZR9F9OQKWQMLB"], "questionOptions": ["1.H1OJ5NCT05W7N99LQX936", "2.3V9AX1GAUQO4ID3ZR9F9OQKWQMLB", "3.VQUCELBYNJNEIZD4ER"], "answerLink": "S8GF284SQK"}, {"questionId": 261, "questionText": "5TAME2PE847YUOXGZ2VH2R1K6FXZ21YCE9NLTMHC4KZRFMTTWI88FIG7LHRGZTE6THLRCMZPJE4G6JLNV6B9J5Q3MU5VF2C2IN0YMHFSV756PZTWXL", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "2.N7P0NFQZ4RX8CHD8R", "wrongAnswers": ["1.OA5BOHZBN89SNHVI2KC988UV0", "3.P8YFWFB9WKMGWNROMDY2KKM"], "questionOptions": ["1.OA5BOHZBN89SNHVI2KC988UV0", "2.N7P0NFQZ4RX8CHD8R", "3.P8YFWFB9WKMGWNROMDY2KKM"], "answerLink": "RPON380R5X"}, {"questionId": 262, "questionText": "OO9RVEKNYIOGU6Y0EHNHG941Z3PBZTCU9LCM3HNWLYT2TFDXQYS1TPQGLBF1K1R3399HEFYPA3Q", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "2.SAJ0OG56ILT1YC6YL0XKDOOAV9VTHT1W", "wrongAnswers": ["1.EGZBBL1IE3SV2IT4DU", "3.HVQM81ICNOHPC27DWJB7SNFCWJFF"], "questionOptions": ["1.EGZBBL1IE3SV2IT4DU", "2.SAJ0OG56ILT1YC6YL0XKDOOAV9VTHT1W", "3.HVQM81ICNOHPC27DWJB7SNFCWJFF"], "answerLink": "AQMV1Q8Z48"}, {"questionId": 263, "questionText": "1ZXFS6O06KLCMDRBUFFKLXTYKN2QKK726NBCX27CJW51N0KS8517DL8OBLADRGCBG1SBUAFLB18WFYX4GLUVEHE85DC330QEJ85YT8BQ", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "1.E2ZE53F36NFIR1HL6GJEFPRJ2R2", "wrongAnswers": ["2.Z3XWTHZ3NBNJYGZRVY", "3.EYMKK7WYSUGZL2V71YMDXOOL"], "questionOptions": ["1.E2ZE53F36NFIR1HL6GJEFPRJ2R2", "2.Z3XWTHZ3NBNJYGZRVY", "3.EYMKK7WYSUGZL2V71YMDXOOL"], "answerLink": "PPGUL3N1T8"}, {"questionId": 264, "questionText": "P358K62LO3XGTI7EKDVWFITT7XSWLQEZMXYH8X4E0RH6QI7K101V8F72FW6RMV5F7FP1TRT2STO7L4QF2I78ZITY1MXC600Z29SJM5R", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "2.JKSL5UR5U2XPAJCRK5B9TG", "wrongAnswers": ["1.69J6IPSHAZUGRMB0B6NXSWTQXQD5YF0", "3.P3HFNRWG8Y1REE8NFS9D"], "questionOptions": ["1.69J6IPSHAZUGRMB0B6NXSWTQXQD5YF0", "2.JKSL5UR5U2XPAJCRK5B9TG", "3.P3HFNRWG8Y1REE8NFS9D"], "answerLink": "3XMM1TLAIC"}, {"questionId": 265, "questionText": "QZN08RZAPU17TYPHE0L5JFGYM432UUYFIGVF3VIDGWSCW326V4B3DR1HAAEEGOY44GROLAW6URVEN7VLS7QEUJ1TBEL7EGPTI4GCAHZ9", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "3.BZC2KVDVJAJ2EMXKVPOJHRIOJ4SFT9HJ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.U7SOSSNRH02RAAHA4", "2.MEVKEBLIY4ZGTMNVAQP"], "questionOptions": ["1.U7SOSSNRH02RAAHA4", "2.MEVKEBLIY4ZGTMNVAQP", "3.BZC2KVDVJAJ2EMXKVPOJHRIOJ4SFT9HJ"], "answerLink": "7VM040V997"}, {"questionId": 266, "questionText": "ZHFYQUAE0GZDMGKILQ6YBCADDU2590TD956W7ZTTW9G55L4E866BLWN38GON290HC39E3CV7AAH", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "1.Q72AUCK52JFMYREF4OM4ATJXT7G4X4V", "wrongAnswers": ["2.WJYAIBL40B1C5X8PJ4Z418T5JR2", "3.O89BRHJGT44N2Z8Y5"], "questionOptions": ["1.Q72AUCK52JFMYREF4OM4ATJXT7G4X4V", "2.WJYAIBL40B1C5X8PJ4Z418T5JR2", "3.O89BRHJGT44N2Z8Y5"], "answerLink": "FAE3JG661I"}, {"questionId": 267, "questionText": "5XERBPTBRAZ8YFSQVKCKTX7FY1G3A1FO2SJAHDO5OKPRMM1CTPQYTHIJXKG680UM7ZV5SNA8RA9B10Z7I0W2WYG4RQCYEQVGITWCW43FNESZS85KSZJNK5MIV2GVCV", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "2.83HD4AM17P149IJEC", "wrongAnswers": ["1.8QRTR6IJET8PMPBIFOX2", "3.3BJP8NAIW5RV8HAXJU5ACP"], "questionOptions": ["1.8QRTR6IJET8PMPBIFOX2", "2.83HD4AM17P149IJEC", "3.3BJP8NAIW5RV8HAXJU5ACP"], "answerLink": "3KWRC78NW4"}, {"questionId": 268, "questionText": "PKSGGZLTMHNKSLE5PGQXR5WB1YF2GXSJ44S0UDSPWP69SHCCHSCU4N6UGJTK3DIAXLL0YYWEMXRTN8W99NYO9EUU8XVK6YDAFVQSW6Q", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "3.I34K8ODMC66IYEM3OZ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.O8EZ6GB9IBA5T1WIT9I0Q5", "2.AOCCH997TBP398IX7"], "questionOptions": ["1.O8EZ6GB9IBA5T1WIT9I0Q5", "2.AOCCH997TBP398IX7", "3.I34K8ODMC66IYEM3OZ"], "answerLink": "RXDNACI50V"}, {"questionId": 269, "questionText": "9I3HB4SBF3JTI3OBWQDN8F3EV1GFLVGVDB9N9AUFR7X1F7BKP8G4JIG3GF9Q2KUJQ1YMC0BR77QCN2B", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "1.BCOQTSFW8P6IMGNN", "wrongAnswers": ["2.548Y278LF065H919YM", "3.C055MA3CG8ZM3PLZW"], "questionOptions": ["1.BCOQTSFW8P6IMGNN", "2.548Y278LF065H919YM", "3.C055MA3CG8ZM3PLZW"], "answerLink": "6KHCR1ZBBO"}, {"questionId": 270, "questionText": "4WJFCESJKKP6RH58YUNY8EAWKFNKYD4EZXV6MIITW04VI4FP3KR0MZUF7WOH0DZ5QJN1WHXKC8NZPLZ3RFO8PQHRFXS6G27XSLD", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "2.34J0NZRNTUII1S7I", "wrongAnswers": ["1.8TE6HYH31IVP9VT631", "3.RVZLDXQMR4RDAO54HW9BPIZZ95HY"], "questionOptions": ["1.8TE6HYH31IVP9VT631", "2.34J0NZRNTUII1S7I", "3.RVZLDXQMR4RDAO54HW9BPIZZ95HY"], "answerLink": "OTLMM8G0IE"}, {"questionId": 271, "questionText": "5T8YCR7NC1U27RQYLISSS7ASRXFX1JIX1SJ5EHMGYD9LNONLPA2AQ35VEANJLD1BC", "questionCategory": "Regola 7", "correctAnswers": "2.6MWQM19Y0TMSH7YOQ406OA8NFKE3", "wrongAnswers": ["1.IEWW4LD71TFZ483XU3DBCWQ7BRH4AIH", "3.LZLDDQT007X8N2TYEIWOGF1D203D6I"], "questionOptions": ["1.IEWW4LD71TFZ483XU3DBCWQ7BRH4AIH", "2.6MWQM19Y0TMSH7YOQ406OA8NFKE3", "3.LZLDDQT007X8N2TYEIWOGF1D203D6I"], "answerLink": "OVX93K67T0"}, {"questionId": 272, "questionText": "KAHBJYBU8L48VUNXIVDXYXCTA1HCTPQGC5QFPTO44N3C7U1TQULRNEBWJTOX9C5M5BRH9F7NHSJ70VF1B734CUDB2JESP", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "2.KNBJYL7UA99EVFP2M46FJ2Q4UI0R79", "wrongAnswers": ["1.THNZCGMFUQF1R1GNYZBZT317L0AYR6FD", "3.X0SGKUF3M671TP2KQKEI57BTE"], "questionOptions": ["1.THNZCGMFUQF1R1GNYZBZT317L0AYR6FD", "2.KNBJYL7UA99EVFP2M46FJ2Q4UI0R79", "3.X0SGKUF3M671TP2KQKEI57BTE"], "answerLink": "TL2WO27D96"}, {"questionId": 273, "questionText": "RCS7EPW9VXBMUOPG1F4XJVJZL8JYYEPXC9OLFW1FC05UNAHVLV6U7OZXEE7BAIHZCUMQ5WQV6X4Z7OSHEXFVHBR4KCECKOFLMUCRPX", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "3.2XNFLLDKOAHSOMU8DUD8IC8ZP0HMYS", "wrongAnswers": ["1.7TWDA526YEJ7TSCY4Q8YTE", "2.1X4QA268N1ZHZUXDSFRF8L85XT963CTJ"], "questionOptions": ["1.7TWDA526YEJ7TSCY4Q8YTE", "2.1X4QA268N1ZHZUXDSFRF8L85XT963CTJ", "3.2XNFLLDKOAHSOMU8DUD8IC8ZP0HMYS"], "answerLink": "XFZVKPKVLE"}, {"questionId": 274, "questionText": "PUX7SPEF7PUFUX6OW7CSAKGJD2QA9KNC3V9D5OF5HZ4XKNNS9WFRF0EZ5V6G1NJZ1MFOEXWEZ7Y585UZOB4", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "3.RCFL37CHHJZZXXFE2WG20392QVNS9W", "wrongAnswers": ["1.LAU6EO2ASN7LQ50RUJ1GOMT3O", "2.Z3H51CMGJLEZ2UD1L"], "questionOptions": ["1.LAU6EO2ASN7LQ50RUJ1GOMT3O", "2.Z3H51CMGJLEZ2UD1L", "3.RCFL37CHHJZZXXFE2WG20392QVNS9W"], "answerLink": "9LPP5MNDGK"}, {"questionId": 275, "questionText": "DO7C1BEOK7KBLFTCEIRD1Q9NIS6SWMDDP918AAO7RXCJZIOHU71542DBGPSQXG7QKNHW7TIQTUD0U22OMMGMV3371E1ZQU6WHSH6V3W8NZCE9WNQNDN", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "1.YMB7WKE6N1DI27ME12MA0E0FNJZ54", "wrongAnswers": ["2.UQ6SZ83OVRE3WCM8BB", "3.NU4XHSCF0A9U2IWC8D4BRT3UEM07KN7V"], "questionOptions": ["1.YMB7WKE6N1DI27ME12MA0E0FNJZ54", "2.UQ6SZ83OVRE3WCM8BB", "3.NU4XHSCF0A9U2IWC8D4BRT3UEM07KN7V"], "answerLink": "FCF8XII4LP"}, {"questionId": 276, "questionText": "LB30JRM68WY49I59G070RF0PBITD5BKCU5A4P4PFF6FGARE7OBZ7ZRNC35BPB5C1KTBUXY8V5JW4ZAS", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "1.TYV7R8D2FM146M5TIE76JOAAG", "wrongAnswers": ["2.75YKMWC9DVUM85W0IJHZKCMU6", "3.RJ56A1KT7152FZROB1PZWPOB96ENTR"], "questionOptions": ["1.TYV7R8D2FM146M5TIE76JOAAG", "2.75YKMWC9DVUM85W0IJHZKCMU6", "3.RJ56A1KT7152FZROB1PZWPOB96ENTR"], "answerLink": "6X75AG2P7E"}, {"questionId": 277, "questionText": "HS4AE65N4158KIMP9AF0125UP9XZPE8DUSO3YKNAEXKL9Z2CCFOL3QMBTPF3DIESHL2GEEL39VI", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "2.055NO619COWLWAR9LJA7D35X", "wrongAnswers": ["1.VBPVI3Z7AJOBURBQLF60UBQAFD", "3.8A7IK2ADP4NP7Z89Z"], "questionOptions": ["1.VBPVI3Z7AJOBURBQLF60UBQAFD", "2.055NO619COWLWAR9LJA7D35X", "3.8A7IK2ADP4NP7Z89Z"], "answerLink": "LY1BIG14SB"}, {"questionId": 278, "questionText": "VLRY58PWEKWC0YJ2GX5RO5EPKNN0F45M5SLXBEF84OS3H4UACVNG6S4NN3H1F6H43DIMNT5W4O3R", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "2.1GPQ09OCKU7LP4CU7V0YXMB2JUG", "wrongAnswers": ["1.W6Q4P4GXJRT7YBHQ", "3.41EHOWMETEVB28MBG7"], "questionOptions": ["1.W6Q4P4GXJRT7YBHQ", "2.1GPQ09OCKU7LP4CU7V0YXMB2JUG", "3.41EHOWMETEVB28MBG7"], "answerLink": "IE8JWQ10ZN"}, {"questionId": 279, "questionText": "CT1XRWULWVD0SGTWA6GVFOA895KTX1TRWKRYWDCM3891RZ439V5X2FA6H9GBW4PMU0DF8QPVOSQ2B87A66ARH7587VY0W4N2PQRXOMELVDN6OP", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "1.R0T5WDVPXCZAXZWLKBUV1Z5004XAB", "wrongAnswers": ["2.R9MQJY9ATH3WQMD7FVTJ9ZUE7M4", "3.R2WF6F9VWTLZVYBYDDX9MUP"], "questionOptions": ["1.R0T5WDVPXCZAXZWLKBUV1Z5004XAB", "2.R9MQJY9ATH3WQMD7FVTJ9ZUE7M4", "3.R2WF6F9VWTLZVYBYDDX9MUP"], "answerLink": "GV6A2CZ880"}, {"questionId": 280, "questionText": "FMGIO412RMQSUNJMRK44SP4XVNMPHXRHX9N89PX0ZBGA0XAMW3AYXX00I5EQQTOHUY4L2USD2C19YB7TOWIPV7Q6YJ156FGZEWKJ118P5G16I", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "2.1FF40M5OG7FPW8SIB21JUYIVCEYRT", "wrongAnswers": ["1.DRMGSHUVV0BZW0XFP70WSCV", "3.936U8OXCGQCVFMP6HWM4Z3SVIMA2"], "questionOptions": ["1.DRMGSHUVV0BZW0XFP70WSCV", "2.1FF40M5OG7FPW8SIB21JUYIVCEYRT", "3.936U8OXCGQCVFMP6HWM4Z3SVIMA2"], "answerLink": "L0W2E61416"}, {"questionId": 281, "questionText": "IDG6OA9CEGM0EH4NBWSO1POARHLSYLFBO5T063K17XL1PIT4CD97QBBMGN76KQGMP7TCLJY5GVJYPXFV359JGAVJIOIMOM0QMKNDER0W9", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "2.BQSQ5BRYTTLMPYZS0QY0BSBQAFFWP", "wrongAnswers": ["1.63S4320CU8ZOYBNAWASHB9VM3I4Y9", "3.C3ZEQR63NEVB5K6XEC1SXC5TQWH"], "questionOptions": ["1.63S4320CU8ZOYBNAWASHB9VM3I4Y9", "2.BQSQ5BRYTTLMPYZS0QY0BSBQAFFWP", "3.C3ZEQR63NEVB5K6XEC1SXC5TQWH"], "answerLink": "T3G2S776VJ"}, {"questionId": 282, "questionText": "I1DNAHS2UBMI3OW6LNZRJXAV0Q9URYS0H51OLJTCXUVYVTDYGQ078K37E9V24168BP7NV86T2B0HG2WJPH1W5O7P1P17IVYR7M6WOSAECHDY4SVG3D8PUSCTA3L", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "1.0GUQRID7K7AOZ0DWAVALRR0C6X21C9L3", "wrongAnswers": ["2.HTYBNEXPKERZEZRBLRVI9SNURJ2UGX25", "3.AJR96NLCNXANOI4F448OYMZ"], "questionOptions": ["1.0GUQRID7K7AOZ0DWAVALRR0C6X21C9L3", "2.HTYBNEXPKERZEZRBLRVI9SNURJ2UGX25", "3.AJR96NLCNXANOI4F448OYMZ"], "answerLink": "YZ6XSQU7QY"}, {"questionId": 283, "questionText": "VFKYOF5769SQT73P2PKJJDDKPIRFJOKKOGZ4A3LTJ8CPGMHJ1ZVFQA40QSYFRG1TLUIT8PCCTI952LO96YOV9OT47MYT57VAFR0NBNBMZ9GN6TKEODBLYR2D4FLUXIA3", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "3.DC0ZBVQRCXOT06S1HH4OUB", "wrongAnswers": ["1.ZPV12MRUFDJN2B6HCE5", "2.3F6IQJYTGG35CJF3NQ6HD9YIPWP5B1NA"], "questionOptions": ["1.ZPV12MRUFDJN2B6HCE5", "2.3F6IQJYTGG35CJF3NQ6HD9YIPWP5B1NA", "3.DC0ZBVQRCXOT06S1HH4OUB"], "answerLink": "1T82ES1SRP"}, {"questionId": 284, "questionText": "3GPK39VWIQW0LM5ZTMGQC59Y267P8VKJG358JNG4NG6VXE0BJE79BCNXCCUQ299EST8R16S9GYJQA7HKRD7AF77H0CD", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "2.0JIW2VDULYS5GLRFCVY", "wrongAnswers": ["1.24L2ZMY9WEIAY4VW0BWLMOWRWP", "3.I81C2V5N6DKLOHNJ1DXZ"], "questionOptions": ["1.24L2ZMY9WEIAY4VW0BWLMOWRWP", "2.0JIW2VDULYS5GLRFCVY", "3.I81C2V5N6DKLOHNJ1DXZ"], "answerLink": "B8FG4PJ0Q2"}, {"questionId": 285, "questionText": "RP7GEDR0IHCH1UBXU0FHE51P7E67CSVURM028C7VRE80RL0XOZ52CQ3R4HIZQ7MN07AI3VR20QG81YBRI6N1302TUVPQIP87HCK", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "2.PEHVP2FQYSH6FHTC407E5EEXU0SQARW", "wrongAnswers": ["1.O0RFVKB2ANRJVWVTY9P", "3.42946O5I3KS2MG826MS0ABCK7UJ936QC"], "questionOptions": ["1.O0RFVKB2ANRJVWVTY9P", "2.PEHVP2FQYSH6FHTC407E5EEXU0SQARW", "3.42946O5I3KS2MG826MS0ABCK7UJ936QC"], "answerLink": "YANV6B957T"}, {"questionId": 286, "questionText": "GQZR3ZEYD78P9NL8QYVODQAL1CT8TWAT9RG8SYPU2RE46U3G4JRYRHFQZXEZA7UUZ08IVDZ1ZGUHUYEII6APM2BA8I8", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "3.3D133J89AM2HJKP4EU07NFP", "wrongAnswers": ["1.CRQSU9JGXYHP51GHF2", "2.CA111FJR5Q0G5RXPJ4S75KFGP0AFHJE0"], "questionOptions": ["1.CRQSU9JGXYHP51GHF2", "2.CA111FJR5Q0G5RXPJ4S75KFGP0AFHJE0", "3.3D133J89AM2HJKP4EU07NFP"], "answerLink": "GV7FYX19TI"}, {"questionId": 287, "questionText": "ZYK8V5C1FQ10CL5AW6NBZ2BPUS1MUHXP6G0BKWH2B2GGHP4TJW6YB46L2L0RA3HE08FX3VCC0YATDCE1SLDZ5R5GN7", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "1.4ZYDBTQ71SM115462G1HQ", "wrongAnswers": ["2.XAKG2MH6CN3LS9OTMT65BD", "3.RJ9LVHM5C1TV0HNSUE"], "questionOptions": ["1.4ZYDBTQ71SM115462G1HQ", "2.XAKG2MH6CN3LS9OTMT65BD", "3.RJ9LVHM5C1TV0HNSUE"], "answerLink": "6R0212P06J"}, {"questionId": 288, "questionText": "64PEDEK6J4K4E86IYG4J3NL5GWMW96SANNAMCEVCTHF2043L7XC1X4WP2M43FH5JR5F4H09AWIE90UENFP92BRGMHXW1LUBP1X3V1N3NH6HC9XSDNDQ", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "3.MWOPGS1R155H6OUHO0RR7XPSAL", "wrongAnswers": ["1.H0BMSUGFB5CQ00FO0L1FA7XWFKA66KY", "2.PGNI1GAW4W4WYMK7427B1L"], "questionOptions": ["1.H0BMSUGFB5CQ00FO0L1FA7XWFKA66KY", "2.PGNI1GAW4W4WYMK7427B1L", "3.MWOPGS1R155H6OUHO0RR7XPSAL"], "answerLink": "Q1G37BSU02"}, {"questionId": 289, "questionText": "MH6P6EIQHGQ2QQ64NES5TLXSMS7F7S71F99V6VFN61QOOR59XMOSO08OG7TB551K2Z7CCDQTXB6N60NHPLWWJO8ST", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "1.3NQ8G0VCFPLKQXJB5PV7", "wrongAnswers": ["2.D95XW7L4NVKQKONZZP9JL", "3.RW38979UIAL6ELRPMMWZ0QBV94"], "questionOptions": ["1.3NQ8G0VCFPLKQXJB5PV7", "2.D95XW7L4NVKQKONZZP9JL", "3.RW38979UIAL6ELRPMMWZ0QBV94"], "answerLink": "5TTJC7LZL5"}, {"questionId": 290, "questionText": "PP5KYF010QCNOSSSVQ4FH4IBQK889NH5PW6I2CRNVSOWE5LFMH4QAOD97WHQDCDFCVXLCRALLFJO77O1Y80E", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "1.IAB62D89BYEA4YSXZ", "wrongAnswers": ["2.M06SCN0SDZMF53LWS77X401QY6QNEL60", "3.YTUOU49II8AMAWQIPLFTYS7"], "questionOptions": ["1.IAB62D89BYEA4YSXZ", "2.M06SCN0SDZMF53LWS77X401QY6QNEL60", "3.YTUOU49II8AMAWQIPLFTYS7"], "answerLink": "P4I0NP5607"}, {"questionId": 291, "questionText": "PCVTB6LBN1EO0W63MUKWYWET7YK74SGR6UMVAP3QYC1EBPV2KQROYSMCZ2GGB7R8HOGFMOU616WUT3CBSHHB0MF21SMSJ0UF93ZF29PUS4082OEVU26W", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "3.FJYNSMPTCITTD9HYQ48WYW4Z3LM406S", "wrongAnswers": ["1.SLB0PJZ4KGDCOSGGY3W2PFJ", "2.PS01X1IAIDBMS34YB65WMFY3"], "questionOptions": ["1.SLB0PJZ4KGDCOSGGY3W2PFJ", "2.PS01X1IAIDBMS34YB65WMFY3", "3.FJYNSMPTCITTD9HYQ48WYW4Z3LM406S"], "answerLink": "QGBKXBUQ10"}, {"questionId": 292, "questionText": "7ALAJF8B8VQF3RCCPAKTTQISFVANCZU5OPSBH0X1KDV8T5980RLJM1MY6YISPVM79G3SLPDPWWASA2WSLGZWNFE12VOV57AAHBWVSTDUZNXY7JG5N0PD9", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "3.2FYJ22H4LO2ULPOM5KZWEVVD10", "wrongAnswers": ["1.IIM0OXSZBLO1FGN8N6LVREHVIIYUCI8E", "2.18ZL1FO62B6PVIH912"], "questionOptions": ["1.IIM0OXSZBLO1FGN8N6LVREHVIIYUCI8E", "2.18ZL1FO62B6PVIH912", "3.2FYJ22H4LO2ULPOM5KZWEVVD10"], "answerLink": "03Y2EG3PQ7"}, {"questionId": 293, "questionText": "X50BX9GLHGUX92GSKJI82DDY8VDLUQAKZIF61N0W0PKABHJ78Y97KAJ5YENV7DMRALP15JQ0HAE4654EKR9SU896ZO4D2", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "2.GL197R52WVGKQXAMPCJ19G", "wrongAnswers": ["1.ZTP6S5AALJVDITCTCPQFN37ATMIM", "3.7R7MZ97UU9REE2J3"], "questionOptions": ["1.ZTP6S5AALJVDITCTCPQFN37ATMIM", "2.GL197R52WVGKQXAMPCJ19G", "3.7R7MZ97UU9REE2J3"], "answerLink": "FEJDGB43TH"}, {"questionId": 294, "questionText": "4UYUR9T17LG2HSABS6B55DO2RUSL09N3T6E4DMWI8I79DXT49CX8EJ45QW3YX06P9A38R94P1Y5CJNQSGC858IKTFIXS0KOUEYD9CGCNHAQWKI0B5D6FF", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "2.EPS4RZJ6QSGB6SF0QYRK5NVNHVG1FUT8", "wrongAnswers": ["1.LD32H22V58BBD3B7BLP22XRMHSCF", "3.U4EEC48OM49UOVIN9G5KKU7"], "questionOptions": ["1.LD32H22V58BBD3B7BLP22XRMHSCF", "2.EPS4RZJ6QSGB6SF0QYRK5NVNHVG1FUT8", "3.U4EEC48OM49UOVIN9G5KKU7"], "answerLink": "85H8LD8Z6X"}, {"questionId": 295, "questionText": "UR3BDVJWGY3CW3Y1C32AXO1YCOSBRQXC2M4Q43OOCCXUDXH9CW5XXPZ40BTVL6X08MSZOWVP4ERKVSGTMK80QDASGL60J6FI69139WMKD3H6FEZUOT8WF0T", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "3.XCLG4J3PPCUB0GY72SF5C4", "wrongAnswers": ["1.OIZ3SW8KL5P1JKQBTFU20J", "2.BUO77F1WUPKIN6QG89PY"], "questionOptions": ["1.OIZ3SW8KL5P1JKQBTFU20J", "2.BUO77F1WUPKIN6QG89PY", "3.XCLG4J3PPCUB0GY72SF5C4"], "answerLink": "B9G360YAB1"}, {"questionId": 296, "questionText": "0CJLRGU8XUQEKUMCDZAYX1WWVSL0FLYYO471ODRCRTLG67NVC8SL3377DAZC883CVWOUOBVRXV4B2BUT31C6QMVFLR1ZQE0YOXPF13XALSA1BQ4D2JA44DZ67HG", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "1.3NR7EMJKJ6GQK58TPWCO6UYZWT92", "wrongAnswers": ["2.6Y0GJM8LM6WNNU1M2YIV07J6UG8LZM", "3.O88JSILSPIWY2SH1M8Q82HBTQY"], "questionOptions": ["1.3NR7EMJKJ6GQK58TPWCO6UYZWT92", "2.6Y0GJM8LM6WNNU1M2YIV07J6UG8LZM", "3.O88JSILSPIWY2SH1M8Q82HBTQY"], "answerLink": "NMK3AU35EJ"}, {"questionId": 297, "questionText": "NKF6W7VYLVY5DME3JBPNVAZSXJQY75AJLPILFIVF7X50R0AK4HV7RJ3TXGZPJIV76O8M8XQ1CI9V5KARLAACPNQUPRORIXL", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "3.ZF1UTM6TY1GQGDSIHBC6KWMIHYG", "wrongAnswers": ["1.IKTFYNNG9XESN58SNN", "2.E3LSC29N9W1DYG5MS23QT"], "questionOptions": ["1.IKTFYNNG9XESN58SNN", "2.E3LSC29N9W1DYG5MS23QT", "3.ZF1UTM6TY1GQGDSIHBC6KWMIHYG"], "answerLink": "SEU7SZH9W1"}, {"questionId": 298, "questionText": "CQBELQ5QO7IPIQR4TQ7JSHA46D95C2XT7YQ18U5QR1QY7N3PTLP0GHLJVJ57Q7E11YRTM4D0ZZP2ILLBNOECVH7BBL55N1QGX", "questionCategory": "Regola 8", "correctAnswers": "1.8FYX5OQE25TAOGBZ22GZQ69", "wrongAnswers": ["2.QJV1I72T9EG3OQYKJZACHR7J", "3.4FSEBQ1VQ3PPIG6FFR0T8JELK"], "questionOptions": ["1.8FYX5OQE25TAOGBZ22GZQ69", "2.QJV1I72T9EG3OQYKJZACHR7J", "3.4FSEBQ1VQ3PPIG6FFR0T8JELK"], "answerLink": "Y1VJM4PZ81"}, {"questionId": 299, "questionText": "HL0U7VXKEWUWWVCUTWVYM3WK2B5VVYPKSNIGA8U9X54FAQE1MR8L0136VOCQ0QLOS9I7S", "questionCategory": "Regola 9", "correctAnswers": "1.R8WFPCLD6TFSBLYLI3786BQ2", "wrongAnswers": ["2.OS3SP0KE8BVA6LQR120", "3.58A2GP0ZO0531HUUD8I9G19N"], "questionOptions": ["1.R8WFPCLD6TFSBLYLI3786BQ2", "2.OS3SP0KE8BVA6LQR120", "3.58A2GP0ZO0531HUUD8I9G19N"], "answerLink": "75D1W2V1F4"}, {"questionId": 300, "questionText": "EPSC35B62K89AE7FGWM0IIBI3U3UXG9SDOTDP5AP2O5RV33GAX41VJMDN20MQYBZ7I85KROY78SGYC1RNSNHMTPIEK7291JGMG", "questionCategory": "Regola 9", "correctAnswers": "2.LPS36MA3AFZGC9FB74G5SQGR", "wrongAnswers": ["1.Z593KV842HTRMTAP", "3.KJSTIUZDDEDROQBYR3AYZ"], "questionOptions": ["1.Z593KV842HTRMTAP", "2.LPS36MA3AFZGC9FB74G5SQGR", "3.KJSTIUZDDEDROQBYR3AYZ"], "answerLink": "55GUBA0ALT"}, {"questionId": 301, "questionText": "0LLNVONFBTM6L0BXFQMWTD4K9Z6X73D61CYSP820H0ESLFDFBRO1KE1QSROYIV7P4CMRTNETRRGSXRXUY9NQCT67H6T77E5JVHJE602R89U", "questionCategory": "Regola 9", "correctAnswers": "3.GBEJPM15M0G2J9I3", "wrongAnswers": ["1.MXWT6ADA2NJGEHTGBWMXV7", "2.5RAGJUAJAAML1M6TFXDHN6V26BHKFDV"], "questionOptions": ["1.MXWT6ADA2NJGEHTGBWMXV7", "2.5RAGJUAJAAML1M6TFXDHN6V26BHKFDV", "3.GBEJPM15M0G2J9I3"], "answerLink": "URHLIUG72B"}, {"questionId": 302, "questionText": "OVG5YO7249C2ELIYYQQ98KB028QQAKEGP538EF7640PWFND3PU2GIF5MHHSRP2XMMG8XXJLNMH0U0HV6SSX7RCUYB4TK0QWGNH", "questionCategory": "Regola 9", "correctAnswers": "1.QZZ180Z7BWZ03793L9NTIOUYVG20QT", "wrongAnswers": ["2.21HBU4MRVT94XR63IJFG2", "3.7KT5FXHDDJIK7SHQ04ZUVIRC"], "questionOptions": ["1.QZZ180Z7BWZ03793L9NTIOUYVG20QT", "2.21HBU4MRVT94XR63IJFG2", "3.7KT5FXHDDJIK7SHQ04ZUVIRC"], "answerLink": "XSR2T8ODL4"}, {"questionId": 303, "questionText": "OUE5YNFHAJTREK947A5E3TJ1RK0JDWZGJ1R402NDE52YGSHA1TZFVD6JBG719LB3W9FYY2PXHWYJDTK9MGWJUNC5J61NF5MGMB4U8", "questionCategory": "Regola 9", "correctAnswers": "1.P14L1H5OG0W346Q2WJ", "wrongAnswers": ["2.IQV8OEFE2GZ98O5U83U", "3.5BT3Q3I17RYKR3SXM5X8K9DMGG"], "questionOptions": ["1.P14L1H5OG0W346Q2WJ", "2.IQV8OEFE2GZ98O5U83U", "3.5BT3Q3I17RYKR3SXM5X8K9DMGG"], "answerLink": "78GQM6A552"}, {"questionId": 304, "questionText": "WZRGNA39Q59AX248N2YBHYCJFKFROORFA4VY4S98R52VY2SK4KIZBX5SCFQYOFN0R6CXO", "questionCategory": "Regola 9", "correctAnswers": "2.NBWMT6IIQA8J04LLBKRPA6WYX", "wrongAnswers": ["1.3DVT7PYSY8ALH9BM6UXMOL3QWBM", "3.SRRBTPTJBKJY1AV8NF3"], "questionOptions": ["1.3DVT7PYSY8ALH9BM6UXMOL3QWBM", "2.NBWMT6IIQA8J04LLBKRPA6WYX", "3.SRRBTPTJBKJY1AV8NF3"], "answerLink": "1DN1SPHYX3"}, {"questionId": 305, "questionText": "MC48BJZN9QQH5238MWIK6TA5093TW19L1GZ91NAAYZBXE1853FS5UQ9UAKY0YQBZN6QP505LF3IUNXIZ4CFQJ5XHZI", "questionCategory": "Regola 9", "correctAnswers": "1.QRJQEQ1ERWZL3AEFI6F", "wrongAnswers": ["2.XIQBP19F9EQW9AQTK6L7S3N7S4VTYU", "3.F9V80XIG1TF84EZADIY1QSDNN"], "questionOptions": ["1.QRJQEQ1ERWZL3AEFI6F", "2.XIQBP19F9EQW9AQTK6L7S3N7S4VTYU", "3.F9V80XIG1TF84EZADIY1QSDNN"], "answerLink": "2SHP9NT61W"}, {"questionId": 306, "questionText": "H5V0I31ZO09X5IRVOWTJ7DBVKEOFIYHWT44MYN52X26P53FREAMN4NK1S0RM6CNQZABV9MPLEREZSA13OF9LA3PU7QN78QQ3BIUU1K7LKH7B6DIA5S10ZPP4VTEQ2M", "questionCategory": "Regola 9", "correctAnswers": "1.4G24MO2T9F3X6TAEVR745XOGTELNGW", "wrongAnswers": ["2.CAZNSBPGN209UQAYDP7NST9R", "3.OQD6ALM7RKLB9MOJ1"], "questionOptions": ["1.4G24MO2T9F3X6TAEVR745XOGTELNGW", "2.CAZNSBPGN209UQAYDP7NST9R", "3.OQD6ALM7RKLB9MOJ1"], "answerLink": "EGLDI8VGM2"}, {"questionId": 307, "questionText": "FVBZ08T97UE00617SFV96RMN51IDK3S50M7ADUNEP08LPGGMIH4L8WQ4I8GQX4Y0Q5FHGPH02WARIO2QBILVKE5KY83RBYMP3J6Z6N99LWSO343IA0", "questionCategory": "Regola 9", "correctAnswers": "1.XWL9LW4VZ6RRTEIGFJMLW14MY16J", "wrongAnswers": ["2.HVBPW4CC0QGYKNEXHBORJAB8QE3B", "3.ONJ1JMEPLWS39NNU"], "questionOptions": ["1.XWL9LW4VZ6RRTEIGFJMLW14MY16J", "2.HVBPW4CC0QGYKNEXHBORJAB8QE3B", "3.ONJ1JMEPLWS39NNU"], "answerLink": "3JWSIA5JPX"}, {"questionId": 308, "questionText": "EWEKA058WNE3YT8K6CBHR7WMV46DF4X9EIWOECUDYMXTNQ9MTDU1R084CBEV47CTPKLGS8IAASEZZU", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "3.SA8CBJG4NKEPYTBPL9RRF3", "wrongAnswers": ["1.4LM5EE79P6ZJQT8CD", "2.CCZINKABE5NNJRTITVE124"], "questionOptions": ["1.4LM5EE79P6ZJQT8CD", "2.CCZINKABE5NNJRTITVE124", "3.SA8CBJG4NKEPYTBPL9RRF3"], "answerLink": "1UOHU6X4N3"}, {"questionId": 309, "questionText": "VFRUVI83CDB75YWJHXOFRSSDDQSQ52U57IBB97ENN5Q4N1GFT7MQYJJA4SW8S5MZZ6723SD39VXS1KXMKFK31BJ358J7C2", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "1.IV1U3OAGFHGK0L3N6UR9K4ICR7BH", "wrongAnswers": ["2.CKANDSTZMVKKHDDO1HHPMYAGRQL", "3.S0X1AXLQK19ZY9FMEJ7QVRVI42A"], "questionOptions": ["1.IV1U3OAGFHGK0L3N6UR9K4ICR7BH", "2.CKANDSTZMVKKHDDO1HHPMYAGRQL", "3.S0X1AXLQK19ZY9FMEJ7QVRVI42A"], "answerLink": "45T92CZTM3"}, {"questionId": 310, "questionText": "X6JZMAX6PAPZWC1FOUG4ASG3GDTZ1UG6XHTDUNM5S8Q8A8QCYEYWUSID7P59IOWZBEY14S3Z8XMBY3ZLNFJOFGULFGSH5Q17CA4GAMKSRCZOOTO", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "3.WCDNNOD5LKWDCD9IPZQ6CXNEHG1", "wrongAnswers": ["1.970ZJP6G3UCC3V8359XW8YB0F3VC", "2.H9G2ZEOOMQGJ96MMSRK2I"], "questionOptions": ["1.970ZJP6G3UCC3V8359XW8YB0F3VC", "2.H9G2ZEOOMQGJ96MMSRK2I", "3.WCDNNOD5LKWDCD9IPZQ6CXNEHG1"], "answerLink": "XSTMJ59D3N"}, {"questionId": 311, "questionText": "4U5QJH6F3CNN94C2HHX7P19GUWCG7KNMUUBLJHJAJEB5WI6LP7GN8RLKHGN76TOHNEDW5YZKFC2XOR7G0RMYZIUT14238ZYCXDL9QMUIMGK5WCTB4", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "1.A4GQ3V5U3SCHIYHHRSYVHOU3OM8F2E", "wrongAnswers": ["2.7IE7TIIEKO1N32XME69DDQHYGZ7EO", "3.RPDD8GGEK6L3B1WLF376CMFUV"], "questionOptions": ["1.A4GQ3V5U3SCHIYHHRSYVHOU3OM8F2E", "2.7IE7TIIEKO1N32XME69DDQHYGZ7EO", "3.RPDD8GGEK6L3B1WLF376CMFUV"], "answerLink": "F6ZI4HS1YR"}, {"questionId": 312, "questionText": "QVMX9MY942Z7Y7T0FKJHFOYZ3GOA00KPHT6X2V73KYMDA4F78DUTYZMG8T1EMQRX9J208U2QRZTQCNW6HCS759MHMDMI1K68U2LIDQPOB1M0JX0T5T6TV", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "1.ZP3U0T5R7ZDF1LF6Q65", "wrongAnswers": ["2.J9JKLDJUNQBOG3IEINNEDSAUBLOU", "3.8AC2F0VYC38JLHQO"], "questionOptions": ["1.ZP3U0T5R7ZDF1LF6Q65", "2.J9JKLDJUNQBOG3IEINNEDSAUBLOU", "3.8AC2F0VYC38JLHQO"], "answerLink": "WPRSQQS9Q9"}, {"questionId": 313, "questionText": "DSFZZCHP0VALANB5UVOKELOMYHBVKIDQTBE3U8RD5UE2OA39JOPK8T808L61328GT662KX2ZH6JDYCWDDJNARKVYG76XTY974PN", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "3.Q7HF2VFWE9C6SQJS8DKIAZORJ8CG", "wrongAnswers": ["1.IMMKB82Y8WFCFX5FRVBR1MZKA5O", "2.BVENCV7V4NYK434M7X99TGM"], "questionOptions": ["1.IMMKB82Y8WFCFX5FRVBR1MZKA5O", "2.BVENCV7V4NYK434M7X99TGM", "3.Q7HF2VFWE9C6SQJS8DKIAZORJ8CG"], "answerLink": "O5D6OYRDTG"}, {"questionId": 314, "questionText": "MJD2M7OVGAAY2PU7889FEDZRIMVMOUOOV74NAQJE9D3538EI3F3GN9D71XHSWO8O5PRRP91NWIBENTB58C5EA80LIA26LYQ40QW8FKZ", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "1.O8RUYLVE8JFSHDL6SMUT5", "wrongAnswers": ["2.VV8QDBUH8YTZ983HMK3R7K46R", "3.UT9SZFQB2A4PZZF8ZN0Q8DW1KQZ4IP"], "questionOptions": ["1.O8RUYLVE8JFSHDL6SMUT5", "2.VV8QDBUH8YTZ983HMK3R7K46R", "3.UT9SZFQB2A4PZZF8ZN0Q8DW1KQZ4IP"], "answerLink": "E7JIATPS8I"}, {"questionId": 315, "questionText": "EY790YBN0WXEF5CA6Z96DCRRLD9ZKU55H9XYLU56F6PS0A76HJ69KV1FUL9JWN4CJ754FRPQ4PGDZLDOPY6RQNIDOVX70MSQ02JIPYLCHHI0", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "3.7YZCBCKDHLNBYBQ2EV2", "wrongAnswers": ["1.MBBOOWKB7B6FZ3PJ21RJ84LE5CTK", "2.U7S85S16ATPBZ7WW41O2W48Q7YPQ"], "questionOptions": ["1.MBBOOWKB7B6FZ3PJ21RJ84LE5CTK", "2.U7S85S16ATPBZ7WW41O2W48Q7YPQ", "3.7YZCBCKDHLNBYBQ2EV2"], "answerLink": "S9XMW8CVB9"}, {"questionId": 316, "questionText": "7XPLKHUDLAPXQAOVWRI40TZW6XT41TLHCYCJ0MD9CVOCB547E9PFO2DKVIKS099ABQYIFY765JP7NCVTVOOB7XOJVNKOD8E4DZF54W45FPZMNQ8GV", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "2.43UMD4PN6BHW4UR75OF18", "wrongAnswers": ["1.OJN0Z588UOI3B4LZ", "3.FTMB4EQSOICBJQIPJ8KU1NMREK9KME"], "questionOptions": ["1.OJN0Z588UOI3B4LZ", "2.43UMD4PN6BHW4UR75OF18", "3.FTMB4EQSOICBJQIPJ8KU1NMREK9KME"], "answerLink": "7FAJP8BV15"}, {"questionId": 317, "questionText": "EMPLHI42TR13O2EIQMQZ43LQ90TIAT5FH1LOGQORYXKDAR78TPYMQES5Z4FE2MSN32X5AXFK8K87PM2HPRSTLP2X0LJB", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "1.Z97SPB7UESGG6WQ3FL", "wrongAnswers": ["2.BLH84ZAN2F493JGK4MPJYZM35HWJ4K8M", "3.0UJFK9UZT27L6ET441DAD1QSQKICHF5"], "questionOptions": ["1.Z97SPB7UESGG6WQ3FL", "2.BLH84ZAN2F493JGK4MPJYZM35HWJ4K8M", "3.0UJFK9UZT27L6ET441DAD1QSQKICHF5"], "answerLink": "8NN46B8Y9A"}, {"questionId": 318, "questionText": "LM8LN4DWZHZ08JXUQIC2E39OQMBZAJLWNGFOUETWAL5D0MZIW56QWYARJUM4CDG72TCGXRY55G7NUXO3XRX", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "1.O9E3ENN6U1EQE2HNXGSBRB2EX70", "wrongAnswers": ["2.MUJ8J2TTKXM5OTFPCT8CAC92IJG", "3.YP2HCIYHAOS1ISROZQWKNI84PBB"], "questionOptions": ["1.O9E3ENN6U1EQE2HNXGSBRB2EX70", "2.MUJ8J2TTKXM5OTFPCT8CAC92IJG", "3.YP2HCIYHAOS1ISROZQWKNI84PBB"], "answerLink": "TP25KDSSR7"}, {"questionId": 319, "questionText": "X8OHNBUYAFT22ISJQP4N6SS7TBNR9OIGLC33G83DA9J2SL30PPUKKFWXRAHP3DI43S6FPVLBS3DY50EOP778V1EYGEYH93L", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "3.ZVYTPOYF0NXX5C2NTJNL03TQ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.VBEPX5A0IA95ZG6I4UPURJ3BVD8", "2.ZNATIC1JBFJYRJ10"], "questionOptions": ["1.VBEPX5A0IA95ZG6I4UPURJ3BVD8", "2.ZNATIC1JBFJYRJ10", "3.ZVYTPOYF0NXX5C2NTJNL03TQ"], "answerLink": "OQR6MPV786"}, {"questionId": 320, "questionText": "2DWJZ2BUVE2L8RAG3ZKZHE9TGTPQTN7XPR78FNHHFB40EVQZ4RC47MGVQMSMIWAWCACFX4OO5B84JXMBOX79KBOWH6MSZFJJRE1RPB17E3OM818YW7YHT", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "2.JLGCQTVFMFMVUM8TZ6P6JB2RYKZMDA0", "wrongAnswers": ["1.A326UWCQXAPMFXT6SI", "3.BG2J2FAETJ3CJG20FY0"], "questionOptions": ["1.A326UWCQXAPMFXT6SI", "2.JLGCQTVFMFMVUM8TZ6P6JB2RYKZMDA0", "3.BG2J2FAETJ3CJG20FY0"], "answerLink": "9N3GS0ALAX"}, {"questionId": 321, "questionText": "SG850AW1Z9MKPZZTTPDQTE6K9BV3YQ8MP3M6JUC0SPC69ROHKXVONQYH681BMOOSJHPQTHWU9DYIPI08BSLOG6L1FHKUXD9MKVBSG8W0EI86Z1EULCVY3Q5", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "2.LOBC8XXIC5719HBGG40Z71AY", "wrongAnswers": ["1.4VY234WONMS8ONE47BL", "3.2RT2D8MIYQ27W9HQ"], "questionOptions": ["1.4VY234WONMS8ONE47BL", "2.LOBC8XXIC5719HBGG40Z71AY", "3.2RT2D8MIYQ27W9HQ"], "answerLink": "B7VOQN2FUW"}, {"questionId": 322, "questionText": "4GOCFAY6EG5KDYTO1SZ2CN4XKFZ19C4XPBJ8GMPDRQ5A2YF5FDKYI5RFGB71BIDA07H601KDF8WIQLDPKS4IBG", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "1.KUTYRDU7L0NNKX59HPNMV4B99RV", "wrongAnswers": ["2.6NM1OBGMYGUTFJS2QGQAWRZ1XI2FUZ", "3.G266110OV9DKIF2MKLTPOK"], "questionOptions": ["1.KUTYRDU7L0NNKX59HPNMV4B99RV", "2.6NM1OBGMYGUTFJS2QGQAWRZ1XI2FUZ", "3.G266110OV9DKIF2MKLTPOK"], "answerLink": "WIQOV0G80L"}, {"questionId": 323, "questionText": "N4SXDTANDW0JSQN6HQUQLIH5S8TKR0QZIQC89EBYUN71K1BWBJ0WIRST0R6E71ZZTXAWFGMCM9KRBWS6", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "2.DMX9RYEM0PEVLYU0U1L67YIT3ZL", "wrongAnswers": ["1.TML4SLHT137F25R5B8MQ906HI1PAS79", "3.L6KXJG8U74OMIPOYDWJ6Z8M2F7FL0HCJ"], "questionOptions": ["1.TML4SLHT137F25R5B8MQ906HI1PAS79", "2.DMX9RYEM0PEVLYU0U1L67YIT3ZL", "3.L6KXJG8U74OMIPOYDWJ6Z8M2F7FL0HCJ"], "answerLink": "SHZJPCNRCV"}, {"questionId": 324, "questionText": "G0U0GAFTATGGZFD48B3G7Q7GWTFRBLPHIIJK4EZX9D2E1JE3FI6K3VBXEO89T7TR0V", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "2.UJLO1Z83979HUZY7B8MOQU9LM", "wrongAnswers": ["1.K2F3PLA3SNM3WUZ9NNO7Y549OAIJZ", "3.XH4T4QQMWGS1IIYECQUPIFTJ58SAB3UC"], "questionOptions": ["1.K2F3PLA3SNM3WUZ9NNO7Y549OAIJZ", "2.UJLO1Z83979HUZY7B8MOQU9LM", "3.XH4T4QQMWGS1IIYECQUPIFTJ58SAB3UC"], "answerLink": "ZTAP746FYE"}, {"questionId": 325, "questionText": "V50EXQLOY068X8OXK1Q5AAQY9J7XIIJ9M3GEHLQMYEDV9J7MHJG4551Y4PNYFUG1ZKETUO6CB41QLH5X6IM3QX0O8V5HVBDHUYTNJ0Q8JN0KX9JUTZ1TTFM87V2XRPO", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "1.5O2PEBNOU3SJWJH9Z2BRACI3", "wrongAnswers": ["2.9ELJCEDPTRUB9M411YDYRDO2H5S3", "3.1ZIYFE2ZVJ32CQUSP3YNT1YP1SU3"], "questionOptions": ["1.5O2PEBNOU3SJWJH9Z2BRACI3", "2.9ELJCEDPTRUB9M411YDYRDO2H5S3", "3.1ZIYFE2ZVJ32CQUSP3YNT1YP1SU3"], "answerLink": "R4VVUQ21JP"}, {"questionId": 326, "questionText": "3IOG6WUY0WHNOB5OUR2XS0MT0S9P9L4G02MC7VAWBRZ1DZK7PZO6AOYHOVP94D0V3MXHY1TKXDNRBN92", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "1.YMS52PAX1L25NYA6THDWLB", "wrongAnswers": ["2.STMW8YWLIYLDHWGOO074DVFFSQA4TJ", "3.A8D6RN4GHAZXWLV3TH"], "questionOptions": ["1.YMS52PAX1L25NYA6THDWLB", "2.STMW8YWLIYLDHWGOO074DVFFSQA4TJ", "3.A8D6RN4GHAZXWLV3TH"], "answerLink": "HAUMUDKQ2A"}, {"questionId": 327, "questionText": "5R1IADN2Z9M3W0ZLLWQPTWYI6EO3UCWE8E34V6RRNSNF9D0QR76N988J97PTEMJ1EELXNMSUIJM0UPEV1ESK34216UIWOWQMQRSM", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "2.OYHYPMIG0SBX14U3HQA836BSLVMN7", "wrongAnswers": ["1.A1HSZB54W6UEIO52SI2VAA1TK407JS", "3.N8IZ13X470Y71IIWF0BZ2W6"], "questionOptions": ["1.A1HSZB54W6UEIO52SI2VAA1TK407JS", "2.OYHYPMIG0SBX14U3HQA836BSLVMN7", "3.N8IZ13X470Y71IIWF0BZ2W6"], "answerLink": "MZS2HIO9KL"}, {"questionId": 328, "questionText": "JTR5GS1IQJQQ8NTVHHAIPZMY60OA36Q7Y3AKORXERMVR3M3UVFYGMUAI5WSYS2Z25VYY2EOKQKYA4ZMMCLN1ZONA9AXRHQ1HH", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "1.PJFUAI4IV24PL13RZ", "wrongAnswers": ["2.WHUHINL18COAQ76JZ7EH5I", "3.N8MIPMB8SZVNW6J17SVXI7P0WPM28"], "questionOptions": ["1.PJFUAI4IV24PL13RZ", "2.WHUHINL18COAQ76JZ7EH5I", "3.N8MIPMB8SZVNW6J17SVXI7P0WPM28"], "answerLink": "H0ZGZ4BNZN"}, {"questionId": 329, "questionText": "E4G9KOMO8UY2BL2PTEEAHG3JI1ID6OMZEL5Y96V0FSFWRCHODKZN21ETVNJ4LKC4848QCSX5DKIVTI", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "1.VDM599DIFIXGXLEWM31Y", "wrongAnswers": ["2.6C6HHAGGKTY28RLH287ES7", "3.KSJK87IHMTAZ24R9HYDQPCJ5XC6JVAI"], "questionOptions": ["1.VDM599DIFIXGXLEWM31Y", "2.6C6HHAGGKTY28RLH287ES7", "3.KSJK87IHMTAZ24R9HYDQPCJ5XC6JVAI"], "answerLink": "HFTEBXNE9Z"}, {"questionId": 330, "questionText": "C1G6634JU1U9UKCP0PQXJUWD6VGSMBCUHM4XA0ZVOYL8QP890F5LEAP7E4VY6O06FH4M", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "1.DJKAU938GUC9JL2VQ1EWNAYDK8I6O", "wrongAnswers": ["2.PI9GMT44POXMKDETEGJIWR0L8", "3.6YG7EUBLXRRB8F3ESRSF54"], "questionOptions": ["1.DJKAU938GUC9JL2VQ1EWNAYDK8I6O", "2.PI9GMT44POXMKDETEGJIWR0L8", "3.6YG7EUBLXRRB8F3ESRSF54"], "answerLink": "X576GSSIRF"}, {"questionId": 331, "questionText": "7BDL8JYVW08U28QEVFB3679W7HNK8J3VQWGH8BHUTP95FYZR2ZHDEKBTYE0J5S0FI17TSS6DPR8FHAAATD07CKNBQ1G1WJNVB7UTXZ2YEK9W0", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "1.PE8O18Y45F28M2HI0YICUB", "wrongAnswers": ["2.PPOLADQIS3NCS2D9GITG6UO9RN99QW", "3.4EMNXT07DKGTYYNI0V0UDQ"], "questionOptions": ["1.PE8O18Y45F28M2HI0YICUB", "2.PPOLADQIS3NCS2D9GITG6UO9RN99QW", "3.4EMNXT07DKGTYYNI0V0UDQ"], "answerLink": "VL9VTIHJ0P"}, {"questionId": 332, "questionText": "OTYGECPC6M428ZP0EPTTGTI0LJZ3U5TALQRXFON71JYOU0YJEGC443VMZSSD7JRKRL2P4KAOE1LSDJ9UPJTCVVFJTQDHPAXCEBTL3OB8", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "2.HPUOHBSAFX4TTHH1OX", "wrongAnswers": ["1.MLSPXCGW52BJ7XN4BA3R11", "3.NN27KN733PVWYBE9T27T5A0"], "questionOptions": ["1.MLSPXCGW52BJ7XN4BA3R11", "2.HPUOHBSAFX4TTHH1OX", "3.NN27KN733PVWYBE9T27T5A0"], "answerLink": "TLK95ZN9E8"}, {"questionId": 333, "questionText": "2UW9GRY02WDVGH3Z89V5CNX165WLU0BN7IB31XYYAWHX3TTWG80HUKI7470W9IEI13B5EB7188JVD91693RLZ6N", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "2.6S3KWF65MQAMQA8T2SNGGMOQVHTN1", "wrongAnswers": ["1.MAAOJ37DLC68J9CNRTXKYMS0", "3.7QC5KN043PGP13X9SA2HICIDWWPDHNC"], "questionOptions": ["1.MAAOJ37DLC68J9CNRTXKYMS0", "2.6S3KWF65MQAMQA8T2SNGGMOQVHTN1", "3.7QC5KN043PGP13X9SA2HICIDWWPDHNC"], "answerLink": "UJU74RMIF9"}, {"questionId": 334, "questionText": "V7DOZEDLFLHTQ2YQ0THGKHO3D6FZZ74T15U36BTEV908RJ0Y64L0SIWJ7E9GNSW4KZDX3TE921WRUD0515XCG1", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "2.4N4GBKWMOJXZMVGE", "wrongAnswers": ["1.9SF3OVCM4BWUCRBWCDDVO8R45", "3.CH2QCJJOTBPBV56L77H2R7B19B4DYJK7"], "questionOptions": ["1.9SF3OVCM4BWUCRBWCDDVO8R45", "2.4N4GBKWMOJXZMVGE", "3.CH2QCJJOTBPBV56L77H2R7B19B4DYJK7"], "answerLink": "F9H131APCH"}, {"questionId": 335, "questionText": "VR1BTUGD9GFN0UN5R1ZK0H3EJ3EB99FUS7KUF41OMWIQZCL795W000AWZPLYCEHEQQWUDEORRYEL9L0JQVMFX", "questionCategory": "Regola 10", "correctAnswers": "3.VEXFSQYNFVZQAZ82RH0H1J50JWD6", "wrongAnswers": ["1.SNSQGQNE14GX2ULN31MX", "2.PF4HO1AEBFYC9SYOIQP3AHFGGEPF"], "questionOptions": ["1.SNSQGQNE14GX2ULN31MX", "2.PF4HO1AEBFYC9SYOIQP3AHFGGEPF", "3.VEXFSQYNFVZQAZ82RH0H1J50JWD6"], "answerLink": "ZLMJPOZW8P"}, {"questionId": 336, "questionText": "KYLBYJ6BNSTR37I5XEU9YFMYYQU33UFTG8KSZ88ISLKE5PCYLN1SL7PZUY4YC2BYZJELS5U1SI5KXWP1MG21YDNXM9VGUXP5TQC", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "2.B9L7PKY2P72BQOJY4VM2EXOXFUI", "wrongAnswers": ["1.XUMZ9LW7URXM4H1A5AYIIP", "3.ZJ1VNQ2KSA7CC1VSDVVMB"], "questionOptions": ["1.XUMZ9LW7URXM4H1A5AYIIP", "2.B9L7PKY2P72BQOJY4VM2EXOXFUI", "3.ZJ1VNQ2KSA7CC1VSDVVMB"], "answerLink": "YOMYZZ2VMR"}, {"questionId": 337, "questionText": "NOTZDN83VS340HS4X6VITSBDM124HKHCJIRLB08Y85ZL6HDD4U0RJZNXO8U90QD127M25QN8SD", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "2.TP0568DURBPLECU1IWUL", "wrongAnswers": ["1.WPZ2C5OEF18X17GPZA5NZV9", "3.FET3WF4O58XSNY53J9N"], "questionOptions": ["1.WPZ2C5OEF18X17GPZA5NZV9", "2.TP0568DURBPLECU1IWUL", "3.FET3WF4O58XSNY53J9N"], "answerLink": "VCFLSBS7U7"}, {"questionId": 338, "questionText": "K95FGJXKYVWY593DPYVZH0HX8BE2BK8XV52BGJKLYJ1RGYYE1J00GKANF5PD4HEUKA1H0L2M65GSI9PR8OPI3ERJ", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "1.0ULJOTR2RXSXJQD7EUYH3JZAX", "wrongAnswers": ["2.0IU729HDDD8JL671G175D0RIOKPYCJ", "3.H7VMK945BMROJUMNW"], "questionOptions": ["1.0ULJOTR2RXSXJQD7EUYH3JZAX", "2.0IU729HDDD8JL671G175D0RIOKPYCJ", "3.H7VMK945BMROJUMNW"], "answerLink": "LFAH9MOLR1"}, {"questionId": 339, "questionText": "2JIAWGET5WZ05QVUS7BPBTF3YYG1HFXEKCUFPK68RWEKGHA4XL9272CGN09XAKIN6IJIQ2ZS", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "3.M55SXEWEF0ERH47FLQ9XSRNS8HW9C1", "wrongAnswers": ["1.PC9CV8CD86I37K5C1QR8YCA31E5J9RL", "2.9GBL2NGKEA6L2D29U5EIF6VZN7C9"], "questionOptions": ["1.PC9CV8CD86I37K5C1QR8YCA31E5J9RL", "2.9GBL2NGKEA6L2D29U5EIF6VZN7C9", "3.M55SXEWEF0ERH47FLQ9XSRNS8HW9C1"], "answerLink": "4QB1G74KHK"}, {"questionId": 340, "questionText": "VGK422Q3VHWEFJDQ18G6TMIJG81WCI1YOZMXGEMCCGZW1DB8EU1GQJSAM5HXEKBJMV7HCN033QBEAC9VM2I9PKW7LTIA1KA40LX5BQ9BGEP0V57ANQ7F91G", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "2.J4VE39KOTRQ0D313GLDRYIY", "wrongAnswers": ["1.ISDIRV5C7PJB69KIIKD", "3.5MHR3YDA2TATXKQ22FQXQY0"], "questionOptions": ["1.ISDIRV5C7PJB69KIIKD", "2.J4VE39KOTRQ0D313GLDRYIY", "3.5MHR3YDA2TATXKQ22FQXQY0"], "answerLink": "2QBPDKS481"}, {"questionId": 341, "questionText": "8IARWB43L2D06FOBE8QGRG8UAPCXLYUJ73FRLYFSLQMDJLGVIP0983N2K5ISYTXIVX9Y4W5LX0R2QM05X8R", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "2.LWU6LYUR5Q0ZCG0KJ7Q9H8T0WSV", "wrongAnswers": ["1.YN0KRBKIGEGL5DROCW3", "3.8IK8AJXEG84RYVD33RGXSDT68HDV0"], "questionOptions": ["1.YN0KRBKIGEGL5DROCW3", "2.LWU6LYUR5Q0ZCG0KJ7Q9H8T0WSV", "3.8IK8AJXEG84RYVD33RGXSDT68HDV0"], "answerLink": "AZUIXYC3TH"}, {"questionId": 342, "questionText": "HUVHV9SBVM61C0JUOFFGLR6900Q1IYCE1TAOLQDXOSW902CORT27A2FNRLNQ8M9OMQH3LG0ULHV99PD9DJB", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "3.YLAWYO98D1LIFSD8304", "wrongAnswers": ["1.KNO9WOW63C0I630SVUWAICT", "2.DJ9KPGRUS9WU9SSCZOUZZI3Q6IV"], "questionOptions": ["1.KNO9WOW63C0I630SVUWAICT", "2.DJ9KPGRUS9WU9SSCZOUZZI3Q6IV", "3.YLAWYO98D1LIFSD8304"], "answerLink": "V1MRKL39AR"}, {"questionId": 343, "questionText": "7PMOFJPJLCFQNIY2OS66TB70XSLWVCOLFWM1ZNU3KPUC7J1571CAOWWT7J6A3T5NYF3FGPB0IC8H2E3DR4B13XN06AAAA", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "1.N9OBFKYUR6OAGRP0", "wrongAnswers": ["2.XIOKXBXYVOTHR2LK6D8LDSY4L4MQ", "3.VTHBOEYH6WDM1H4OPUFU456TNN0R7C"], "questionOptions": ["1.N9OBFKYUR6OAGRP0", "2.XIOKXBXYVOTHR2LK6D8LDSY4L4MQ", "3.VTHBOEYH6WDM1H4OPUFU456TNN0R7C"], "answerLink": "B1FCMW9KGB"}, {"questionId": 344, "questionText": "7BA4HEDWVCK803DNZU8M4XAD86LG83ZTJRYDVW4USRWT10DEKXQ2VSI5ZZNJGQ3O3PGL2AACN3K454M7W3ZTF6P36WZUH35PC7V7P", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "1.I98XQ0K2KNIVJL92YY6S", "wrongAnswers": ["2.QLVYFRZJX5UJD0F3R4DLTZH", "3.WK7CHG1AC2XAA56PGPI"], "questionOptions": ["1.I98XQ0K2KNIVJL92YY6S", "2.QLVYFRZJX5UJD0F3R4DLTZH", "3.WK7CHG1AC2XAA56PGPI"], "answerLink": "5PDKCP0SJZ"}, {"questionId": 345, "questionText": "LUZZ1141Q7M31U5J3CXTDLII82NPGE2O6VJ7G0A7UJNJLSGWPXU354N2E8BL31CVDL6CMUCN7ADB1D19Y2QHJUQK935XQ47BW47T6YDGVY49QAUH3ANLNL8Z8ZVOUA", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "1.OJ2D4UDHA4MXFGC56QA8ML5V5H18I", "wrongAnswers": ["2.HQME3ZFHIELFKOTFAMYQ461DENGNXR8U", "3.C07SDTID55LVUZBNSAXM2"], "questionOptions": ["1.OJ2D4UDHA4MXFGC56QA8ML5V5H18I", "2.HQME3ZFHIELFKOTFAMYQ461DENGNXR8U", "3.C07SDTID55LVUZBNSAXM2"], "answerLink": "J139FLT8D5"}, {"questionId": 346, "questionText": "UYFMZDA6OPGGN527X9T54TIJJY41BYXHE0H03FCIQB7693WEW6T9SA0PB0Y4Z03L9TXZWXAVW8BSGMSG854ARBYRY9AR4JKYM0BHMLIG62", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "2.XSPSKNTP88DXMUMF7ZIUF4668RM", "wrongAnswers": ["1.6PYOZODT84R6N40JU", "3.18TS2MHSJNR4HISTZ"], "questionOptions": ["1.6PYOZODT84R6N40JU", "2.XSPSKNTP88DXMUMF7ZIUF4668RM", "3.18TS2MHSJNR4HISTZ"], "answerLink": "8JLYOCO632"}, {"questionId": 347, "questionText": "LHLUI62VC5NNQ0OYS51VJGE0YIGRORYN2OI4Q1J84LS1W22VUOZY9H71ELXL3353FLV6ARDCOCBX9ZIM8MTZORCIQZ01FXF8NDCQM38GBEZR6DYG6UG9", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "1.RKC3X2W92JHZ2HJW2YV0", "wrongAnswers": ["2.0M39QW1CY30IRZIXUQJP", "3.SWGQ4D8PAOB2K34KPLFU0KJDK"], "questionOptions": ["1.RKC3X2W92JHZ2HJW2YV0", "2.0M39QW1CY30IRZIXUQJP", "3.SWGQ4D8PAOB2K34KPLFU0KJDK"], "answerLink": "G2UJDOWYGK"}, {"questionId": 348, "questionText": "LZ0D9KXNZ3GA7PZFRPYH8EH75P8ILBGCCF69UC84KVCSEJGI7D27RE6WAQULGEKK67SU52L12B8V7QKEL33EB9P9ALUIS7KS7NOL02F5BQKD", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "1.TM3UUEQJJQ2UOT3WDKPJD8PO47W2S07F", "wrongAnswers": ["2.31OK7JFI6ZCNY1S2JMEM4", "3.SCFIL6FK14KHHW3BKCS160V3H"], "questionOptions": ["1.TM3UUEQJJQ2UOT3WDKPJD8PO47W2S07F", "2.31OK7JFI6ZCNY1S2JMEM4", "3.SCFIL6FK14KHHW3BKCS160V3H"], "answerLink": "MDPHTK6GBY"}, {"questionId": 349, "questionText": "6ULYI03537ZESGG2QSIAGULM4O37QX6OUKNKRAFUAPB93INGY4Z7E95MVCN6L0RXNDGNC0VWYIQPL0FBTBWEQQEBTAAAQ8M", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "3.7KXPR735YVNC407J7O6QQFT7UG5329F2", "wrongAnswers": ["1.8A8SKCG6ENIPATF2HAC73ZMVP8B", "2.0KUV4FF7TKHS2IB2R93OOA9G"], "questionOptions": ["1.8A8SKCG6ENIPATF2HAC73ZMVP8B", "2.0KUV4FF7TKHS2IB2R93OOA9G", "3.7KXPR735YVNC407J7O6QQFT7UG5329F2"], "answerLink": "VFDY5QSJ0R"}, {"questionId": 350, "questionText": "MA8F7OTVVF1NWADP5VV404DZX6PJZAY8YOFHPDM7YTNRMZLUG1S48YFR8J5S1DP2WWHOOH9BYRZSAFI4U2S0M8PC3JUFSRL3J8EGPR2K", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "2.CGGAK4NLCXACYPB719JE99ANV", "wrongAnswers": ["1.XXT3C5NZVRYEHNR9CLGWR65ID4ESX", "3.1EVOXEJEAQPLSHVFUP70M7R47V"], "questionOptions": ["1.XXT3C5NZVRYEHNR9CLGWR65ID4ESX", "2.CGGAK4NLCXACYPB719JE99ANV", "3.1EVOXEJEAQPLSHVFUP70M7R47V"], "answerLink": "9VJL073BNZ"}, {"questionId": 351, "questionText": "9UH5Q590VA2IHGS73NCUA59GQ2I4RRCMOJJHEMS6YICWCHMJDKIF8NRNSW91V5YH08OW1RRJE63TAQULC16FRR1LVYW6T2J6S56TP6LKCNJPNKZC", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "1.M8AP0IJUXEI84FLEIA45TH9Z5KEIU85", "wrongAnswers": ["2.9F13N87J0QJ4FUU4H7B0BWSLHGF", "3.NHD5BHNFZF2LLVISUVN21"], "questionOptions": ["1.M8AP0IJUXEI84FLEIA45TH9Z5KEIU85", "2.9F13N87J0QJ4FUU4H7B0BWSLHGF", "3.NHD5BHNFZF2LLVISUVN21"], "answerLink": "G4JCXWM6ME"}, {"questionId": 352, "questionText": "5YW5TIUZA0RFO77IJNWM0T8QU43XT5OEL320THEYYEZGUMY74T4J8IHGZNQJNIL4504ELGL8FOLY6TUMX7PLF9HOURVVOT1T6O6MW8L66CFHWAFKWCC0R1M2JXBHP", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "2.C0DC2QVK1GCR0UEUNKD5MJMP038JAH1", "wrongAnswers": ["1.EB8JGKO8R646DO1XG0ITPQNU8", "3.ZMGPH9LMIVMBAENNJA7V"], "questionOptions": ["1.EB8JGKO8R646DO1XG0ITPQNU8", "2.C0DC2QVK1GCR0UEUNKD5MJMP038JAH1", "3.ZMGPH9LMIVMBAENNJA7V"], "answerLink": "4SJWM1B3AZ"}, {"questionId": 353, "questionText": "9DMEXR4RI8B8KFN3RJWPLPDE80JDM9JF50K7IJ7S2Z1FJ84C9RQH4JR2U9MN2524D6EU5X9TWVBJP", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "3.D9CFCANIEW0L8G8R9X", "wrongAnswers": ["1.MORLBTL1803863MAFC", "2.4KZ0A8LLLA1KVCS0A5YC2L"], "questionOptions": ["1.MORLBTL1803863MAFC", "2.4KZ0A8LLLA1KVCS0A5YC2L", "3.D9CFCANIEW0L8G8R9X"], "answerLink": "3WYSOXIR2O"}, {"questionId": 354, "questionText": "FO3XXUBA45C32SAHF4MZSK8USQD0D416HCIAS6UQM0MFXF4RQV4ZDWP3927TGOPYKPTKO", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "3.2S3DAJDZH05ZDCC3PKE", "wrongAnswers": ["1.T2545Z83NVFGD92F", "2.6OG21NDOZVZN62HRX"], "questionOptions": ["1.T2545Z83NVFGD92F", "2.6OG21NDOZVZN62HRX", "3.2S3DAJDZH05ZDCC3PKE"], "answerLink": "9VD0WPBBUY"}, {"questionId": 355, "questionText": "9QKM17QNTBU1VNA73BBUUETMNW18IX1MRAV3LB5CVOLPWWMTRSRD1S8GBSBPT9FN8A9OQ9J994X3YQUOOJM3JQ0IKYC07B91FCV7E48CBYAPQBSSXKKT5BZXF0YN03L3", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "3.Q011Q610YJ2KGEXTTDLRNH0M70ST", "wrongAnswers": ["1.O0WL7JQS8MRA9T8EJMO8", "2.UTS027KUDO5NJQJUT6TRHSKHF"], "questionOptions": ["1.O0WL7JQS8MRA9T8EJMO8", "2.UTS027KUDO5NJQJUT6TRHSKHF", "3.Q011Q610YJ2KGEXTTDLRNH0M70ST"], "answerLink": "6E5VSGVQLB"}, {"questionId": 356, "questionText": "R6I8B13RH3FCIZDIKADNAU6PC0G5VWNQYRRJQBCR67BBG0QWA7HVZAAU6M0LXID3IHKUPGI2BWA38GX94OQA4LD9L8KL4JYQFUPPEUNXSNU98NQ246S4K0KMS2V4", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "1.AR2NY3EAWMQ9ZESYKHJQ4YUB3", "wrongAnswers": ["2.WSRLYF33TQAVPRDXX3U745MYMSK", "3.T5GB1PL9Y4SS627KWCCEVNR"], "questionOptions": ["1.AR2NY3EAWMQ9ZESYKHJQ4YUB3", "2.WSRLYF33TQAVPRDXX3U745MYMSK", "3.T5GB1PL9Y4SS627KWCCEVNR"], "answerLink": "RM5K508YOZ"}, {"questionId": 357, "questionText": "1VMG7SZDTR7WOVV47XBAJX611UNEJ5VPK6PWK46H1PFZITKMHBUTBIIY86OIR3RINWFFJSESF6VP7DX927YS9NDE6KSTANHZFCC2K", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "2.IU8DUUVMN2U985R1DWZ2H1WN34", "wrongAnswers": ["1.U9DHMH3AZRKQ3MKYQ2G0Z", "3.Y537Y8I2FZZZH1DEO433NSGPUNU6"], "questionOptions": ["1.U9DHMH3AZRKQ3MKYQ2G0Z", "2.IU8DUUVMN2U985R1DWZ2H1WN34", "3.Y537Y8I2FZZZH1DEO433NSGPUNU6"], "answerLink": "I81MZ7I8LB"}, {"questionId": 358, "questionText": "85MOZIYCZXAP00KZT0XMAPM8I2I4VHP4OBCOVHQ65P046UXPMX08RKPQ0N9G5FPC0YTPG0DFMI79S2EAV", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "3.U03MM0PNL3JHXKYQCNNKCCS53IPXUHZ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.RX4WR61TQCU650MRQN92I00LIHE96O", "2.ILOGEMW9F3UFPKUFPIHN5UPVP94MDWPN"], "questionOptions": ["1.RX4WR61TQCU650MRQN92I00LIHE96O", "2.ILOGEMW9F3UFPKUFPIHN5UPVP94MDWPN", "3.U03MM0PNL3JHXKYQCNNKCCS53IPXUHZ"], "answerLink": "HDESVCI3U3"}, {"questionId": 359, "questionText": "UCQ75KJ9D4YYQZADDPACD3M0E361EGEOIK8972GC5B727HRH4NMROFNR3GDWX6P6F7ZZQ0HE1UBYOP", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "2.BQ141UGV9KT7VM7130ZG1CG6XS1GD", "wrongAnswers": ["1.6PL3BPCKSQF40XU1EPMY4", "3.8HON96C40U3AZ4FT"], "questionOptions": ["1.6PL3BPCKSQF40XU1EPMY4", "2.BQ141UGV9KT7VM7130ZG1CG6XS1GD", "3.8HON96C40U3AZ4FT"], "answerLink": "0HMWW18FGF"}, {"questionId": 360, "questionText": "3YK3O32W73FYTO81246OVZXPOHBT03CL8OK0R7O7DU94ACWGNFDR3M9OG9YX7BPUDX7R2KDP4GUD8C5BX0OSMG3XKPZ7RGXN05XS4Q6Q8DQ94OO", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "2.FRMX3MA3FZT1LWV31DFNT9SAW5JQ0", "wrongAnswers": ["1.8A9X6GVN081RTZMT", "3.K0OW5OASGHX2GZJCJFDHD8WA"], "questionOptions": ["1.8A9X6GVN081RTZMT", "2.FRMX3MA3FZT1LWV31DFNT9SAW5JQ0", "3.K0OW5OASGHX2GZJCJFDHD8WA"], "answerLink": "8LYLS9QEJK"}, {"questionId": 361, "questionText": "JF1T0NKTJRTKD78R8EOF8JJGNBQOHSYPP7IZHML42XX5YY5DNPINQRSYKYP92LZ27ZIV5U52YNVVQI92PUDWNNA4JOGLAS", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "2.KNCJ3E7E7F1ZZSBEL", "wrongAnswers": ["1.5SI30K6IVHJP0JENGS405NX", "3.OYB1GY95SJCASI2N8NIY60SM68MSVW"], "questionOptions": ["1.5SI30K6IVHJP0JENGS405NX", "2.KNCJ3E7E7F1ZZSBEL", "3.OYB1GY95SJCASI2N8NIY60SM68MSVW"], "answerLink": "MWHWRI3ZLR"}, {"questionId": 362, "questionText": "G56ZZR80YPUIQDR8FOP5J9Y83563SFL8ZQY1Z4E90F49QFCF5AF894TUYIROBJBYRB6S7SN93Q878DA9UO01MSZF2SUQ0I6U", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "1.DVJNSIRBS026QXHKODTC", "wrongAnswers": ["2.IN1ZGMKD18OTCOVOV25", "3.BRMCBTX9HVN04MBFCYW5RRAWMJFAR1"], "questionOptions": ["1.DVJNSIRBS026QXHKODTC", "2.IN1ZGMKD18OTCOVOV25", "3.BRMCBTX9HVN04MBFCYW5RRAWMJFAR1"], "answerLink": "Q51ACXE3QT"}, {"questionId": 363, "questionText": "F718N8CTCHZH0COIZ3YH1SB0P3RD8WNONE6XKET12NVV14YYXEHSE3AL676AMHFE1SW9XXRDW7FSWTIK09W", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "1.WHV8VN6ROPZDKUB5FOJHGXAVSLGL6XT", "wrongAnswers": ["2.56E26D62Q1RDWVXDAJBTYKPD9A5Z5M4R", "3.EMV9XK45XNCYF1HN9NOJJFX4X97"], "questionOptions": ["1.WHV8VN6ROPZDKUB5FOJHGXAVSLGL6XT", "2.56E26D62Q1RDWVXDAJBTYKPD9A5Z5M4R", "3.EMV9XK45XNCYF1HN9NOJJFX4X97"], "answerLink": "QB5859IXFJ"}, {"questionId": 364, "questionText": "JEHRGN9LG08FIQIBIGRKKSMYGKW64O6ZSIPM7YD000H9HICNVLFIGX3N0504FYAU23A6TQBWZTWIUI6HTIGVHE1S3W8NW0B0FVQEZX4IZBZJE", "questionCategory": "Regola 11", "correctAnswers": "3.KPEV89XCJNGC013PH", "wrongAnswers": ["1.6T6084O7OD7SNOZO754VZ27SKAZ", "2.G3EURL0EF45CQCC83QHEU38KGDNE"], "questionOptions": ["1.6T6084O7OD7SNOZO754VZ27SKAZ", "2.G3EURL0EF45CQCC83QHEU38KGDNE", "3.KPEV89XCJNGC013PH"], "answerLink": "QPZC1BMXBM"}, {"questionId": 365, "questionText": "05QE1XET1BG4ZVBMSSQGUJG05YSX4BIWCKD7PK1VIBYA4HSKN5LJI0RKKIL8JMLLM19HB5XROXRSIMINYB7DFRDR5C1CG03GH", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.OHKDS6EU1EKWCJ6WQ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.GSP98TBXHS2YUHNTCQPWDFP5UKAK11E", "3.GSYPXW7ZPFRDCYRO5"], "questionOptions": ["1.GSP98TBXHS2YUHNTCQPWDFP5UKAK11E", "2.OHKDS6EU1EKWCJ6WQ", "3.GSYPXW7ZPFRDCYRO5"], "answerLink": "5BQFSVNY7F"}, {"questionId": 366, "questionText": "QILTR4WCGJMDJZAKLEQ2E87P3G6VR9FL3FP5K532EZ8RCVG1TT52BUCN0CC6R0AI3WIPQMOTC6XT4IGL3AC5V3YN2TF1SYDQXAHWI682496F461Q7O1S4YXDR8MR1LLV", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.7P564O2CYZJYQXVJA2KQNLCRG", "wrongAnswers": ["1.KVTP1L9VQ2IK4NY27WHCCA9TKCCC", "2.CUZTA5FX845I2X5BKPC560Q32GRZ"], "questionOptions": ["1.KVTP1L9VQ2IK4NY27WHCCA9TKCCC", "2.CUZTA5FX845I2X5BKPC560Q32GRZ", "3.7P564O2CYZJYQXVJA2KQNLCRG"], "answerLink": "3KLA8S5TXV"}, {"questionId": 367, "questionText": "OO3D0AZHTZIUOOWGCRB3RKZEX56G2S6OJDHM51EB7XMX2Z3VMMRXM4ZDOODMF46NW8ZPXBKOKKG2SMAYZHQNC54R4466USTZ8FXKGWK7HVO8HHBTP28", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.P6Y7C74ZWQ772VDSZLIY5I9EF02", "wrongAnswers": ["1.GCUMHN40O7U8DS7D5AV7CJ4", "3.LEUCPWN1RE1TF4GNY8QSMLOH631C4U3"], "questionOptions": ["1.GCUMHN40O7U8DS7D5AV7CJ4", "2.P6Y7C74ZWQ772VDSZLIY5I9EF02", "3.LEUCPWN1RE1TF4GNY8QSMLOH631C4U3"], "answerLink": "MU1FIU6S7V"}, {"questionId": 368, "questionText": "L4PL4O34OSFKDEE4BNTWXTK6MQWDSNZXA362IVQM6MOLS76GJ9677XXYQUOG1EI0NX93TK34HYJ9R0C98MAY4ED27B6F5TYSIGJWZK", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.17XJSL7CGMEZQOPFBBTIDEQLUG5XYTD2", "wrongAnswers": ["2.SYOQP45ZS0SO8JJBU3", "3.87AVO6S8YE89FGPCNR9HJO29CXPWM"], "questionOptions": ["1.17XJSL7CGMEZQOPFBBTIDEQLUG5XYTD2", "2.SYOQP45ZS0SO8JJBU3", "3.87AVO6S8YE89FGPCNR9HJO29CXPWM"], "answerLink": "23OEX7PDHY"}, {"questionId": 369, "questionText": "GWFKBM9HQ0OQIEB4KFRVFB8DP2YAHE5B4RJTH6YC6A401TRU3VIUTSX1QY7QUQTJ3A4Z57OC44BO5XNQM7XU3EZB5I", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.XZSX6AK8VSKKD8UI4FD", "wrongAnswers": ["1.XUZPAEGCHSHINUYL", "3.SJLMKRKLP3FKXLWZ3HAZS21EMIOV"], "questionOptions": ["1.XUZPAEGCHSHINUYL", "2.XZSX6AK8VSKKD8UI4FD", "3.SJLMKRKLP3FKXLWZ3HAZS21EMIOV"], "answerLink": "7ACVN6U17N"}, {"questionId": 370, "questionText": "Y0HN26S3N8LT00T9Q2VWHZLHDFQY9F21UHA3N9Y6AHCVIOO4J88AOCSGHCVZPH8ROWRELVP2KOCLQKTB441WZFNEOYDD", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.XIKHQISFZ464IW7WZ1", "wrongAnswers": ["1.UJQU3G4APNDOQUH4CB8W5KU1EDTDY", "3.RESAPQ97QLXUH6NKC2Y9VGHHHI94ZFKC"], "questionOptions": ["1.UJQU3G4APNDOQUH4CB8W5KU1EDTDY", "2.XIKHQISFZ464IW7WZ1", "3.RESAPQ97QLXUH6NKC2Y9VGHHHI94ZFKC"], "answerLink": "6M97P9QY48"}, {"questionId": 371, "questionText": "RDUAN1FH02LLV84NZGIQN6K9Y5EZO2BF1Q3FFDVNBEZNG1KG95GDQEN19RNEQVU8GOVKOPAI2MF6BNCHZZOX7K2QE3I5LC6AK", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.OWMRISG9GERVNWGEVX7XL", "wrongAnswers": ["1.IXT4IWWQ1VBMMVHY0U0I69X", "2.7J671V87B1BVX1YYCJZ2ECZH0029XOPZ"], "questionOptions": ["1.IXT4IWWQ1VBMMVHY0U0I69X", "2.7J671V87B1BVX1YYCJZ2ECZH0029XOPZ", "3.OWMRISG9GERVNWGEVX7XL"], "answerLink": "M0ZTVURK9Q"}, {"questionId": 372, "questionText": "7Q3HRZPDQST0UNE3ORYETL40KK93EYMQAYKLIDCTEVCBJV7VVBEMNAQ6IR68FUAUHY6GR3HSZIVCDBQ2K26TXHOKTDDVSTRXT9N2W4ZR5HO8Z8H", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.0MX7BWZ0ZFWOB6XNKP25TDW5Z", "wrongAnswers": ["1.EXUQ4ILNJGNXOJTSVNQHZJK", "2.BJNFEQTPIFNCIUMN5SQ9G"], "questionOptions": ["1.EXUQ4ILNJGNXOJTSVNQHZJK", "2.BJNFEQTPIFNCIUMN5SQ9G", "3.0MX7BWZ0ZFWOB6XNKP25TDW5Z"], "answerLink": "Q8HH5NHSDX"}, {"questionId": 373, "questionText": "WYMN00RVLOBK0F23SSDJCDFO8BX5OEEQ0Y11VV4WO8ZZ5BG7EVBJFTY6MQWF98399XKUN9YEQWPMRUMAMPKZQA5AA2AG3HHZ4XHZU5EQ83HTXZT6OOCQOT5MA", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.B8XR1ONWCBAMAFP1C", "wrongAnswers": ["1.XBIYDVIPMAOXG5JKFZ0W0MII8HC7S", "3.6Z6JA5WV2ET2KMPAGU3GGO5"], "questionOptions": ["1.XBIYDVIPMAOXG5JKFZ0W0MII8HC7S", "2.B8XR1ONWCBAMAFP1C", "3.6Z6JA5WV2ET2KMPAGU3GGO5"], "answerLink": "QYE1ZGJNJK"}, {"questionId": 374, "questionText": "KZVVJB008PFLBYH0M0ONAY6G104UZUT6SEXO8XZGN9FTHI3JD64AFQZLNLMU2ZJKX6", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.JG7511K8TOKMZBJ7TKPISQ83", "wrongAnswers": ["1.B0XX8CAWZT973FQCQD91V", "3.S6PDNMYWF5SQTW0AXTWPDMT5GM0QVPC"], "questionOptions": ["1.B0XX8CAWZT973FQCQD91V", "2.JG7511K8TOKMZBJ7TKPISQ83", "3.S6PDNMYWF5SQTW0AXTWPDMT5GM0QVPC"], "answerLink": "PIABJBQIK6"}, {"questionId": 375, "questionText": "JINMIL3KFIU2YWIZ59DYDZWTS00WI17EAS7HKOFP1XMJ9L8WCIJK9L3DKSBIFB54ZQKX4UNGIFV9L9LUZRTDJWFCQLDKJ6EKY72HFP", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.PPFKXG1ZZCJOYFQPWWUZNETRPRB2O", "wrongAnswers": ["1.MEBTCZ89UI3854P3CY", "2.71HL6DZFD8Q89WEULHN3VZ8S0C6U7"], "questionOptions": ["1.MEBTCZ89UI3854P3CY", "2.71HL6DZFD8Q89WEULHN3VZ8S0C6U7", "3.PPFKXG1ZZCJOYFQPWWUZNETRPRB2O"], "answerLink": "JBU3XPZRBX"}, {"questionId": 376, "questionText": "OETEX5CNF2YRJ7DNIS3JNBB40IX7GTQXPPBBVTTGDWXH0OVTUXB40G8SKPCB8KUZ0JWBZTP8PDXMSR10916YPOY45WLJOPJYRWJ7BCOXTIT1YK6XLV825ZXWM2XG1QDW", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.HPBQCLLNC4NF4SPK2LAK6NL5YU", "wrongAnswers": ["2.WKLNXEZ50I9705IET7XH8", "3.A5U2ZN8B0J0O6P43M3OS032LKML1JT37"], "questionOptions": ["1.HPBQCLLNC4NF4SPK2LAK6NL5YU", "2.WKLNXEZ50I9705IET7XH8", "3.A5U2ZN8B0J0O6P43M3OS032LKML1JT37"], "answerLink": "SFUKKQSJVA"}, {"questionId": 377, "questionText": "J8G0UGRMBLUMCU4Z0ILB9IQ00GQMG4KX347BN3ZD6OXZ2FKTCED2IIGCPZGJ1WU3IIW2SYFPUYLN4YWEIKAJ8GXR4XNZ3SSCB1RQNIKIO32Y8U7JJCWS619SDVYTR1W", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.DUA98QAGZJHXEAYBTHKZ", "wrongAnswers": ["2.865IJERXWTA0LA8D3XIDE0", "3.0PJUIKSDF6KY8Z07ST"], "questionOptions": ["1.DUA98QAGZJHXEAYBTHKZ", "2.865IJERXWTA0LA8D3XIDE0", "3.0PJUIKSDF6KY8Z07ST"], "answerLink": "N7MW33T9QY"}, {"questionId": 378, "questionText": "4XYS7BMX70FOGAFMSJHN7ZCNN9R044BRUNDM10Y24I4GTINWRJX6MFEKC0AAKLV7P1FIJFOPX4VW1RLERIXUL2TDO16V4O2B0HBCOUTE4QJ", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.1OI3IUW8ETYTIDPXF1JB", "wrongAnswers": ["1.YXWGVLUDIC1AWQGDAB97KEP3I", "2.TMOIFIPIQOT5OL9OUEFUIX7"], "questionOptions": ["1.YXWGVLUDIC1AWQGDAB97KEP3I", "2.TMOIFIPIQOT5OL9OUEFUIX7", "3.1OI3IUW8ETYTIDPXF1JB"], "answerLink": "7LVTTRIPZW"}, {"questionId": 379, "questionText": "Z8N0O17LWROIDSB93YEQC6TATVHI8GACGPRTDJEWGU5PY65PDIVDKX7VVVKB06S9GJV95AYBU6SI3AU", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.HK2K9L8URT9L47ZBGLW9656EFNMA", "wrongAnswers": ["1.W655T3K8W5053TWABWSK0S0XSP", "3.C57PPNAP1WNBY61R1"], "questionOptions": ["1.W655T3K8W5053TWABWSK0S0XSP", "2.HK2K9L8URT9L47ZBGLW9656EFNMA", "3.C57PPNAP1WNBY61R1"], "answerLink": "BGU0FWUYCX"}, {"questionId": 380, "questionText": "VZ2AMC1VYWABWSKD5APZQEK7CE48PPFTB4R0ZR79NZ3SWQ99GUEWPUIWVOQ3PK0CUY1QBBGL58AGNFQQHPL2BBSB6MVVW0V2CME2", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.S8G2Y6D85NOXTDRF9NK", "wrongAnswers": ["1.9GZFYLTDEB5UUTX0UK32KUKI4D", "2.FP8UOFFYZJDY9AKVKI"], "questionOptions": ["1.9GZFYLTDEB5UUTX0UK32KUKI4D", "2.FP8UOFFYZJDY9AKVKI", "3.S8G2Y6D85NOXTDRF9NK"], "answerLink": "1GCEWFEVQN"}, {"questionId": 381, "questionText": "4SID9H3ANLLXZ44RWZTZNF3OQ7O39DFFZGCSRXYZM825YSBOHSJLTPOY59BUUWGE1LKGL0Z0D1UGV1JX7HNPIVJZ2MQ46IRFVZLMVQX0GVD70RUT033WLGTKD3OECK", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.ND8699SQ2K8KB02AL2", "wrongAnswers": ["1.9556IWORZKUP9EH0BA0NC29", "3.TZ52DWO248J46AA2UBJ"], "questionOptions": ["1.9556IWORZKUP9EH0BA0NC29", "2.ND8699SQ2K8KB02AL2", "3.TZ52DWO248J46AA2UBJ"], "answerLink": "0XFD6WEU37"}, {"questionId": 382, "questionText": "W9V3KP9ZAFOQ1JDWUES2XYOLRBDCOO2V50VI1N38OT0M3NL0OUICL55BUOM22FQQMBJB16OV3U4S3MSLJW8NZXPTGK5EOHYEW91WHXMNGLUGC", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.NRT5A52WM957F8Z65IRM79WE68I2WFS", "wrongAnswers": ["1.SF0VPZ3WRF51SPWDIIM8WR2LVA", "2.G6RUUHMD0DIQRMDPZUGFHM"], "questionOptions": ["1.SF0VPZ3WRF51SPWDIIM8WR2LVA", "2.G6RUUHMD0DIQRMDPZUGFHM", "3.NRT5A52WM957F8Z65IRM79WE68I2WFS"], "answerLink": "DFHEES7ZY0"}, {"questionId": 383, "questionText": "PICFCCUDWO1YQ7K1K3NJ327PNZ7QQYBWABCJJ7523PU76O0BJI83UX9GVU45MGAUGGYVCV2P9I5K3YQ01FIHF3YB66WY", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.BUBAVG551XEHSMGVTPMX4L8YI1SVW4X", "wrongAnswers": ["1.W43WRI35JJIZ6S2NOOJ", "3.IWDCC9SZLVODMND6G867692FKWX5Y"], "questionOptions": ["1.W43WRI35JJIZ6S2NOOJ", "2.BUBAVG551XEHSMGVTPMX4L8YI1SVW4X", "3.IWDCC9SZLVODMND6G867692FKWX5Y"], "answerLink": "XCP0V21XUW"}, {"questionId": 384, "questionText": "7VIQ9698UPJ402DAB52DQACG8ORL9841J7NKG3UB5GEWEY04ZMCQTJYRRW1C5OTWYF0A7L2IZD2AYNVO40TNKSQIO6IE41FL", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.S5DS85FKPG3AI6VIDCF5OQ75", "wrongAnswers": ["1.47PSXQRMPHT58NPUP4BTN", "2.5BYDT11PKRSNXRA16H7"], "questionOptions": ["1.47PSXQRMPHT58NPUP4BTN", "2.5BYDT11PKRSNXRA16H7", "3.S5DS85FKPG3AI6VIDCF5OQ75"], "answerLink": "TLW9FTO7VP"}, {"questionId": 385, "questionText": "K6P0HBA0UASVXIGQFEO1MG4R4GYG4X4FCUMGE0GTUJ5VTRO0BBJPCFE5AX2CZH7IXVD8PZP13", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.FE5E7NPLK8OSSJEHSBBTXV4", "wrongAnswers": ["2.TKDC32REA9WFJJIDLVSB43HZF", "3.04FLXK2O8QCBUNF2PWMUXPGFJQ"], "questionOptions": ["1.FE5E7NPLK8OSSJEHSBBTXV4", "2.TKDC32REA9WFJJIDLVSB43HZF", "3.04FLXK2O8QCBUNF2PWMUXPGFJQ"], "answerLink": "W4QNUP359B"}, {"questionId": 386, "questionText": "9UK3P7Y68URC2MFG8T7BHLSKFJFSGY5T37EV6UOT2235KCWMMWODXT5EC8DIMB4YVA3PAQZ3QQZHM2E1DHTRC26KP57K3M9FQQV2YEHKS63C4087328K85A5A9H", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.FXRC0VIE4QX1LJX9FID7FYMAKEQU4G", "wrongAnswers": ["1.8WT15YWYEX4BHNF2ZQVTUCJT7372ZNIX", "3.MSS5NFTN1F6PWYRUAURSI22"], "questionOptions": ["1.8WT15YWYEX4BHNF2ZQVTUCJT7372ZNIX", "2.FXRC0VIE4QX1LJX9FID7FYMAKEQU4G", "3.MSS5NFTN1F6PWYRUAURSI22"], "answerLink": "KH99DA2N8Q"}, {"questionId": 387, "questionText": "YB28ZSS25EWIPY2CB4IF0THBW2PRJMH05XUMMZHELTR6YSPSYQXUV1BBT9XNOO1CACNG9CC", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.NAKNQZL0LCTV3KDHAECZDV4778AU0", "wrongAnswers": ["1.Q1WUM7RAY4IYBQ2U17H", "2.DVQ85OAB17L9P315ZK8"], "questionOptions": ["1.Q1WUM7RAY4IYBQ2U17H", "2.DVQ85OAB17L9P315ZK8", "3.NAKNQZL0LCTV3KDHAECZDV4778AU0"], "answerLink": "3TGJMSBY5H"}, {"questionId": 388, "questionText": "DNTRKLZR566WGBTQSZMVP30PFKK4GERGZIKAXJJOZGMMK64YURUZ5NCW7AKIFCYRC2NNEAC6O3IM5626MMV695X27EB0DR3FXWWAGQBA9M7", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.Y9C5CD5BCGI96DIQV284", "wrongAnswers": ["1.XTK8TODK5BDKN5WY", "2.I8H875LCCD5FYGGKICMYSH1MSEB5"], "questionOptions": ["1.XTK8TODK5BDKN5WY", "2.I8H875LCCD5FYGGKICMYSH1MSEB5", "3.Y9C5CD5BCGI96DIQV284"], "answerLink": "DADLXM8Q4X"}, {"questionId": 389, "questionText": "WGF6HQ9W3MYJFJ711WT6OU1S9WZZGGPNVM4GIXXQO0JW7SGBVYBZJCJQ1G7CFCWUEHSWOIXEO645ZK1", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.JGLLPVBQQ0F3A009AJLFWF33UDAY", "wrongAnswers": ["1.SYVYP774TK2O8ZGD16FXGOVACEE3", "3.WMM5XS4ASS8F1RVIPHOYQLE4"], "questionOptions": ["1.SYVYP774TK2O8ZGD16FXGOVACEE3", "2.JGLLPVBQQ0F3A009AJLFWF33UDAY", "3.WMM5XS4ASS8F1RVIPHOYQLE4"], "answerLink": "XEEDDFVW7T"}, {"questionId": 390, "questionText": "AY7XXUIVL4KAY0XO23RFN4WNUZ9CSUW2C6WI1J20U6AF0BF73DEAN20093UTMC65U6DXU8YMOTPYABT5E9LXXMDEOQAHWS6T1XVS", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.1VLT1MA3T4Q2UD8T44WRMU1", "wrongAnswers": ["1.EBN1TWE9Z3MRS1CVPA2", "3.TOSNO8FATZNKK22IEZRPKEQVCWY35"], "questionOptions": ["1.EBN1TWE9Z3MRS1CVPA2", "2.1VLT1MA3T4Q2UD8T44WRMU1", "3.TOSNO8FATZNKK22IEZRPKEQVCWY35"], "answerLink": "9W1BNPHYVH"}, {"questionId": 391, "questionText": "O25LIE5WNXQTJLQV75515QD06AWP9EAUODTWJ7TNVYAU5ALR6794QOOW0OQRLN8OAILJVF4Y0R916G02PIOHUJ8N2ELEZPMLL4S34EEM0LUZUQW", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.E22VG6H7KDK8TR3W2L", "wrongAnswers": ["1.IFMVYV93UH1CE2ZJLG6ZJY87", "2.H969JYL1NMY2A7YO8BRK7BX"], "questionOptions": ["1.IFMVYV93UH1CE2ZJLG6ZJY87", "2.H969JYL1NMY2A7YO8BRK7BX", "3.E22VG6H7KDK8TR3W2L"], "answerLink": "C1R40J7VZC"}, {"questionId": 392, "questionText": "GQHBD7ZX60FZOHQ42RNK5UGOJZ89B28ZIBQMB8R759EP11857ZXP0WX40H4FHVKNZVMDGB1Y7BFLT9B6NGKQRWSR", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.WDHB5168N2AWAV2CHW6WK", "wrongAnswers": ["1.648SDY2MQUC6RBDRFE5Q5", "2.1BP4MEDM3DBKSB7G"], "questionOptions": ["1.648SDY2MQUC6RBDRFE5Q5", "2.1BP4MEDM3DBKSB7G", "3.WDHB5168N2AWAV2CHW6WK"], "answerLink": "88NVUTDILK"}, {"questionId": 393, "questionText": "E3GX0BVPCHPB56H0XISL09N9QQY0TC732ZE164ZMP73MREH8PVYFJ6VB189QG2YZTZBZCD1QTCXMU9V74BG93QTDO", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.NDMTIZ70504ELZA5SWY48", "wrongAnswers": ["2.2JGQG5BIYNKQJ9F59IGO", "3.XU3N7UMX3SFN95970NL"], "questionOptions": ["1.NDMTIZ70504ELZA5SWY48", "2.2JGQG5BIYNKQJ9F59IGO", "3.XU3N7UMX3SFN95970NL"], "answerLink": "JHRMVC0F2E"}, {"questionId": 394, "questionText": "FOWOZ0B8HP7QCN0ZNB1HYVD49NX6MB5G7GSRWE97DVHIG5RN3VHLN6O9ISBGBMZH1E3N0PG8T33B3W", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.Y6WYH4FFGOHUTGPSYSDDN", "wrongAnswers": ["2.PAC32T20K6OZBH298SHHFGFKQFG9C", "3.FSFYI13FYJM93LETU9KTTPDKGBTMA"], "questionOptions": ["1.Y6WYH4FFGOHUTGPSYSDDN", "2.PAC32T20K6OZBH298SHHFGFKQFG9C", "3.FSFYI13FYJM93LETU9KTTPDKGBTMA"], "answerLink": "9F20KVCBJ4"}, {"questionId": 395, "questionText": "FZVGXJKBM1KYRUAD3Q07RXO054MR7D5GVMOUMAO89MS8ABMKTWSB5OMH5T4HH1QIZ507O", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.ZU0BAK5ZQ7L7N8SLY7HDT7Q3WLFOP", "wrongAnswers": ["1.BL7MFWGONJ5IMTLS33QN3435IW2TQ", "3.68VMADODVZ6FG2K3SO"], "questionOptions": ["1.BL7MFWGONJ5IMTLS33QN3435IW2TQ", "2.ZU0BAK5ZQ7L7N8SLY7HDT7Q3WLFOP", "3.68VMADODVZ6FG2K3SO"], "answerLink": "WWGQIW8UF5"}, {"questionId": 396, "questionText": "3UAYF8644NN3V3M9LIEJIRQ4DMYIFQWIIY8HLJ9MUJS24AMXUKVGVD3TGCTGFFJ880NH4L3FVW0R", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.WSR4J89UBV86ULPR33XQS2DP4I0GN9N", "wrongAnswers": ["2.2W7LK1MZ9H4U2KD96EP8XN63DKZX45", "3.ASOE3LX11T2CBN9XODI9"], "questionOptions": ["1.WSR4J89UBV86ULPR33XQS2DP4I0GN9N", "2.2W7LK1MZ9H4U2KD96EP8XN63DKZX45", "3.ASOE3LX11T2CBN9XODI9"], "answerLink": "BFDRHAKAH5"}, {"questionId": 397, "questionText": "IJ6X01OP9P0UN18I3U1D1TJNB7GOFFDTXY2TBNMJR6R87DFT3RPGC4Z8L8OQQ4842ZE", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.SA5OYU814I4V9BK6XD79S6", "wrongAnswers": ["1.120MRZWKIRCXL2RE59B7CSFV6DW", "3.0UK3PPEUHSCJFO0SZ86"], "questionOptions": ["1.120MRZWKIRCXL2RE59B7CSFV6DW", "2.SA5OYU814I4V9BK6XD79S6", "3.0UK3PPEUHSCJFO0SZ86"], "answerLink": "UIDDWSX472"}, {"questionId": 398, "questionText": "8FX42XYXSRF5L0WCQ4LBRSBJYR7YBD4KWCMK4EYJ878QUNVJJAGWGTSLM7EEGE2WEUQVQWL8ZMFL85YFCF2NOH5", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.8QXPVJRGH6ZJB8XF7BB495VUU", "wrongAnswers": ["2.KX89L6WS64SR05HVOUO8EH6F", "3.EB7DQR5PVRW24SB8PGJ13LIRI08NZ9"], "questionOptions": ["1.8QXPVJRGH6ZJB8XF7BB495VUU", "2.KX89L6WS64SR05HVOUO8EH6F", "3.EB7DQR5PVRW24SB8PGJ13LIRI08NZ9"], "answerLink": "PSKI2QS5RB"}, {"questionId": 399, "questionText": "BZ6HZP1V9U5YSIOJ6ZNY53DXOKAZ3RS9YU192HBF5FI6AFLO8WAO6VMVW3YA7Z3N", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.H5TMA0BOZ626DLBS1XCIJDD2ESD8O", "wrongAnswers": ["1.H29YTH1LB8179ITE310TP2N2", "2.CM8MMH4RF061GH4N7"], "questionOptions": ["1.H29YTH1LB8179ITE310TP2N2", "2.CM8MMH4RF061GH4N7", "3.H5TMA0BOZ626DLBS1XCIJDD2ESD8O"], "answerLink": "0ERWGIB6EA"}, {"questionId": 400, "questionText": "VUS3RXNI285EJU2EZNVE52DDB60HSJJ1SKND5ZRZ0X42GSEG3FCTNBUUL0LKJX98Q0HCF0O0GLWLTM59LVIR8UVLSAUHCTK9LKD6M3COIA1K", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.93YTC1L5QPW22QV0IXB59W4234JIR49", "wrongAnswers": ["1.LM1NJ6SRYTLD0X61U3I6RGADL", "2.UF2YE4O02SGPA8HMP8H4OKLSDZRQ7M"], "questionOptions": ["1.LM1NJ6SRYTLD0X61U3I6RGADL", "2.UF2YE4O02SGPA8HMP8H4OKLSDZRQ7M", "3.93YTC1L5QPW22QV0IXB59W4234JIR49"], "answerLink": "04M5B657BU"}, {"questionId": 401, "questionText": "ABBHCHRXIK8Q669G3ZEOMGUUOPEZ8LB2Z76E7XZ0JBDVLDNRMPIX0X7YXWQGHIN63MFG83TWJEJ3K3RTYZX2HAER639XXPN08T8VTUHVXPZQIAETQBUM1", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.HP36VBIJJZHYAJEKRUX", "wrongAnswers": ["1.A7AZGIZSIQFOSEF96V2ZO", "2.IC4KM75EL6NUOW5W2WQ9X7UTNFMC5V"], "questionOptions": ["1.A7AZGIZSIQFOSEF96V2ZO", "2.IC4KM75EL6NUOW5W2WQ9X7UTNFMC5V", "3.HP36VBIJJZHYAJEKRUX"], "answerLink": "26PVA7E8NJ"}, {"questionId": 402, "questionText": "72YDK1JTSSS5ZX59PGVQWF6ZJ8252LHZCEH9IAXDEK6Y5CXG2S9R33396AFEDQFKDT6OH50F9UY2KMB9D8FXVISYP58PO", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.0E6Q6LHXC9WZWLCC5KNHCMUR", "wrongAnswers": ["1.IYV939SRNGQKDHL2DBREW", "2.EYC7C8P1NU043F6CD9LQLPGDG5B40"], "questionOptions": ["1.IYV939SRNGQKDHL2DBREW", "2.EYC7C8P1NU043F6CD9LQLPGDG5B40", "3.0E6Q6LHXC9WZWLCC5KNHCMUR"], "answerLink": "1IPK0CL4F0"}, {"questionId": 403, "questionText": "0YKPSSHGJT4K2Z7BV5ZX988H7HGXJXVEG4V0K04NRMDRJAAU2LONCXF9NJWZXA8UIW60KKFT6606VI0CRC7DS9DWC107NTKA7VQF7I9O5OLD2I6H9PI", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.EJ6ETX13KF4QDUI6YKS88J9X", "wrongAnswers": ["1.JWKG8GJKUOYKOJZI93WZZ83WD5NSKHV", "3.H979R1DQDXHFOHD0T8X7Q26VE5YIDVH"], "questionOptions": ["1.JWKG8GJKUOYKOJZI93WZZ83WD5NSKHV", "2.EJ6ETX13KF4QDUI6YKS88J9X", "3.H979R1DQDXHFOHD0T8X7Q26VE5YIDVH"], "answerLink": "YOLGPIEY90"}, {"questionId": 404, "questionText": "WGP76WM0ZNGSXMTVWXY3NR7F9P348QO9WEGL3YMBL1SY9D6TU4JFHICSP0CWRXF9UN4NVUKQ5XDBHG8O4AJBPGN5SV8XR1S26", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.XW0BRJ7VQPZK27F9A1QRG7LKJ", "wrongAnswers": ["2.981V11J4I2XCQT2BMKUW1OEJCS8K", "3.9VXLCF23PC0MKWSIKRIS9L"], "questionOptions": ["1.XW0BRJ7VQPZK27F9A1QRG7LKJ", "2.981V11J4I2XCQT2BMKUW1OEJCS8K", "3.9VXLCF23PC0MKWSIKRIS9L"], "answerLink": "67CXEAGIQB"}, {"questionId": 405, "questionText": "I8JHTV46GW0MSYJ5FE993DE4CUR3K2Q34H4TXJMKUIUX61DSTX4SNEKYQOWNVFXYJHKMLCHB350SVP70RSZGB9TJG0", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.42PXHG3LT0SLMBJKZPFRAS5", "wrongAnswers": ["1.4NB1JL3RZ89TPEITL5PREL6", "3.DPWIC2UFZMF77YL0GUJ9HS25"], "questionOptions": ["1.4NB1JL3RZ89TPEITL5PREL6", "2.42PXHG3LT0SLMBJKZPFRAS5", "3.DPWIC2UFZMF77YL0GUJ9HS25"], "answerLink": "OIS20I39JL"}, {"questionId": 406, "questionText": "RHC5BB2VZJDUFFDCLHERXF4CHVQIWA0THS88T53RAYHQF9MHPRTIPK3797CH6WQAF8W5B42W", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.V8JGALIO7N1IQOITSME6QVHAHZ1", "wrongAnswers": ["1.W92CEL6RV4RUUJ31JKLLXTFABGK", "2.DO43TXZUFCO2EX3SIYNXDI"], "questionOptions": ["1.W92CEL6RV4RUUJ31JKLLXTFABGK", "2.DO43TXZUFCO2EX3SIYNXDI", "3.V8JGALIO7N1IQOITSME6QVHAHZ1"], "answerLink": "CXTH3BW7HI"}, {"questionId": 407, "questionText": "QBC0KJJDW59KMJUM1P8F6U4ME1AJ0UFBFZ1AEF7L50BNDNO34TSV3YYWXPOZ9EJS4WKVRUD8P8G", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.J6UIPMZ5VLTC0YDGXFV7DMS", "wrongAnswers": ["2.RRHJNPZTFF9EPGORCDO6VM0H", "3.JICAD7ZFURDZGZPD5EXLEA546W"], "questionOptions": ["1.J6UIPMZ5VLTC0YDGXFV7DMS", "2.RRHJNPZTFF9EPGORCDO6VM0H", "3.JICAD7ZFURDZGZPD5EXLEA546W"], "answerLink": "GHHQYSZD5Q"}, {"questionId": 408, "questionText": "ZUZQ4J6FKRL7KAT2XNQ30K3NVO1KEHL4P9DEKF8YI3QR6X7ILIGY387BVF5XUCWUZKY4UK3TJMX0AGY6RREYHEJV4D6QZE94R", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.0X3YX7W8QCS5KQL7", "wrongAnswers": ["1.3VZ7WYZ8JEVWHL3ZR750K", "2.AHD84LN3DUZ8OJ2O8X2B2"], "questionOptions": ["1.3VZ7WYZ8JEVWHL3ZR750K", "2.AHD84LN3DUZ8OJ2O8X2B2", "3.0X3YX7W8QCS5KQL7"], "answerLink": "YAI5094E7C"}, {"questionId": 409, "questionText": "48R5I48QOWFRE0PKHEV11743LO8657LUL6UUPHLJY4WGNLJ90YJN4J54KHEPCAOK72CEPAX", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.ESUGVRL1YXZESNJF3Q3ZYXTK", "wrongAnswers": ["2.YUE3JHDHO81QP6SWO5CVSM", "3.BEIFZT8HTNIPO943A"], "questionOptions": ["1.ESUGVRL1YXZESNJF3Q3ZYXTK", "2.YUE3JHDHO81QP6SWO5CVSM", "3.BEIFZT8HTNIPO943A"], "answerLink": "PKNHS3TJTO"}, {"questionId": 410, "questionText": "ZMA3MVH3HEAPHFG9TETQVK6SJ150JM6RK0KLEZ294KPK5GTL4BARDV9L7VDCWM1XN8CSZ0QT", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.14ONNIM4XGIAROZOQHXC8RF07E0QW9U2", "wrongAnswers": ["2.SFH4I1SUELMTBBWFF07ZLY114LO", "3.0MT6FGETRAZDD1SWAKHPTG"], "questionOptions": ["1.14ONNIM4XGIAROZOQHXC8RF07E0QW9U2", "2.SFH4I1SUELMTBBWFF07ZLY114LO", "3.0MT6FGETRAZDD1SWAKHPTG"], "answerLink": "1USDRTIRFK"}, {"questionId": 411, "questionText": "DU470Y0G3PEYB9LDL79GZ0G6LCLKUBA8K451P9AA27XFJ4G5N91VBAYTVP7ER95IQNZLELXT", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.U69C9PT6F8VC8S0Q1TRA", "wrongAnswers": ["2.YSD52GO341Z9WZ96ZLWYHXO6DR", "3.RMW6OI2361TEG8KSFLBX"], "questionOptions": ["1.U69C9PT6F8VC8S0Q1TRA", "2.YSD52GO341Z9WZ96ZLWYHXO6DR", "3.RMW6OI2361TEG8KSFLBX"], "answerLink": "Y9Q63P8DO1"}, {"questionId": 412, "questionText": "J4VQNQ7A2HRUE81M96V8SWWCQ4NPPEMQ678GOKZ9WWEDRJDZJQ2LEWRXB0SNIXSZ4F45X6OROFBURJBB7VHORBSO74D89M33VRVLDNAD2VVFKPYG", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.FYQVZSE5I9TU6NZLDO3ITAIX", "wrongAnswers": ["1.F3S0SZLQGEZPZUOEOPYFQLVNLTEFUEQ", "3.34YHOADGG9R3I4O88J36E11FQ1UGQ"], "questionOptions": ["1.F3S0SZLQGEZPZUOEOPYFQLVNLTEFUEQ", "2.FYQVZSE5I9TU6NZLDO3ITAIX", "3.34YHOADGG9R3I4O88J36E11FQ1UGQ"], "answerLink": "HO4UL78Z23"}, {"questionId": 413, "questionText": "7FKGTVKOW9GXW5HK8FAYPL5Y4TO6SG8KQQNPNVGK7ZWLBYHTRMPUG7V2KQAWYTWK456", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.QRHT5DKN790AVRZGQW4S1JC", "wrongAnswers": ["1.LBI4BLZ9L8GTAU2JELXWNFLRYQ3JTDO", "2.Q7IBLRQ9DMBGLIMTF3YA8EQ2Z4O"], "questionOptions": ["1.LBI4BLZ9L8GTAU2JELXWNFLRYQ3JTDO", "2.Q7IBLRQ9DMBGLIMTF3YA8EQ2Z4O", "3.QRHT5DKN790AVRZGQW4S1JC"], "answerLink": "5NXZI2V9NE"}, {"questionId": 414, "questionText": "PNIL69R064R7C221ENOJGYDZ3J1YF89SIJBZ9OC5ND3EO9Y835EGGMENMF1O8967JO1H5I06CK3WZG2Z52WTNV9YCE4PAAXVTQHS8AR9K1U14JVFVBVYVWM", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.ZD86XYARZ2SGKOITL6UD87GQM1869", "wrongAnswers": ["2.377IGO2Z91YD954AZ9", "3.CAMHAOAC1IIEDNY5V2B5EC"], "questionOptions": ["1.ZD86XYARZ2SGKOITL6UD87GQM1869", "2.377IGO2Z91YD954AZ9", "3.CAMHAOAC1IIEDNY5V2B5EC"], "answerLink": "454ZAKUHGY"}, {"questionId": 415, "questionText": "D0BPFJ6QJCYPSW8MK1ELWQNJYVJIA9205KTLLM1FJEH7E02HBKT410RUS14QUC50N19A1C2EBZMSZCZ2KPMU2PVUELVOSMS1PBZVU", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.L4M4X1AL88FLXVM0GGBV2FO", "wrongAnswers": ["1.LBNDDEQPBK5TA6DJC66PCRIZW5HO6HE", "3.A6LJBTVHP0EJMHREFNNP"], "questionOptions": ["1.LBNDDEQPBK5TA6DJC66PCRIZW5HO6HE", "2.L4M4X1AL88FLXVM0GGBV2FO", "3.A6LJBTVHP0EJMHREFNNP"], "answerLink": "A0U39ELYTH"}, {"questionId": 416, "questionText": "UPUN98MB7GDQR84QH07UZ7TEIU0JK6ND6QE66WWGDBJZQ5FKFJD1U0Q76EBEA5RARL87FJQCE7Q6L7EO84UWQBVEKIZDUF88NUSKHD3AXRM", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.RNNL36J32E4CP9MCMXLRLRH68U7U0PY", "wrongAnswers": ["1.RZ4EDTQIPVEN9XKUA34C7O56T9DD", "3.L5L1JPJV72TXIHJ6HCR"], "questionOptions": ["1.RZ4EDTQIPVEN9XKUA34C7O56T9DD", "2.RNNL36J32E4CP9MCMXLRLRH68U7U0PY", "3.L5L1JPJV72TXIHJ6HCR"], "answerLink": "6DKUNNTMO3"}, {"questionId": 417, "questionText": "O3PZCKJVPOII1X3ZFP8V7AA8PLUDROS6KZNC3IUPUR3S0L65TSY67AVXTTW5WAO5ATGJGOJ5MWIGP0R6WJ8QQG6N7PNYR6R494D6HJ7LB01", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.5CN0KJD4IAACWVADRORE6TS5H29", "wrongAnswers": ["1.1VGOKHWTH0D9OC0SZSS0RC", "2.647K0JHQSNS9JMW5TJMJ3"], "questionOptions": ["1.1VGOKHWTH0D9OC0SZSS0RC", "2.647K0JHQSNS9JMW5TJMJ3", "3.5CN0KJD4IAACWVADRORE6TS5H29"], "answerLink": "4P92N99CPQ"}, {"questionId": 418, "questionText": "TVL6PEUWA9IIOEK1U3QGA1283WUON4RJDQW68HQBRYOP2PCYUXITJXDC16D97DS4VPG3VHKAGWLN7CDBQTRZ07NYK7VGEB", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.VX6JKT0MUU439NNF33B6RB", "wrongAnswers": ["2.LCO595KIZ1MRWGTADL5U9J", "3.K8X4X944N20SDH7JLQOC0HYWT"], "questionOptions": ["1.VX6JKT0MUU439NNF33B6RB", "2.LCO595KIZ1MRWGTADL5U9J", "3.K8X4X944N20SDH7JLQOC0HYWT"], "answerLink": "JYZELRTY8U"}, {"questionId": 419, "questionText": "SAHHMGRZUH60A11A2A5UDLRB38J1FWO0RP6NYJ20QGAM1ZKZ5B9VYWVGC3Q59WSDAHNSAA9WZOVO8V12NLDO6", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.RQ9RC4UGT0QIUFVWR6PN1KIKFP", "wrongAnswers": ["2.ML87M644GB16NKMEIJL3", "3.Z0SV79W5KOMCIDH0JR86"], "questionOptions": ["1.RQ9RC4UGT0QIUFVWR6PN1KIKFP", "2.ML87M644GB16NKMEIJL3", "3.Z0SV79W5KOMCIDH0JR86"], "answerLink": "8PG3KNM78L"}, {"questionId": 420, "questionText": "ZPO6YWW7YLIKE3FTCN11S93TAVI27FKLTOPPZYQF8PBABGG31SY6MXCNLMMUMPR1QLCCU5LFV2H42F0STWE78KZTJ", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.O7YZ1M995TNEQ6X0GTVSPI35V", "wrongAnswers": ["1.EYF3WZOG9083X01YMLO", "2.369ZV17NLDL3MVV6RWF"], "questionOptions": ["1.EYF3WZOG9083X01YMLO", "2.369ZV17NLDL3MVV6RWF", "3.O7YZ1M995TNEQ6X0GTVSPI35V"], "answerLink": "S791FJY91N"}, {"questionId": 421, "questionText": "BM53AFI6NTT3G7URWJ74MB3E083WRN7AM90I3HFD6P7GSWCSQ6IZD0HY49EUS2M2M4H9TOEGKBF8RR1IKR28T7QBZ", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.KG55Y3GC8XRVJRRTEFJTZBBNT4E", "wrongAnswers": ["2.TF03UD4ZNZN4QKIA25A2O1G", "3.YU4AFI52I4725DS70ZCVCWIEGANPXDK4"], "questionOptions": ["1.KG55Y3GC8XRVJRRTEFJTZBBNT4E", "2.TF03UD4ZNZN4QKIA25A2O1G", "3.YU4AFI52I4725DS70ZCVCWIEGANPXDK4"], "answerLink": "IJIJKTVCGA"}, {"questionId": 422, "questionText": "OI7V3CHA5B8XCCOAEX0XZ4TXXPLU0BDPO3JBF95T4P9C4ZFDO45WTSSDHY0O9DVK9QR", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.HJH79RIAMPX163MRXHG3SRRW4HHG", "wrongAnswers": ["1.PR8G2LH9MS2ZFUZF79X", "2.FQLUFHKNWYYD69MIWA"], "questionOptions": ["1.PR8G2LH9MS2ZFUZF79X", "2.FQLUFHKNWYYD69MIWA", "3.HJH79RIAMPX163MRXHG3SRRW4HHG"], "answerLink": "LBV1Y8CB9D"}, {"questionId": 423, "questionText": "VIT7ZGHBWVWC81FL9Z1M1DZJ5KS33XTA8UBKWYVYC9BBIYJ8M5PX4BDEM7Z56NSKSR74DPEMSLCYSMQHG2KZIGE0ZZQGSIYNO3F5", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.FUWQZ2PTJQNY86LXHC", "wrongAnswers": ["1.J162H3K0YQ09TCZPEP7QK9W6VS", "3.YP4NNUVCYBQYXVWWWKU"], "questionOptions": ["1.J162H3K0YQ09TCZPEP7QK9W6VS", "2.FUWQZ2PTJQNY86LXHC", "3.YP4NNUVCYBQYXVWWWKU"], "answerLink": "WT68GZTCB3"}, {"questionId": 424, "questionText": "SUKWVBRMWLRP8HHPXMJP7VE6R2LLMIMNRQR06GXSDNBULV4SRYAMUWAIEF6BT63YPFU1UFU4GITE1K9OJ4L5PJK02JYL208DGYL0828HOXMHICLCEMA", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.RCNAX33NHO6AEX3ZVNP5R7K", "wrongAnswers": ["1.W1Z1GAY4MQ8TDGT6", "3.WSFPNDWJPR3GNBNYW"], "questionOptions": ["1.W1Z1GAY4MQ8TDGT6", "2.RCNAX33NHO6AEX3ZVNP5R7K", "3.WSFPNDWJPR3GNBNYW"], "answerLink": "L7BGKQT5EW"}, {"questionId": 425, "questionText": "ZU2UUUA8Y3Y8HDZNKZFQHUOA6WSBFWEJEJ2DNSLFB16AQFJ3I7U68293C2C2EFR20F0SS9L3HZT90JY951D", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.APBN20D4GHEGXXSXRV4O7RQ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.1J86114C708BF2OOM26", "2.KJWHK4N1OPD2P960N5Y02F0YLA"], "questionOptions": ["1.1J86114C708BF2OOM26", "2.KJWHK4N1OPD2P960N5Y02F0YLA", "3.APBN20D4GHEGXXSXRV4O7RQ"], "answerLink": "5423LUV1IU"}, {"questionId": 426, "questionText": "7WGBCK0Q2S4KIPIAZGRWKGQISDYUFMRGT9KJS67H1OAEBJDUEEJEJYKB7SIN1R58GQIDHF8HJ85L7DKJIW5XUWNK7C5DWU55MI21F77DBTCVJHW", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.Z0ZB48RQM58T49CFK", "wrongAnswers": ["1.KZ9JHVT0Q1IFXFJ46P2J8OU", "3.JU6NI93192Q358JQQC4DA"], "questionOptions": ["1.KZ9JHVT0Q1IFXFJ46P2J8OU", "2.Z0ZB48RQM58T49CFK", "3.JU6NI93192Q358JQQC4DA"], "answerLink": "SD40JHXVVP"}, {"questionId": 427, "questionText": "10UJOCTVX5SSPVO2NE9LCEMI6ILOJILJ47ETXW3BVO0JT0KDVJ2F4L9FIRFWTNQX0ZT0SJB5GV85IX97KINYPQKX5HQI1C3A9YR6M8G2K", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.ZMYY47SOPAPR9XCXOBG7", "wrongAnswers": ["1.YC13L5S6M0SV8JZGYVE4G", "3.RVAEYMI5WF23DOSTBKQ3EF"], "questionOptions": ["1.YC13L5S6M0SV8JZGYVE4G", "2.ZMYY47SOPAPR9XCXOBG7", "3.RVAEYMI5WF23DOSTBKQ3EF"], "answerLink": "55IPEQRJCY"}, {"questionId": 428, "questionText": "83YUODWEEL3GQWBMPVICAHNNC21XMO4DR5755C7A8IS4HIXA5F9LC09MGYRJ8K5MXG9OOHVDY9CR0XG6D3HHDKWGH", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.2MVS8EN512PLHW43S8GFGGOJXLQWQKQ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.ZL32CJ8627JSV6TCZGUDWNI2YDMZ8", "3.F4IVZYN89WN0HBA9T7D1E1"], "questionOptions": ["1.ZL32CJ8627JSV6TCZGUDWNI2YDMZ8", "2.2MVS8EN512PLHW43S8GFGGOJXLQWQKQ", "3.F4IVZYN89WN0HBA9T7D1E1"], "answerLink": "G7FQRRXK6N"}, {"questionId": 429, "questionText": "0IN9GECLFULTTNPT0JF99R4DFQ9HZN33BNSFELEDQ867MK8XTOVUS5ZKIDDQMFIUPC9A35O5CE9DGLWN9E2IBC6ITL24HF3AEIKMIXO9ZZQ2NRUIMU4A2YGJ", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.OYV7RDZC455RK0KQLNGD87K", "wrongAnswers": ["1.BRMFDOC5QQXJNT6PD32FQIR5LTVM", "3.QMO6QX1VLAVXW2ZSXLLV02IW0AVA"], "questionOptions": ["1.BRMFDOC5QQXJNT6PD32FQIR5LTVM", "2.OYV7RDZC455RK0KQLNGD87K", "3.QMO6QX1VLAVXW2ZSXLLV02IW0AVA"], "answerLink": "0I1GMP0HCP"}, {"questionId": 430, "questionText": "LGEDHTPLPCA5H7Y7U0U7Y72TZKCD6BW0TMVIXV9BWQAAC9O8SNGO8RD65RJPSQ33KLW60D4X0UWNYT6IUNJM2R6SU2P9Z0DBHCMMQQ2N6", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.0BZPFEYPP6QM6EZO8VCF", "wrongAnswers": ["1.NAOOSJIP4PR9BNUCMSEZ9PE9E50", "3.RJ025GXAZANMIRA81RVX2"], "questionOptions": ["1.NAOOSJIP4PR9BNUCMSEZ9PE9E50", "2.0BZPFEYPP6QM6EZO8VCF", "3.RJ025GXAZANMIRA81RVX2"], "answerLink": "ZVEB6WPBNQ"}, {"questionId": 431, "questionText": "J6B08IV9VR68XPRDGVEDVYEIIHAXDHYN3C8N2Z08AZ2HMPEY1IR5D4HGHDB7FHSI5ACKWW4LI9N41KJWDNDS5BO5KX6UOAQ", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.OYQ8V9X7M5IPT2IEFZW", "wrongAnswers": ["1.6UIOVKJ74SGVYGBJUCZOJGK", "2.40Z2ATXSTGK86YHL4ZVMI905FIV0S"], "questionOptions": ["1.6UIOVKJ74SGVYGBJUCZOJGK", "2.40Z2ATXSTGK86YHL4ZVMI905FIV0S", "3.OYQ8V9X7M5IPT2IEFZW"], "answerLink": "ZBMWTMZDLC"}, {"questionId": 432, "questionText": "JBFA3N4KVFGQSTHD6DNUW4GVWMS0ZC13UVQUGUARQ8YBRNVUQQX7N11OLRBULCPX3AX5NG", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.LM71SZEQEXBCO8PJ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.7LXC42LNJNMNK9MIWRVU4UTS8I", "2.Z457A8N1PG8TPNAASN21730P"], "questionOptions": ["1.7LXC42LNJNMNK9MIWRVU4UTS8I", "2.Z457A8N1PG8TPNAASN21730P", "3.LM71SZEQEXBCO8PJ"], "answerLink": "ZTO2WG49A9"}, {"questionId": 433, "questionText": "94WOVVX12JI159G9FRNXI2I47ISL8OBXVUVPAQ53SIY0KD136HR9Z1Y2CW8PJEV8LAPBBQ86IOCLL9KLHV5A4ZPPTLV67P9", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.UK24BB5XH4UB1RZNOVSPNL", "wrongAnswers": ["1.B0ZZBG51BVGOBNBK1L4IHKEDQJ0U8JQF", "3.X0ECACQ2V0ILLVG3E8KR8"], "questionOptions": ["1.B0ZZBG51BVGOBNBK1L4IHKEDQJ0U8JQF", "2.UK24BB5XH4UB1RZNOVSPNL", "3.X0ECACQ2V0ILLVG3E8KR8"], "answerLink": "RJZ9UVB8LO"}, {"questionId": 434, "questionText": "MPR3QAN4VIX9N0Q0DGQXI0RGG6YT6TWTD2LUVS4ME5IWPQTB6V2EPMFSJ3XWR11HHY0ZN67NAQAN0EMT3S2NR0DAYO567CLHL4A3B", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.47IQIXOAUDEM7ZYB3", "wrongAnswers": ["1.TSWEJH304NTGZELVHU3HB6I", "2.BN774WYDPHBEDNNLZJHRNS8QK0AE"], "questionOptions": ["1.TSWEJH304NTGZELVHU3HB6I", "2.BN774WYDPHBEDNNLZJHRNS8QK0AE", "3.47IQIXOAUDEM7ZYB3"], "answerLink": "JMSOHWU24X"}, {"questionId": 435, "questionText": "AV9HKHOU86YYTYRB28ZV81C1J8H91XQ2UK7HJS0ZFD0PEBDL9VNXLNV88OWFY92DXCH3UYSX0HTEJ029S8CI287X0BW5X7OX4XMOHQ0JPX4", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.1HNCASZW2AO3CVG4MTVCJUNNVV3GRI", "wrongAnswers": ["1.3TOX3JG3S7A9EXG747N", "3.5QYPZMBTCV53MEJ0BXBDWQ7JYU"], "questionOptions": ["1.3TOX3JG3S7A9EXG747N", "2.1HNCASZW2AO3CVG4MTVCJUNNVV3GRI", "3.5QYPZMBTCV53MEJ0BXBDWQ7JYU"], "answerLink": "FRV8JAQ21F"}, {"questionId": 436, "questionText": "3ZTNSHDHRMULK3BUSHHO1ULB10P1P7JKPYRUHNM83GAHO7775L1O3OO8Q7RJ5ZPWQD1", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.KD11ERSNUDUO6HZ8O268OP23OJVBQA", "wrongAnswers": ["1.HETAJ6BJZA0XTKEVD74YBD", "2.DXF3L714B65IAKUWLCQIVX9"], "questionOptions": ["1.HETAJ6BJZA0XTKEVD74YBD", "2.DXF3L714B65IAKUWLCQIVX9", "3.KD11ERSNUDUO6HZ8O268OP23OJVBQA"], "answerLink": "MPH0TR4SAQ"}, {"questionId": 437, "questionText": "3PRT5S1OFKGPK0BX7FB6VQ8NPQNSV8TZC418BC09EHCUF6EVMPYR19C4E6LO2XX7E0TEWKVWZXK2JIPO8JUCKD05GQEJ", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.E34YQPR7FJBCNLL6KJDZ77TEH4DOXZXS", "wrongAnswers": ["1.5RPCVT208N0NN1E6JTQN0TGBQN9KKRDA", "3.IFNMTZZFJRJ0JAG4VPCK"], "questionOptions": ["1.5RPCVT208N0NN1E6JTQN0TGBQN9KKRDA", "2.E34YQPR7FJBCNLL6KJDZ77TEH4DOXZXS", "3.IFNMTZZFJRJ0JAG4VPCK"], "answerLink": "8WP4IT3GF7"}, {"questionId": 438, "questionText": "QJEDX2QMVS3XI4F0B5IADN2VSPVDQCYGJJU1C3FTR0SMHVDAZV4KLOHBF5E69QKOL0V8SS3DANW9AYNL3418V8ZD23DYJ6RID7WWW6CIX9W6KXAS9DNTRLSHCE7G", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.NM569PCSGN0QDF5ENMR00", "wrongAnswers": ["1.GFCS63HQ7JL0IGOF83D8XT5ZBR", "2.AZ9YEUZHMBLGV6DDTK"], "questionOptions": ["1.GFCS63HQ7JL0IGOF83D8XT5ZBR", "2.AZ9YEUZHMBLGV6DDTK", "3.NM569PCSGN0QDF5ENMR00"], "answerLink": "EZSEWVX8VJ"}, {"questionId": 439, "questionText": "4ASJFCM959535DR0RJUOAF858BB8V3UQ0POS72L4MOESKZ3CAPPY9YR7UOLZEBV8LGO1JK9JKVS69SZFT9OKRBT937X8LM8D62TPNEVQRWEGUZ2QP", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.UG6AXZJC28UNT7FSX9GCV32XBC1Z9S", "wrongAnswers": ["1.BKR3WLAO8Q9UMCODWTJYB", "3.XZEZSN6DTVEUVBQRLPAFP5IP"], "questionOptions": ["1.BKR3WLAO8Q9UMCODWTJYB", "2.UG6AXZJC28UNT7FSX9GCV32XBC1Z9S", "3.XZEZSN6DTVEUVBQRLPAFP5IP"], "answerLink": "V1AH2KLBU5"}, {"questionId": 440, "questionText": "M4VMOXVSYBPZ9NS3M02BLFKYRKW87O4ZO06DDXRPTYEPVH2XSSRDQIHS1OT336OSF06MDUT5BK4HY954GXJX325IQ0IJHHIVTI29OHN8DCY", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.BV9CIAUJXXIX7RUB0QQ8", "wrongAnswers": ["1.TQUN3KJ6U5SYHOGQYD", "2.55MIBFC6SOWMZ1MVW"], "questionOptions": ["1.TQUN3KJ6U5SYHOGQYD", "2.55MIBFC6SOWMZ1MVW", "3.BV9CIAUJXXIX7RUB0QQ8"], "answerLink": "O1TDLWYKTC"}, {"questionId": 441, "questionText": "45VSSFBQT84JA5YUY45C2UVAZZ33J4W2GQTF2YK5Z9RCBAR0258J0UOV1QYQFLBAK3RMAY9GYFNOQ9UQM5A3PBP5COCSFXOSVA1B6", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.2RW6P46A6A00TNFMOXP3U02Z1HL", "wrongAnswers": ["1.ZS9KT5ITE3LGF4B69LNU8HVD1AT", "2.LN3NF8PBAPJRWUGEEKI9"], "questionOptions": ["1.ZS9KT5ITE3LGF4B69LNU8HVD1AT", "2.LN3NF8PBAPJRWUGEEKI9", "3.2RW6P46A6A00TNFMOXP3U02Z1HL"], "answerLink": "PN99FNQDX2"}, {"questionId": 442, "questionText": "1GML2IAIOOBL3SN3Z7EOCMH5O7RX0P4B7X0D08H27MVPIVVDRVSE5BKU87WMBVHK5W7MGSP9T9UK5K", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.8YZMFNHH0ZF0FORWT5B83TVX217CCJF", "wrongAnswers": ["1.5DZLK0HOASPGOQLWFD0Q", "2.IWTV7X9DTCQ285Z9HLUCENDA0D45L0"], "questionOptions": ["1.5DZLK0HOASPGOQLWFD0Q", "2.IWTV7X9DTCQ285Z9HLUCENDA0D45L0", "3.8YZMFNHH0ZF0FORWT5B83TVX217CCJF"], "answerLink": "I1R4HE3SXY"}, {"questionId": 443, "questionText": "U77224G9WH8II664875J93YHKM0C5UUUKEESV58NJFZD9G49O7KF32JBHM6K83SXOJDGVYTS", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.5F79GSWPUC9TDU8NCX6QDOALXK", "wrongAnswers": ["2.6QM2MDRQYR34DUQ1MPC", "3.GYSRZ4GLVLV00BQN3LTQFP2V4Q22BBR"], "questionOptions": ["1.5F79GSWPUC9TDU8NCX6QDOALXK", "2.6QM2MDRQYR34DUQ1MPC", "3.GYSRZ4GLVLV00BQN3LTQFP2V4Q22BBR"], "answerLink": "NLMQEWOTJQ"}, {"questionId": 444, "questionText": "KDMOC9NCZPQ42FFJ5EJA13JZKI0F2BMIAVBHTXN27KH4A5HIIJI4SR38SII0E89Z9KWH5J3R0LEFEYW48DPWLHL7ND5U4CDL6C3", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.I7X5MKMBPV4DBA5H4QWP6P13A", "wrongAnswers": ["1.6G5I02Z22O7KSC2V8ZMQY7I8G5", "3.3ZGCBK9Q5TBR00854I31PI2T5SMRN"], "questionOptions": ["1.6G5I02Z22O7KSC2V8ZMQY7I8G5", "2.I7X5MKMBPV4DBA5H4QWP6P13A", "3.3ZGCBK9Q5TBR00854I31PI2T5SMRN"], "answerLink": "3JVKTA5AM8"}, {"questionId": 445, "questionText": "8TL7UAO4XA5YAIIY5E27AJJNFBKX12VQIU4YH1U68LXA5DQ7Q7WPZ9UCOFT6RXY8J66O2ZPD3MQTNE42J4XBKVGF1NBR0JLXC6D7666FXZVJRW9HLOGQY", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.L5HS2X9V23N7AYNXHUUP5B7B1XMVMA", "wrongAnswers": ["2.99IY0IKUFBB135G4W", "3.QZH8GOT4W5TMO9O4"], "questionOptions": ["1.L5HS2X9V23N7AYNXHUUP5B7B1XMVMA", "2.99IY0IKUFBB135G4W", "3.QZH8GOT4W5TMO9O4"], "answerLink": "T3XEBFRVQ3"}, {"questionId": 446, "questionText": "6A060HGI9IFQFRYBZ4E2ES1ATJTH3Y6FYACUUMJKR59HYAMPSBO8PLKQL2FCPWE82DDE1545Y1CKY9OMJ75DY9CN1E9MLS1NPY6NQI5FRFS", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.8UNP2H23Y68RPQ39EBG1", "wrongAnswers": ["1.2UVJHVAWQV1YMTWQHL9EZF", "3.W209MV9YWK5PVFHKVIGOISQ9AX5"], "questionOptions": ["1.2UVJHVAWQV1YMTWQHL9EZF", "2.8UNP2H23Y68RPQ39EBG1", "3.W209MV9YWK5PVFHKVIGOISQ9AX5"], "answerLink": "EKGQN55RWY"}, {"questionId": 447, "questionText": "3FSHYM6DQN2EXLZ5G7DMU1ISGFQJXGBGM3FA077GQOST1VY9FYKZ5LDCQRAPZVA0O", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.ML2D9TYGAFDQQZWUHCE8SNUYA57DNUYB", "wrongAnswers": ["1.6AYAP6P9R9AF0WU593ZZU6XHSMY0S74S", "3.3XOS9SBJ0BCGBN6R4RQKNC0FODGJ"], "questionOptions": ["1.6AYAP6P9R9AF0WU593ZZU6XHSMY0S74S", "2.ML2D9TYGAFDQQZWUHCE8SNUYA57DNUYB", "3.3XOS9SBJ0BCGBN6R4RQKNC0FODGJ"], "answerLink": "85CWHE4BU5"}, {"questionId": 448, "questionText": "95C7N2LL1OZM9R6I28L0AF86ZELXSF7LR2RH9X2TKGQ1WGD3LSQP5K5BGZTOIB7AIXTMOOKEF9VA90188WX5PG4T3FAMNTIP8O07RS9TA21PJUI", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.VSQ0VRPRQUQ5GD5NLNSG6N5X", "wrongAnswers": ["1.RJ8S8HVSI54TYCH4FQPN29J47HL", "2.0NYZUG1V7TYSG5VSRAO"], "questionOptions": ["1.RJ8S8HVSI54TYCH4FQPN29J47HL", "2.0NYZUG1V7TYSG5VSRAO", "3.VSQ0VRPRQUQ5GD5NLNSG6N5X"], "answerLink": "D1M2VDHKU9"}, {"questionId": 449, "questionText": "8UN6SZBS9188YFV8P598ZJ1F1P7ANP0XJ15V0VHWJXNP7N9FP4LOGAIYG8IL4ROAPTT1JDBZX7S86W7XXIMHP", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.9R304LEJDF04MLGE05A5IAPQ1FT01", "wrongAnswers": ["2.9YZ83LGB38Z2RAKK", "3.2RCVXJ381GJZYGGYWJSQ38KJM"], "questionOptions": ["1.9R304LEJDF04MLGE05A5IAPQ1FT01", "2.9YZ83LGB38Z2RAKK", "3.2RCVXJ381GJZYGGYWJSQ38KJM"], "answerLink": "SQ1WVQRR0S"}, {"questionId": 450, "questionText": "ZZNOII14TWM92RFJ78HKY105R5O9RH7BN7GY0SK7KVFD9CTQOJ1VMRHYASW7M1HW8IBYZ04SI5PBGFP8IS1J4", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.DLGJ6XDF45CNZSR1ZSUJZUPVOO8UMNTJ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.XML8JK7W4AK07EZUOCVPG1DD8KJ", "3.AZA15YLNPJN54YZZJY7TSB3"], "questionOptions": ["1.XML8JK7W4AK07EZUOCVPG1DD8KJ", "2.DLGJ6XDF45CNZSR1ZSUJZUPVOO8UMNTJ", "3.AZA15YLNPJN54YZZJY7TSB3"], "answerLink": "ZVP0J12U9W"}, {"questionId": 451, "questionText": "G6K6QWE9PXHZODWB9SKUDTXLGMGLRTPEKABNB09WB5PRA58AUVIZL8O0D3PREEJO6RZZW39KV0JH", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.28G5LOUCN45XRXNWPUYEU4QBBZ48NST1", "wrongAnswers": ["2.8OEI1OR5CEAGREXJ67M86", "3.I76LA92A1LL4CJL1HX6OGUH"], "questionOptions": ["1.28G5LOUCN45XRXNWPUYEU4QBBZ48NST1", "2.8OEI1OR5CEAGREXJ67M86", "3.I76LA92A1LL4CJL1HX6OGUH"], "answerLink": "GNT0AXMQKB"}, {"questionId": 452, "questionText": "QGLR7IZVFLYHDX820ANM180S8EA4JT57HDM9AO1USI6WIYC88M5DJU8AHRI3497UHWL", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.TJNH3VGDTHXMGMQHKQIRMWHDRF1", "wrongAnswers": ["2.VT6DP0FNC5RKCCQ588D8", "3.20UOXW241BC34262WQQP0NB9R8Q5TSM"], "questionOptions": ["1.TJNH3VGDTHXMGMQHKQIRMWHDRF1", "2.VT6DP0FNC5RKCCQ588D8", "3.20UOXW241BC34262WQQP0NB9R8Q5TSM"], "answerLink": "CL971RGTPA"}, {"questionId": 453, "questionText": "W0FESLDJLFLWEPKZ6W2RPS2X91IC7DI26HDRI9F2PETERM4I4ROGQYGX0HFB5EI8ZM", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.MTVFC2HMAL20XBD54Y1A0N2U", "wrongAnswers": ["2.UP45ID0BW0R4S6Q48QZB6", "3.ZYCUUI6867OTN5ZWRDYJE7DKDWC"], "questionOptions": ["1.MTVFC2HMAL20XBD54Y1A0N2U", "2.UP45ID0BW0R4S6Q48QZB6", "3.ZYCUUI6867OTN5ZWRDYJE7DKDWC"], "answerLink": "5KIIM67I0O"}, {"questionId": 454, "questionText": "BUZ0EQKDKJUM10G4ZPFT63WHDQV0N5LW74CFRM5X3A4W5RNKW0U34GA2XBVDE9EIKXVGW6NFDIM30EBW89SHG3HZONBPCOTTDMSAH16IFNIY0UV33ID3UMFQ6WV48SD", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.IE3VIDC511WA4BRXLRQWWCP3QEDBM", "wrongAnswers": ["2.6NNBCDFLNE0QPC2R5TEL6SMHK62BO", "3.ENC1RTUHVECPDL48IQ06F8BTEZ"], "questionOptions": ["1.IE3VIDC511WA4BRXLRQWWCP3QEDBM", "2.6NNBCDFLNE0QPC2R5TEL6SMHK62BO", "3.ENC1RTUHVECPDL48IQ06F8BTEZ"], "answerLink": "LKUATQC3OT"}, {"questionId": 455, "questionText": "TC70CH1JQAQZMF4P8VPVV1NS0KXTP8PR764D0C1XA4841ZIKG0FJ34JRMJC1DV59TADNPQSYOB2280P3ZIOWNGSF18QL6BREJEWDPARSUNXMENEPQ9HBPHIS8ENG", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.XBUNW9SN6V11U27WM957XPM6JLLJE", "wrongAnswers": ["1.1OYU72TKJSLE8AMOF", "2.M3HCMJ2P72YMT80IDL"], "questionOptions": ["1.1OYU72TKJSLE8AMOF", "2.M3HCMJ2P72YMT80IDL", "3.XBUNW9SN6V11U27WM957XPM6JLLJE"], "answerLink": "CYJSEAXF67"}, {"questionId": 456, "questionText": "7V60JU0WZMZPJMIO6J48QCYGLHSYYI7P4BC4FISIE09Z86QUCD25WXRX6NS6YV601508RM998D5KUYMVFEI4TR63H6GNR4BARZCT0GU1L0", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.JIOBLWDINHAKLPUQC314MUUHM", "wrongAnswers": ["2.6U97S6RH9TGBCTIPNOKOJYKGK", "3.KIAAYSPZ5LY7H25VBU"], "questionOptions": ["1.JIOBLWDINHAKLPUQC314MUUHM", "2.6U97S6RH9TGBCTIPNOKOJYKGK", "3.KIAAYSPZ5LY7H25VBU"], "answerLink": "Z1WP12PMX5"}, {"questionId": 457, "questionText": "YE22VJN3X5KU8ZJ7U9592C7FLD9ZPG72JFPBD36BSZBI58MSYQOONC8VWSC5U9MRJKBW9OKOBP6YB91D47PYH35ATGR5WTPZNG2PY61AE1MNPQGVJKVZ96HM635", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.VQVXRRGPFBT3RUB7OPONU1RQ2691BCKB", "wrongAnswers": ["2.JUHSV1R2IC4F5773S8AP9MZR92L", "3.FB9F3C4NSJ7GGSB0DXA1VW546"], "questionOptions": ["1.VQVXRRGPFBT3RUB7OPONU1RQ2691BCKB", "2.JUHSV1R2IC4F5773S8AP9MZR92L", "3.FB9F3C4NSJ7GGSB0DXA1VW546"], "answerLink": "WTKW08L1SY"}, {"questionId": 458, "questionText": "UL45N99JNFEQGRQ9TLIP63TOVMAK92TKMNVLEN2D169S860XXZZOEPNPFHRCRMCMBMJXZ1EIIQGDMD7T7XEAN4PZZ9GTR52LZSXDOMM", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.ROXAQ4WCGARIATDMA", "wrongAnswers": ["1.U6UPC7N2ELMBZQEM4C532", "3.5DYKMAI6TROFJBMRLLZUE6UZC"], "questionOptions": ["1.U6UPC7N2ELMBZQEM4C532", "2.ROXAQ4WCGARIATDMA", "3.5DYKMAI6TROFJBMRLLZUE6UZC"], "answerLink": "KB2WQ9XGQ0"}, {"questionId": 459, "questionText": "K6VNZBSY6YO8YHD24FHROV5X737BMPBY44ZLFMABJZFL5ZNY3QIFWV7CWHWX22UD38BJGKB22WPK28GB8L7BPQJ0A", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.A518P39DG68C3AX4A1T4BRE", "wrongAnswers": ["2.N0L8419KS3L0FLVV7LK629ARXLXMD61", "3.0LB2DTI7PNBSGUFBVROK"], "questionOptions": ["1.A518P39DG68C3AX4A1T4BRE", "2.N0L8419KS3L0FLVV7LK629ARXLXMD61", "3.0LB2DTI7PNBSGUFBVROK"], "answerLink": "JXXU2TIGS4"}, {"questionId": 460, "questionText": "M19R9D4QSO2QVU0I147ZYTPVFGC5SNYR0ME6CN31I3HBENZIEAQ95FOXIRERZK2JMLAF1ZPNGBKX920NUU7PPZUZPYIIFWKBZOKB", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.ZST701HPU8EN7SLIR772V0S", "wrongAnswers": ["2.8I0PV3Q1QHTA7EM3C3BG", "3.1DEDDOIDA1BK5NK9ANGJ71"], "questionOptions": ["1.ZST701HPU8EN7SLIR772V0S", "2.8I0PV3Q1QHTA7EM3C3BG", "3.1DEDDOIDA1BK5NK9ANGJ71"], "answerLink": "FRQHH7TJ5Z"}, {"questionId": 461, "questionText": "RXT6SIB1VZMT0UA37A0YIP27W6QFRKNNZ08MB6DGAVIXR8U19Z0WPHLR6GFILZ35BMD6M5MHPVVN5C89J1M4FPDW24Z7LRIPIO20HFQY7", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.O82U322J4VE322YTQ", "wrongAnswers": ["2.KB6FJ9BIA86BBJKQLDEAFAK", "3.XDZHSF3JMDUG4D2OXQF"], "questionOptions": ["1.O82U322J4VE322YTQ", "2.KB6FJ9BIA86BBJKQLDEAFAK", "3.XDZHSF3JMDUG4D2OXQF"], "answerLink": "AC8CEBYY57"}, {"questionId": 462, "questionText": "4Z989NWCIIY0DXWCPRSMPMDY3LVT02A1W1L6Z6W6JB7GPTXJURG3050K4W4JSRM8I5557X9B", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.TQ9XU1T2JS8NEIAEFBO7SCM77JOBNYEE", "wrongAnswers": ["2.G66FBM1IPRQJL3VEMCC35PJ15Y721KTV", "3.P1HY8BG2LHS1PA6YNM8"], "questionOptions": ["1.TQ9XU1T2JS8NEIAEFBO7SCM77JOBNYEE", "2.G66FBM1IPRQJL3VEMCC35PJ15Y721KTV", "3.P1HY8BG2LHS1PA6YNM8"], "answerLink": "S1XRJYRUBS"}, {"questionId": 463, "questionText": "P2N9YHE9Y4PM7KT32UKXEUJKFRVZNC8O5OE46J5GRV2KVOI93X3FH0B9B3OWHSZGZ2IRA4B090IUFOYN04", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.WQ7RH9D9O4RACG93WTROZQH5", "wrongAnswers": ["2.1TMI28WYFTIH7W06P7DUE4", "3.K12ZX536ONXEOZPSXK8K"], "questionOptions": ["1.WQ7RH9D9O4RACG93WTROZQH5", "2.1TMI28WYFTIH7W06P7DUE4", "3.K12ZX536ONXEOZPSXK8K"], "answerLink": "S9RWS0MG76"}, {"questionId": 464, "questionText": "H9UFDZNSBQ16KXMDJWPQVDK3Z4J8VIJEURKVS397LRJ80L2FP18SDKNFPOB6PTZWXQEHPYCJYY4WO2CO6316JKBH57HET6LQUXD60YKUK7YWFQ5I4NU", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.DDDYT2UCJVVOJXYSL20I1", "wrongAnswers": ["1.07F7DDNQ42M3HJH5KLV0", "3.VPS6LK0A47NTUDZVSI"], "questionOptions": ["1.07F7DDNQ42M3HJH5KLV0", "2.DDDYT2UCJVVOJXYSL20I1", "3.VPS6LK0A47NTUDZVSI"], "answerLink": "2R5C55USSA"}, {"questionId": 465, "questionText": "M7PY9LMDR58D70HE6JF47MN970ZQ85PYVL96LEE39QG9AAJ8DT4FT1VZLFXCP2FDE81NYZCMXV8O5M3IOWEM7CLZRRZ444Z4WEN4P6AQPDRIHEZWRAT1F2S", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.OVLYPDTDM8JF7FVKKC1N9K2DPU", "wrongAnswers": ["1.4I8706FM36VVLZV81NAW2QIJNTQXGQ", "3.P5HSKNEASQ6NYPFEYXYGAEOWUT1"], "questionOptions": ["1.4I8706FM36VVLZV81NAW2QIJNTQXGQ", "2.OVLYPDTDM8JF7FVKKC1N9K2DPU", "3.P5HSKNEASQ6NYPFEYXYGAEOWUT1"], "answerLink": "98LDB6L8I1"}, {"questionId": 466, "questionText": "WONQE08D2H59PFORVXYR1IISB1U1KCB8IAK9NZKKACZRG1M0RBJ2R8JSNYKOEIHDC394GGUU3HIRG1GXG2", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.SUSA927TQIPTMIOM9M47W9TQ4Z", "wrongAnswers": ["1.OK8C63RUWVJYIQJLVWQ6CI7XE", "3.H458SLF3G0E9LU8882I4O2R5LU"], "questionOptions": ["1.OK8C63RUWVJYIQJLVWQ6CI7XE", "2.SUSA927TQIPTMIOM9M47W9TQ4Z", "3.H458SLF3G0E9LU8882I4O2R5LU"], "answerLink": "NHA5HLSYWP"}, {"questionId": 467, "questionText": "TBT83MIB798J3CL60HNVCBU5BRKZJO2X1H343IJNVBYFUA22Z024NGBG04EN5IXI77BPX28ZBPO637KZV5WIIMFZRK9KWWG14JWKESLT174PGAG417WCIBK", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.ZG47J72KZ3Y5ACX4Q0AMYX32", "wrongAnswers": ["1.EGTQACOEUQ4312XSMJXSXTGPPG46LJX", "2.YG370M759K03RH6D56PURBW"], "questionOptions": ["1.EGTQACOEUQ4312XSMJXSXTGPPG46LJX", "2.YG370M759K03RH6D56PURBW", "3.ZG47J72KZ3Y5ACX4Q0AMYX32"], "answerLink": "L7AAYQZ699"}, {"questionId": 468, "questionText": "TX6JP2PJ181WNKZLAFGWQQX4UYK0WIJLLJNRF8YO8ZVM6KT44Z21D43EJYDL21TWV1OQRFZGZ1IFMQPZOF7I2LF", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.T75JZATL3RQ9CET2", "wrongAnswers": ["1.67DC2XXRGE9TJR3EUA9N59W5DRP", "2.UST1R1480WFANRLIX3LFSW"], "questionOptions": ["1.67DC2XXRGE9TJR3EUA9N59W5DRP", "2.UST1R1480WFANRLIX3LFSW", "3.T75JZATL3RQ9CET2"], "answerLink": "LMA8VXVTHM"}, {"questionId": 469, "questionText": "IQ4BW34P03FZH9B8W8WVQ2IVF2S2LBDKAZDDEVLMI743VNVOYG99QBCH3NWLZ4XVTIKPMQZDSJ80SNK36XNGABZZCN4BWRTB1CQ6U7Y0Q6CPGJVMR5XENJ7A", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.V44PZ8ZTMPP5B1R2F", "wrongAnswers": ["2.HOF1JNCKVH89SBR1KM7WQ8ZQA", "3.3O92S6MVLJRMYN4Z"], "questionOptions": ["1.V44PZ8ZTMPP5B1R2F", "2.HOF1JNCKVH89SBR1KM7WQ8ZQA", "3.3O92S6MVLJRMYN4Z"], "answerLink": "QM41TUY6F8"}, {"questionId": 470, "questionText": "4SI44MAM81B7VO3Y71CKM34CEVDIRH50LD5D25D27PEN5PVRSTXVIB7VJVHVWEJCABD9LBWMAJI9XNPP15W256SVMYBSTQIW7WLRRIG77QDN", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.G66TIPPC239EPGYWDXTJIA4PKHC7C", "wrongAnswers": ["1.7GG43IFKTGYINFCYNBATQJYDXSJXXR", "3.XGYB4PODHX4J1YUJU"], "questionOptions": ["1.7GG43IFKTGYINFCYNBATQJYDXSJXXR", "2.G66TIPPC239EPGYWDXTJIA4PKHC7C", "3.XGYB4PODHX4J1YUJU"], "answerLink": "09JLTE4HTT"}, {"questionId": 471, "questionText": "AWVZE67VFI741FUOOFT0R5VD83C3SADTC9SMDOITZFWDWBPWMZAH6BXWYV2NUK7MJRD739X5J9BO0FN1ZLOFWB3POH997LHKL00I8KEUYTIR1SETSH", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.HLCIDDZF7CFWSN8PMO69KEZQ2CIXL", "wrongAnswers": ["1.LE2BWXIEHGONN4KV", "2.6D8M493G6RB0F62O6FW"], "questionOptions": ["1.LE2BWXIEHGONN4KV", "2.6D8M493G6RB0F62O6FW", "3.HLCIDDZF7CFWSN8PMO69KEZQ2CIXL"], "answerLink": "7FM7ZXYAOZ"}, {"questionId": 472, "questionText": "BOSMKFUH0OD1M21RU454OBCVX10ZQ1T3EML4X8Y201XRZI2RGSARR4OSNO27F1G3AWZBEL9W0XDRTZZ", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.WZV1PGRJHDC8KW83079ZRKUTB0KT", "wrongAnswers": ["2.O2KGUZTJHRUU5D9LIYNONAN58OSV", "3.QJDFWIIRICLQB83PYKCJRD3MPS"], "questionOptions": ["1.WZV1PGRJHDC8KW83079ZRKUTB0KT", "2.O2KGUZTJHRUU5D9LIYNONAN58OSV", "3.QJDFWIIRICLQB83PYKCJRD3MPS"], "answerLink": "TNKX9E4RL1"}, {"questionId": 473, "questionText": "1MGJUKQUYWHZJ2NJN1NY3X9TG5IVPP9IDHTKURSMS7QSKUVDMKZB5BT2L278Z68K87529K9O3XZRDL5243M9BL85OQM0G3SL29WBMK9PU7JSHM1K2KNQIIF152AA54", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.VYWS38614TSVSREOQ3", "wrongAnswers": ["2.1A5AH8F8VKYAJ0Q0YKA", "3.614GIQLKAWBKDEOL9L1YCRI0KVJSB"], "questionOptions": ["1.VYWS38614TSVSREOQ3", "2.1A5AH8F8VKYAJ0Q0YKA", "3.614GIQLKAWBKDEOL9L1YCRI0KVJSB"], "answerLink": "UX3HNFOZL9"}, {"questionId": 474, "questionText": "5UN0FD9Z3HVFZ3WHUOMGL8VWNQUN9GWSDW3DAGASEMNKQTWUH6BW83KQU9JVMJ65KYIKHHD4APXGQPTLKCK9R99OCCOH1NAKS1M6SQLWOZG08H13HA7", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.XXI62ZJIWG7N6IG3HQHOR1KLRPPXU", "wrongAnswers": ["1.PIV0YM8TK9IN8GUO6TSPJ6KWZ3YYQM", "3.VAOUXZHW3OFBFOJJ32VCMZMAU"], "questionOptions": ["1.PIV0YM8TK9IN8GUO6TSPJ6KWZ3YYQM", "2.XXI62ZJIWG7N6IG3HQHOR1KLRPPXU", "3.VAOUXZHW3OFBFOJJ32VCMZMAU"], "answerLink": "MXKGJ73XYL"}, {"questionId": 475, "questionText": "G17RXOH0R2U0IBKIC8UCEMPZBLSH2BXZE8SJVA8A49ZRZ70IVS3BMX8DZILFAWK8COG047WOUP1TP9WONOVLOV9R8T", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.WKNOK2KNUJ8XY7YN7", "wrongAnswers": ["2.FDCK9A3HPBCQX4FPOGCYBH7QKOEPVEU", "3.5FLC0IRKC84TG5UJF2Q0"], "questionOptions": ["1.WKNOK2KNUJ8XY7YN7", "2.FDCK9A3HPBCQX4FPOGCYBH7QKOEPVEU", "3.5FLC0IRKC84TG5UJF2Q0"], "answerLink": "WIOHNI21CZ"}, {"questionId": 476, "questionText": "U8UD9JLKSDOCBXKNO0JZSV03W9OVVRJP9U47RJX8YK43WVCOIHCHAUBJNUMJCZ4KENKI3YRP2RVXYJFKL5", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.WAAXHKKBLFSEKE1Z36I2YWS", "wrongAnswers": ["1.VB7C5OW7K8UOPMDRO4FVN9YG2VDFD3Z", "2.A52OE9CBJKSJA8G5NPE4DKCZNFL7LJ"], "questionOptions": ["1.VB7C5OW7K8UOPMDRO4FVN9YG2VDFD3Z", "2.A52OE9CBJKSJA8G5NPE4DKCZNFL7LJ", "3.WAAXHKKBLFSEKE1Z36I2YWS"], "answerLink": "PJXD0AKSNE"}, {"questionId": 477, "questionText": "XLRVQXMONVRI4WGUY40FKTPIDP0Q89IN3ZYISOXPPXJNC8KMIWRM9M576YSB3GVPK38OKDU5Q8MH32L8KGJ9SRH0HCHHE9DMM7P3YJQFMLFN", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.3R2M0Q39YU7F46AJ9UQH2FR1NLOOFN", "wrongAnswers": ["1.DGSXYOO53R6ZM733QVZU0Z", "3.98HTLANS9DLEAX1MLB36UQAOGWU"], "questionOptions": ["1.DGSXYOO53R6ZM733QVZU0Z", "2.3R2M0Q39YU7F46AJ9UQH2FR1NLOOFN", "3.98HTLANS9DLEAX1MLB36UQAOGWU"], "answerLink": "5YGHH3OIY9"}, {"questionId": 478, "questionText": "VVTQS9MOIWZC79G8Z98W215IUVKEBJ6J1HDYFW0UJHLU7ULKDAU418H55RB9UKHKX878SNWEDB6LY205SMVQ5R458D1KOTNJA3S834", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.IIX01MM4O4MWMT4VNPZ9A66JOW", "wrongAnswers": ["1.SH52VV3GZWTPFERXSHW6EGUWURQ", "2.OZV92EYW7W6UTSGPJCNWK2"], "questionOptions": ["1.SH52VV3GZWTPFERXSHW6EGUWURQ", "2.OZV92EYW7W6UTSGPJCNWK2", "3.IIX01MM4O4MWMT4VNPZ9A66JOW"], "answerLink": "OENEE7DHEX"}, {"questionId": 479, "questionText": "MI9S65OB4WEW3W1YAC62ONZ7BTMR8F7URSVOL18LQN1TUBMVW8YJ0YN5NWN3FCH0B0ECOZ1G", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.I30GR0RIZ3TY7PQPZAZY79QTFDT561ZH", "wrongAnswers": ["2.ZB99FCWCTU2OV51ATDB6ZB2", "3.QYQELW6PFQFAJSGYWW583EW1K"], "questionOptions": ["1.I30GR0RIZ3TY7PQPZAZY79QTFDT561ZH", "2.ZB99FCWCTU2OV51ATDB6ZB2", "3.QYQELW6PFQFAJSGYWW583EW1K"], "answerLink": "7Y3VTKTQYA"}, {"questionId": 480, "questionText": "V2I78MMD9Q5I684LU8V4KPUH82BM23W92NDW2BXFYSXFRI2LCA2YX4UYLRAS4S7QLT7VYZM8EM0D1MTEVI61ZINCAHE3BO7R08N2S4", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.XKLRL6GO726K1A04Q27NHI9SE", "wrongAnswers": ["1.JTKULWCW8H7XOG3I2RYV0ZJFMOED", "2.MJT6C80DIG89LPH3OEIOF7AAHRAGT"], "questionOptions": ["1.JTKULWCW8H7XOG3I2RYV0ZJFMOED", "2.MJT6C80DIG89LPH3OEIOF7AAHRAGT", "3.XKLRL6GO726K1A04Q27NHI9SE"], "answerLink": "RENUAJWHVT"}, {"questionId": 481, "questionText": "B4NFPNZ3AB5QA9OOEP9NPN1JO27N0ERKKZ1NT9JKMZDC750OQ4V33YV85MBTV9H8GO6QWNJYJ", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.QY39CTZP4MFJLX0EP9P75A761ME3G9", "wrongAnswers": ["2.ODUKQ25WDA6PZJIBQZ34FUZA", "3.S97R6BCIP83LNJ3OW"], "questionOptions": ["1.QY39CTZP4MFJLX0EP9P75A761ME3G9", "2.ODUKQ25WDA6PZJIBQZ34FUZA", "3.S97R6BCIP83LNJ3OW"], "answerLink": "KH7E1C318U"}, {"questionId": 482, "questionText": "PWGE94BLLGQT4W0HLZIQBIA0UWDH1GVC5M2S7X4B7782N6FT7271EDVWU2M3PFCWL99HQ9IPF0E8CTJ7TZSAIFFO9GCG4DOX5ABOSZ5MK0", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.YU4M8DZI7H301QX1ZNAUZ9MM9JPZ", "wrongAnswers": ["2.4V7PK6CF0P45I1UPZ7D", "3.R2GFQEBA3YEGIJ2ISJSRN"], "questionOptions": ["1.YU4M8DZI7H301QX1ZNAUZ9MM9JPZ", "2.4V7PK6CF0P45I1UPZ7D", "3.R2GFQEBA3YEGIJ2ISJSRN"], "answerLink": "4FL922FSV8"}, {"questionId": 483, "questionText": "FWK3JIFK5JZXF5XP8F6OMVCG4YWZOVHV8QRCDQP0QG3E3JTUNUGTPNNTEC3MIIWSIWIBACTQVB3DK27FXXXTFQT", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "2.BQVRVCRNYDZ0LCDF1F6EOSH4C9BDI", "wrongAnswers": ["1.AEM56COLFWEZTCHJGHKUR73CLWT0L", "3.NJ5LPOLJWA53JOXX"], "questionOptions": ["1.AEM56COLFWEZTCHJGHKUR73CLWT0L", "2.BQVRVCRNYDZ0LCDF1F6EOSH4C9BDI", "3.NJ5LPOLJWA53JOXX"], "answerLink": "LSPYVYBJBO"}, {"questionId": 484, "questionText": "M5MSJ7NAPLGU58QVDKZZ5WE3KRWQ464FQDVMSEXRVSIGQ8TF6OBFGY9SWNN91CLYYTNWTDOYCPNYKIVW3KZXS", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.70BY9DLFCAGGBME036SLERH", "wrongAnswers": ["2.T81KN88MM67AV84LR9GAXS0H4J", "3.KZBIPGQW1E1RXUAJ9Q6F2IT45H2TLD"], "questionOptions": ["1.70BY9DLFCAGGBME036SLERH", "2.T81KN88MM67AV84LR9GAXS0H4J", "3.KZBIPGQW1E1RXUAJ9Q6F2IT45H2TLD"], "answerLink": "2LFZXWGCYB"}, {"questionId": 485, "questionText": "E3QXUA5M7ABK6CXQ8UMFCK4TRTM4AG6XQR61J2KJ77KP3X6N5CYHZ96C1H3470Q3P", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "3.RIQMR0JZHFCYG278ZFD", "wrongAnswers": ["1.LU5QBM41VL04GUYHW6LHPCG8VN3YKU", "2.G9VKGF3B1AC4ZLHNOIG4SXJ23QPDQV3O"], "questionOptions": ["1.LU5QBM41VL04GUYHW6LHPCG8VN3YKU", "2.G9VKGF3B1AC4ZLHNOIG4SXJ23QPDQV3O", "3.RIQMR0JZHFCYG278ZFD"], "answerLink": "VN91LYYPGU"}, {"questionId": 486, "questionText": "NN6BBEJD6FK3SMC6W2QR6FG2Z585SWIA33SCJIRANWDER425D3MIZYO3MJ93WF4BXL6I48HRFB", "questionCategory": "Regola 12", "correctAnswers": "1.B0GWWKM323L0ULPERYMEM7HBVN50L", "wrongAnswers": ["2.R7N3HEO7SSOOWPCB2EV", "3.K1DSJ66B7H43HATA3EOGZMYQ2ZGBU"], "questionOptions": ["1.B0GWWKM323L0ULPERYMEM7HBVN50L", "2.R7N3HEO7SSOOWPCB2EV", "3.K1DSJ66B7H43HATA3EOGZMYQ2ZGBU"], "answerLink": "CYGS802I99"}, {"questionId": 487, "questionText": "66H03UUGHPJ3ZIOK2GH4RWZR628TAM31M9G853WFSZJZ2TQKHMX4K1O2PXSNGKNF18KKW", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "3.XRYU0GH42RB6XRCHXCDO9L5MBO3Y5", "wrongAnswers": ["1.RIF7I8XPRTRNPBTTMSSHCNFM8", "2.6E97O411W382DYDWEA5CY3"], "questionOptions": ["1.RIF7I8XPRTRNPBTTMSSHCNFM8", "2.6E97O411W382DYDWEA5CY3", "3.XRYU0GH42RB6XRCHXCDO9L5MBO3Y5"], "answerLink": "XXU643X1XO"}, {"questionId": 488, "questionText": "HMXG7T00MKEX3GLCV1GQ3EVA5C6VA42EJC23GXRYR96JMKZD78KWDAJ0OQLVMK6L5CLU51JA8XPRODATF", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "2.VT1ALA4W6H0RK76OCKVMUV9IQY9K", "wrongAnswers": ["1.CJKJU5HO7A1Y0LH38PIH8OUG9I", "3.5AI32E7RZCFXJ8388P"], "questionOptions": ["1.CJKJU5HO7A1Y0LH38PIH8OUG9I", "2.VT1ALA4W6H0RK76OCKVMUV9IQY9K", "3.5AI32E7RZCFXJ8388P"], "answerLink": "M4KG7GT7OU"}, {"questionId": 489, "questionText": "X1808TXLPBZUPY3PTIYQGFQ3CGAYQPD52HOXTKE9OR6MGJG735X7KKBWM6FDUX5TW8Z", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "3.ZM58WOD1YI5U0KRYP87MA8NQ0", "wrongAnswers": ["1.2JKZXOTUB8ID2WO1S", "2.9ZNIP533VTK6TS2H"], "questionOptions": ["1.2JKZXOTUB8ID2WO1S", "2.9ZNIP533VTK6TS2H", "3.ZM58WOD1YI5U0KRYP87MA8NQ0"], "answerLink": "H727W3JKXS"}, {"questionId": 490, "questionText": "9SAKX7IFG22PFJNMY4N5PLZ3SUUIY4VW51Q0OCWX15RRRRCF9M79UY261FM77ITBWOOJ12CWZ1N3WW2", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "2.0VTIO5OGOO9FFG0L92R", "wrongAnswers": ["1.OSJVTGSDIIWL0VQHT4XEAFI0MNI", "3.MM9JH169GH74LFAUNXDP8"], "questionOptions": ["1.OSJVTGSDIIWL0VQHT4XEAFI0MNI", "2.0VTIO5OGOO9FFG0L92R", "3.MM9JH169GH74LFAUNXDP8"], "answerLink": "HBXVQBV1XX"}, {"questionId": 491, "questionText": "WJCR5Q6YH79NCLGHKZHEOS4R51A7F5ZTS1RA3A38S1KWF1Q3EXQ4OVWQ43O3E0OBGQF8MZYKYOIL8IUP699V06NH7UHZQSZQZVPAZRYY55IPCH3X8IXMCF4BYTW7OK", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "3.GM5DLMV79X7WYHJT9D6413ZGCN9G", "wrongAnswers": ["1.ZUGERVV0YGNKZ9WRIPPDJ", "2.42X8P222NCVO8NYUXYNSTRP70BP5"], "questionOptions": ["1.ZUGERVV0YGNKZ9WRIPPDJ", "2.42X8P222NCVO8NYUXYNSTRP70BP5", "3.GM5DLMV79X7WYHJT9D6413ZGCN9G"], "answerLink": "DZBX22FDCP"}, {"questionId": 492, "questionText": "P3U0JV4S84G5U636D34M2ZO0Z3D5HXD6DEC7NJ00B38LLHDFCDNEGL2UTH6Y4G8T9XOHSWBH8D35R", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "1.11AVH6AKJ8DWQ6QHUQS1XM4MOMA", "wrongAnswers": ["2.H9VFGR2O93FDOA7DQBKQ86KL2UU3658", "3.9NFZX4WVCD370YAOTR97YUKV8RPW7QJC"], "questionOptions": ["1.11AVH6AKJ8DWQ6QHUQS1XM4MOMA", "2.H9VFGR2O93FDOA7DQBKQ86KL2UU3658", "3.9NFZX4WVCD370YAOTR97YUKV8RPW7QJC"], "answerLink": "D9OEVTKKGL"}, {"questionId": 493, "questionText": "TVX8VZWWS08NFUEJJ2VMLAWCFUXNUXQUUWXS25348B5MZQVNX2D2KX629GHAFMX7F9OC21A87T4ICPKE91U6QAPGH7ODEAUZLT9406MFL5N29C250", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "3.RPBDZM0OU41A46HBV", "wrongAnswers": ["1.A95827GW773OYD1LS6YQ3LAB", "2.X0R8UHM493YC89CF4QWXHXVXPFMSIP"], "questionOptions": ["1.A95827GW773OYD1LS6YQ3LAB", "2.X0R8UHM493YC89CF4QWXHXVXPFMSIP", "3.RPBDZM0OU41A46HBV"], "answerLink": "53Z19SD5Q6"}, {"questionId": 494, "questionText": "EVOK5V4YWN4A7JFOW3M0G0GAVIG55XVEITX7VNWL7HCLLMG8CGDWA33UCW0YS02DHJIR4112WT1HY9OM3WU7ZJY42SD5GTM7XZHI6UIDIISAB7Y", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "2.88OF9ZFBZSJ7POAULPXRQJBP4BV", "wrongAnswers": ["1.O6GI7SOJZG104I6E9", "3.B1AC8B6RA1462TMNBG8"], "questionOptions": ["1.O6GI7SOJZG104I6E9", "2.88OF9ZFBZSJ7POAULPXRQJBP4BV", "3.B1AC8B6RA1462TMNBG8"], "answerLink": "L9P2HVQ91W"}, {"questionId": 495, "questionText": "OVJUP8LRCYLVGYD5W5AS13TV9U6D62PLZVQMZH3PVPS5FKI48BS7UE4MS7G6RK6IY26J3", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "2.KKIJEVX6PG3NHS46", "wrongAnswers": ["1.BFPE38VLQMBVAUPRQKW", "3.4AFMP46WAS3CC0NH0NLMYNISSCO"], "questionOptions": ["1.BFPE38VLQMBVAUPRQKW", "2.KKIJEVX6PG3NHS46", "3.4AFMP46WAS3CC0NH0NLMYNISSCO"], "answerLink": "9QLOWNNPVR"}, {"questionId": 496, "questionText": "WIZMCUR1K502D1IMHCERPF655126DTEYPXBBCE6MI66YXK213MO1DASEHFVQ1QPOIH0PVR2FCI8XGDZKMZM04K66X8NHWS1KZCUYLM9564LRU", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "1.1XXLXDUYX6TAVSQ9B6T82648MK2OL7", "wrongAnswers": ["2.4N21ZPXFW7V8KNDANO", "3.F4YX9MFG9JUL6U9IJU3J"], "questionOptions": ["1.1XXLXDUYX6TAVSQ9B6T82648MK2OL7", "2.4N21ZPXFW7V8KNDANO", "3.F4YX9MFG9JUL6U9IJU3J"], "answerLink": "DGD6YJ7BGK"}, {"questionId": 497, "questionText": "SAYHG1R0P8CRRJYUE80P24FJLSBTSE94G1NVE66P80Y14M93XV7Y72ZZHCJP02PHXOHNAZPN4N28376KJOLKIYBBDM7LJ", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "2.NEF4MOOIFIS8NVNDI32NYZV59", "wrongAnswers": ["1.OOPM6NPWY3S0EBS9T", "3.T3TE01A45UUPCAOW7XTA"], "questionOptions": ["1.OOPM6NPWY3S0EBS9T", "2.NEF4MOOIFIS8NVNDI32NYZV59", "3.T3TE01A45UUPCAOW7XTA"], "answerLink": "I4CEIFR1H2"}, {"questionId": 498, "questionText": "0ZJK6OOE4A455TQJVN7UXH2VLM8EZVSXG14MO8NA84XJ01WPFL57D1KI6BFM4G704NLE94JX5ALQD2F8AZ14ZH8KL86XGXRXNDAU", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "3.SSGI3FNZ0ZQSUOTY8HYC33EZS5", "wrongAnswers": ["1.GRGW1MMMU0XPP8P9UOX1IH3", "2.3O8CBG1MFF2X6T9PD8Q8I"], "questionOptions": ["1.GRGW1MMMU0XPP8P9UOX1IH3", "2.3O8CBG1MFF2X6T9PD8Q8I", "3.SSGI3FNZ0ZQSUOTY8HYC33EZS5"], "answerLink": "U3N1X8SL9A"}, {"questionId": 499, "questionText": "RKU1J2CV2IF7GN0ESCI56L03E6YOZMDNEPV0RW4VXQE0U8OUN136OOIV24ZKK0K5SIBN0QXVFB9LC2R75DK0BQMGBRBY17K7OL9JY2WSZQZQ7R7K7G6ZEJSTYWKB5Q", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "2.YPXJHIGG34F5G3SX94H0V", "wrongAnswers": ["1.GU32P0ZPCNLGT3FXO9JM2DO", "3.CUEVNQAK8N1BC2AKBTHW"], "questionOptions": ["1.GU32P0ZPCNLGT3FXO9JM2DO", "2.YPXJHIGG34F5G3SX94H0V", "3.CUEVNQAK8N1BC2AKBTHW"], "answerLink": "BJYX18JNHZ"}, {"questionId": 500, "questionText": "R06DB48IXIOYOFTR4NUTNP5YXAJQEIOG9OT7YSPOMQRMSCAEC8NUR5OG7S5C6K0O", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "2.3RRE3I52PRHFEWGSUBC7W90YADWS9", "wrongAnswers": ["1.GFIS3FQNQZ6TILX0J9LEVQ", "3.S7C6AIGUT9GK43WNYUS8FPYFX6B2WKKC"], "questionOptions": ["1.GFIS3FQNQZ6TILX0J9LEVQ", "2.3RRE3I52PRHFEWGSUBC7W90YADWS9", "3.S7C6AIGUT9GK43WNYUS8FPYFX6B2WKKC"], "answerLink": "PFAT67V30V"}, {"questionId": 501, "questionText": "7BM6BAWTWBS0WKTILOZZUDI4GXHXLX4RN9Z485MD8JLRTADYAJ47BPTZCROJAYPO066E78Y984V0945A29D2NYNRC7ET8LS1", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "3.LO0PR6BS58BY614LQB7I89ROG", "wrongAnswers": ["1.S1EFTIK89V0AW59IHX2L659HEZM2QRJ", "2.KLBXG5E8VPUB7ESYL4PB3UK"], "questionOptions": ["1.S1EFTIK89V0AW59IHX2L659HEZM2QRJ", "2.KLBXG5E8VPUB7ESYL4PB3UK", "3.LO0PR6BS58BY614LQB7I89ROG"], "answerLink": "KRK4YSYO6Y"}, {"questionId": 502, "questionText": "6PZ389JXVZQAFGNU1JV9N0KXUPEB783CZNED4TOL77PSPV76HYY7BAF6NZLTJJ53CF86TCMOH3G0KS3Q3RC75XNIOSMM9", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "2.ICZSJ2V0EDC4QS4IDAIG61", "wrongAnswers": ["1.ODOPECRYMTE0S10YH4T6VBOA", "3.KF8HIC6U8CSB52GM"], "questionOptions": ["1.ODOPECRYMTE0S10YH4T6VBOA", "2.ICZSJ2V0EDC4QS4IDAIG61", "3.KF8HIC6U8CSB52GM"], "answerLink": "G24YPHDRJ5"}, {"questionId": 503, "questionText": "0XDD06W0DOHJBUXMNO6DZALR8KAEGYZMGJSMNELYTR6QFO4PUF0CQMDQ5DY46FPM2VF507UBXBANEJHYENXN7GM1J36P8VRB8NXAWRDKF15BPOP6410A7E8", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "2.X5WN6GNLYIAVYAPKI7KI", "wrongAnswers": ["1.9KNK6TF02F6IPSQ2SRA", "3.WX4BB2ZUP0UYRDAI8GN6011J7PB"], "questionOptions": ["1.9KNK6TF02F6IPSQ2SRA", "2.X5WN6GNLYIAVYAPKI7KI", "3.WX4BB2ZUP0UYRDAI8GN6011J7PB"], "answerLink": "NSD2KTZSF6"}, {"questionId": 504, "questionText": "1K8PMXE2ZUNAWOHFSXTYD9L0EH8SKPVJV4MZEWUEP3HQ8Y4085FPIPDC5OBKX5YGFK4", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "2.Y7FDQADHC5G6BUYL2TKOVKEWCK8FT", "wrongAnswers": ["1.LF57HHTBX8D4PAQO9EAZ5OKW8L9", "3.13KCU3P08K3XB0QLCI6QN"], "questionOptions": ["1.LF57HHTBX8D4PAQO9EAZ5OKW8L9", "2.Y7FDQADHC5G6BUYL2TKOVKEWCK8FT", "3.13KCU3P08K3XB0QLCI6QN"], "answerLink": "23X8JBYM0T"}, {"questionId": 505, "questionText": "1FMWJVMXNOAH9ZNS6NAG7L43JEDWU4U1UBL4KTBEC58TG2MNRF50OTXCFXZ67EOEIVC2PVENB2QRPVJ8I65OJW", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "1.4FRLVGE08UL9R5GOLC0NK", "wrongAnswers": ["2.GAM2P4KSIC9P13DSZEXTEU1F8LU", "3.KGFAUESTSZYCKXZZOSI8H97685YM7K1"], "questionOptions": ["1.4FRLVGE08UL9R5GOLC0NK", "2.GAM2P4KSIC9P13DSZEXTEU1F8LU", "3.KGFAUESTSZYCKXZZOSI8H97685YM7K1"], "answerLink": "Y0XKLQORMS"}, {"questionId": 506, "questionText": "Y6X6KXE7JEPBY3CTQVO59TNDC2VLIBU0ZISWY1AIKAOB1F3O177W9UVBMOSO1XJ9WZ8WNN4VTBZFNUWSEUNC9FSTDRUTDI2XBZBI3OOZ1R", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "2.LISLNX5XKDJVRIAYXYKRKS", "wrongAnswers": ["1.C5UZFUASPPPG8MXJFCJ16TWSG0O6XS8", "3.BMTC47LVOS2VEEKU7M1U"], "questionOptions": ["1.C5UZFUASPPPG8MXJFCJ16TWSG0O6XS8", "2.LISLNX5XKDJVRIAYXYKRKS", "3.BMTC47LVOS2VEEKU7M1U"], "answerLink": "M81TWWMBNC"}, {"questionId": 507, "questionText": "ARIQRLYV375Q76C1TNWMCQNL71ZJ16DND3FC4AAVGQ7PT0AEDGEJ7Q6UZBPNVE26", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "3.EIFJDR5T9LKO5H6DKWVUT", "wrongAnswers": ["1.CM63AYG3PLRI22DE7M8URY7KU4BMSX", "2.KTHMALWOJHJ9ZSF1586FPF"], "questionOptions": ["1.CM63AYG3PLRI22DE7M8URY7KU4BMSX", "2.KTHMALWOJHJ9ZSF1586FPF", "3.EIFJDR5T9LKO5H6DKWVUT"], "answerLink": "TCPB38WZ7O"}, {"questionId": 508, "questionText": "Q6JLR3K7CKN2L0F3T9RS6L4IKTHNGO7OQ06FC7CQQIRR3A6SJYFMTYMCRE2O41KYT024SINFLK17SR9L8R71F42F49JA1C6YIKRLP6D0BV9Y9V26RHLWGFGAG", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "3.2RA2KS0MBDVY245A", "wrongAnswers": ["1.CG85AGP4I673QZK05MPCMBLZJE", "2.PXGKRPD3YA2TH8T6KKBNJI1O7SMGT"], "questionOptions": ["1.CG85AGP4I673QZK05MPCMBLZJE", "2.PXGKRPD3YA2TH8T6KKBNJI1O7SMGT", "3.2RA2KS0MBDVY245A"], "answerLink": "2525MO50I2"}, {"questionId": 509, "questionText": "NTIZPT5E91JHJ7SDKN1MKNQ1OW4F4AOEWVNHLRSV8LN7IQ97K2HZ5FS3VW052H3TXZPEZ5ER43TSCRL4UGI5NFMDRODC29OKFLWWS9GU4G", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "2.K8GE54RO3CJNIR1J4W4", "wrongAnswers": ["1.SGMHFFN3Z7TZ7D3SRDJE7", "3.9EB3VLY1BJHXLZZVXTYV68K3BZ"], "questionOptions": ["1.SGMHFFN3Z7TZ7D3SRDJE7", "2.K8GE54RO3CJNIR1J4W4", "3.9EB3VLY1BJHXLZZVXTYV68K3BZ"], "answerLink": "PAP0BATEU0"}, {"questionId": 510, "questionText": "6O28IDAXMN02C3XUNZ7D9XWOIAI11TUA23UK6QMTG8CCAQ52JOAAUUS4JPPN7KYWQN", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "1.5BV5P8ID31RHNH7UMH4KA6HY49R", "wrongAnswers": ["2.G58AX5RRN55Z4ABM442UZZ2W75", "3.JTF8XODY9LZT89I71NA"], "questionOptions": ["1.5BV5P8ID31RHNH7UMH4KA6HY49R", "2.G58AX5RRN55Z4ABM442UZZ2W75", "3.JTF8XODY9LZT89I71NA"], "answerLink": "R8SI347VLM"}, {"questionId": 511, "questionText": "SEVVBH0RS0P835NV8LW6ZP25S2QE7GBHDUBRLDC12XNIXDBHHAC8DQAZ2RXBAKS0JKB8TXYT6PYMJ9K21W1YA604PII20GF5Y97G51Y6", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "1.PJ8N27CLSXOLDSYOQR46NLL6EMR0A9U", "wrongAnswers": ["2.3OGFUCXW0CQIDIY2WFI4N", "3.5VCKNCIUFQ9IY4EI6T504TR1CTG"], "questionOptions": ["1.PJ8N27CLSXOLDSYOQR46NLL6EMR0A9U", "2.3OGFUCXW0CQIDIY2WFI4N", "3.5VCKNCIUFQ9IY4EI6T504TR1CTG"], "answerLink": "SRNIKRAC0E"}, {"questionId": 512, "questionText": "HPXCYDIJOGNRDGJ8YQET595APC702ZXRG9OJKOY7A7X9HAT20P9YCI97MJHB68Q7XNVJ6WOOGAD3UONAZSJZ7D3R1T5W8YUTUDLC6YKQNDDGOMKHS1LYHYA", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "3.9L9DGE6AW5BFRO62DN5WORX4", "wrongAnswers": ["1.TLDUSN5C1W2W8X6M6LX1OZ2U9BY3V", "2.4HM9K3M1OKE2BDAZY"], "questionOptions": ["1.TLDUSN5C1W2W8X6M6LX1OZ2U9BY3V", "2.4HM9K3M1OKE2BDAZY", "3.9L9DGE6AW5BFRO62DN5WORX4"], "answerLink": "13II04CAXU"}, {"questionId": 513, "questionText": "JIYX1HK9PVWNAOMI4E83HY80PBIL7I5GOL0OX8U422UOB8ICSPWK9NXN34540KJDS62V08H7H91L0SKEF10EW1QQ2TIX53ZURVIQ", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "1.WQD6E1GZIP5X4SQ26JIWYZ3", "wrongAnswers": ["2.RVAVRGH72JEBS0DCHJOBBU1O1IU", "3.1836S8S3LBD8X4QZBO37UXQJ28PA"], "questionOptions": ["1.WQD6E1GZIP5X4SQ26JIWYZ3", "2.RVAVRGH72JEBS0DCHJOBBU1O1IU", "3.1836S8S3LBD8X4QZBO37UXQJ28PA"], "answerLink": "STESS0QQ85"}, {"questionId": 514, "questionText": "QZTYT5L20GRSJ5OTFN7AK3RR1AAXEJXPBNC2BQJOOHNAFG89YTZF8LBZVIU9JR604YZXS04ACNX7NWU876XDQGRL61TV6BVCBO6PS5V2SAVK5P0SMR6BMQU9E1A6", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "3.NRS0G0VWHB24LNCT7WAD1A7WVGKC", "wrongAnswers": ["1.RZ2K3KZYYLW868SF6IE33DQHXKW0S5Y", "2.OGJFLVVLDKCUYCN2WWO1WA"], "questionOptions": ["1.RZ2K3KZYYLW868SF6IE33DQHXKW0S5Y", "2.OGJFLVVLDKCUYCN2WWO1WA", "3.NRS0G0VWHB24LNCT7WAD1A7WVGKC"], "answerLink": "V5G53OOZ77"}, {"questionId": 515, "questionText": "A2FNX0SLC9L47UUUOPTCUY998L7ADJIFN82SJOAA4QRVN9PO410E1FEA3POJU55UMXOFIZFG0OAGW432EATOXUOVVGSL8YBYL9CMUB", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "3.I17VPXWFE596VOZFTD8W0PJ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.O65XB1Y9JL9WP5XVVF0JKSPYFV", "2.ELIQYSD8NAK7WKEEV26V0A79IVQR"], "questionOptions": ["1.O65XB1Y9JL9WP5XVVF0JKSPYFV", "2.ELIQYSD8NAK7WKEEV26V0A79IVQR", "3.I17VPXWFE596VOZFTD8W0PJ"], "answerLink": "Y6DZJP0YEJ"}, {"questionId": 516, "questionText": "1EBG3C7GUOJM3L33B3ZS4JZ1V50EHFC78WAMGBPR3VHL8012ZNX80TU2G12N87K1CP6AFSLL0Z8RX9MZVQHZPYZ673WH43Z2RU", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "2.LOHNB86SRJ0V8L87CR6LDW", "wrongAnswers": ["1.954XBYLYN3MD4FU1N", "3.ELT7012II39P5K1IB"], "questionOptions": ["1.954XBYLYN3MD4FU1N", "2.LOHNB86SRJ0V8L87CR6LDW", "3.ELT7012II39P5K1IB"], "answerLink": "0MWPPOQJRX"}, {"questionId": 517, "questionText": "U110LLT5706XMRKFZE70D4WKGGLVKKSEH5ADU6O308X24L2UOHT6WD79P7PZTKDH1BROGCE2ZWXV8AJNUA3Z57MMCPNE02ZCJXGHG5", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "2.Z8B6DBTGEOFLOSKAZ7BDIKOG2P019DK", "wrongAnswers": ["1.VEMIY1I0QON6ME95H", "3.JGW0Z0KEN3PBT1M27RL"], "questionOptions": ["1.VEMIY1I0QON6ME95H", "2.Z8B6DBTGEOFLOSKAZ7BDIKOG2P019DK", "3.JGW0Z0KEN3PBT1M27RL"], "answerLink": "CL96QQFC2A"}, {"questionId": 518, "questionText": "QBLT9CZGT7QGYUJUWDUFPGKD08I3BBM0HWWN1DFWSJ7UFK065M0DZFDCPMJBVQQG16I2RDSX91C4", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "3.06I4G11XKVOPQ9LEZ40IK9C1", "wrongAnswers": ["1.P4AGFV7JE1ESGA8JS2ESWYYEKREJD", "2.HIB6ZBJ9LJLHZQ044Z6O"], "questionOptions": ["1.P4AGFV7JE1ESGA8JS2ESWYYEKREJD", "2.HIB6ZBJ9LJLHZQ044Z6O", "3.06I4G11XKVOPQ9LEZ40IK9C1"], "answerLink": "GXYGTN5NR5"}, {"questionId": 519, "questionText": "6SB1J2D01GN1PO60X45DXYQWAH74UFIZHI8PMXGH00NDHWHXIPNCYCY6ACEDPW9CJ2AXL26W45VB53DCT", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "2.CWFWKSTFTV0AP6A1ABNQYX2DADDVC", "wrongAnswers": ["1.I0XDAGOC8PVVUCP2", "3.VKMWEZ7XQE8EYLWD9JTY8"], "questionOptions": ["1.I0XDAGOC8PVVUCP2", "2.CWFWKSTFTV0AP6A1ABNQYX2DADDVC", "3.VKMWEZ7XQE8EYLWD9JTY8"], "answerLink": "QWKCD9F3K6"}, {"questionId": 520, "questionText": "M4ZJFJ6KXFDZURS06J5VIOOAGMI92XAKLTP7J69JAFIV2157O4A5LFY5HYGVVLDJZ6HZXBMHTFB0157JXGL2VCD", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "1.EOKJIO6NMTPMNQVKSOLIUY73D9KERS", "wrongAnswers": ["2.0CSKN3X45Y4S4A7QJ0CM67A5HUX", "3.ZW1FGC2WZGMQNDNQWOAY0"], "questionOptions": ["1.EOKJIO6NMTPMNQVKSOLIUY73D9KERS", "2.0CSKN3X45Y4S4A7QJ0CM67A5HUX", "3.ZW1FGC2WZGMQNDNQWOAY0"], "answerLink": "8PRJT2JGDP"}, {"questionId": 521, "questionText": "TMRCL8947DGCLUTBDPM8YD137H5A1AODG4DT9SD1SKG5BDZBSVVE8RVNB0VIZRNOLW97KCHTL3ICT65MH69GX", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "3.XQMW8XA0LN69K7JW272MTBUCRV", "wrongAnswers": ["1.CSZREILY89RNQD039TAM3FMKZW7ISU", "2.447VSQUB02MGLA2BVRYD4G0OMUSR"], "questionOptions": ["1.CSZREILY89RNQD039TAM3FMKZW7ISU", "2.447VSQUB02MGLA2BVRYD4G0OMUSR", "3.XQMW8XA0LN69K7JW272MTBUCRV"], "answerLink": "6KL2LMY4I8"}, {"questionId": 522, "questionText": "464TWB9XSSK6HFO4PHUJ2LF9VH4WBQ62IHXV7QXCA4Z8MF4BVP2IBNGTBFZ1LAC0Y1UXJ826RLLZKOB81JZSGOT97GHG2XR6OGIFIH8TH3WADIP2JXKQ2J7D5", "questionCategory": "Regola 13", "correctAnswers": "3.0JJXI5OBDLPFN7IYICKKP", "wrongAnswers": ["1.VYP9N7GLF46PZJRX5BD", "2.5ZDQN1PLQVN3D7WL7X11G"], "questionOptions": ["1.VYP9N7GLF46PZJRX5BD", "2.5ZDQN1PLQVN3D7WL7X11G", "3.0JJXI5OBDLPFN7IYICKKP"], "answerLink": "LF3LYJQTX1"}, {"questionId": 523, "questionText": "2KDHAAEZC3JJ093P7CROL50JJDO2DMORTZJBADCUKXBLHZLLIHW9D3DKJF7HB078T65N6SA4UF0LVUGWYWOR4MCC4X71XJF9YBR2SBMOFM2IKERSI8", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "1.ZBRTT78YZ9K5ISA3E4H", "wrongAnswers": ["2.28ERUAUWH8E36QG31AMD8TQ6PNAWL", "3.6HSYAJA86WHIMG8ZPT6"], "questionOptions": ["1.ZBRTT78YZ9K5ISA3E4H", "2.28ERUAUWH8E36QG31AMD8TQ6PNAWL", "3.6HSYAJA86WHIMG8ZPT6"], "answerLink": "RJIO6AQDVR"}, {"questionId": 524, "questionText": "PRUX3OYF6V0KZTRUVJKTSVT94VOJMP3DKSX7YG7JVM0LDB5IHOBYD1T3BKHLDM3YWTBXBDJB2IZK1FYFJW90G", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "1.15X7LJTTA4O47JLP9QJNH", "wrongAnswers": ["2.32EGRZ7WN53DD098UOH", "3.8Q3HFZZ8T8ZACORNLM16IMWYEYG"], "questionOptions": ["1.15X7LJTTA4O47JLP9QJNH", "2.32EGRZ7WN53DD098UOH", "3.8Q3HFZZ8T8ZACORNLM16IMWYEYG"], "answerLink": "XL3U8BQRLN"}, {"questionId": 525, "questionText": "BEAFPCBVQQ2MVVTDMFS79X6WFSSB53U9ELQ47AM6K592MSFIZM7LTTCGMR19J5DA034TCON39AWQT2K772QBM0YO5O3E9523", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "3.941XQCVUS5MFVK3BWOPREG8UTWER33", "wrongAnswers": ["1.UDDPJQEVU3INCSR8DXEAEY10YQK", "2.V13KYAEKKA9IOYI0A21H3C"], "questionOptions": ["1.UDDPJQEVU3INCSR8DXEAEY10YQK", "2.V13KYAEKKA9IOYI0A21H3C", "3.941XQCVUS5MFVK3BWOPREG8UTWER33"], "answerLink": "4BA5I86RWF"}, {"questionId": 526, "questionText": "5OM73AO17M67UP80I1A09KYPDF5DM1SLBBT694LZIZX83TO5S6YWVNCQ1BX6OZQ96P451196YO2RWJUDZPYWW82U26TF991OUHFUW3SP9HDLDUPO8HGHYJJGOPTYLL", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "1.GL288AI835J32157RT6WXKUHC1", "wrongAnswers": ["2.KJYMMUB74ANPR6ZJ14IFR9CM", "3.U8VQLLLX7TOH0ISEDAJEM11M6PG"], "questionOptions": ["1.GL288AI835J32157RT6WXKUHC1", "2.KJYMMUB74ANPR6ZJ14IFR9CM", "3.U8VQLLLX7TOH0ISEDAJEM11M6PG"], "answerLink": "83CK2Y8SSA"}, {"questionId": 527, "questionText": "TE4OQDPF7Q77PVWPXRAY2Y75CT0VUIR1K1Q7WDUL45UTGRT6Y96NHHWHVGZHI2PWN9JU4TMFAOE1QYO87HC3JD7LQGSQNE839F5OP", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "1.JGZ3Q7FESD00OSXX96WLOT", "wrongAnswers": ["2.D5AV7FUHX1JQ4QLQ5CHB73XA7WUZUA6V", "3.M16V1L05ED5TN2LIZ1MA"], "questionOptions": ["1.JGZ3Q7FESD00OSXX96WLOT", "2.D5AV7FUHX1JQ4QLQ5CHB73XA7WUZUA6V", "3.M16V1L05ED5TN2LIZ1MA"], "answerLink": "3PDJ6XMQNY"}, {"questionId": 528, "questionText": "D1KRJY10NBOGDACBWK0AWZNHGPZ0MSH4TT7L6HNGTVMOR9RU21W55FUJT4FZ78AILURBGS2MMCPH43RWQJELG", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "3.0AA5JVWA5RKG09ROH3IKR", "wrongAnswers": ["1.N32TBK91QM0MXE8G", "2.XSBBFDOL9KK4UE01GEIVKNQXNK7X4MSI"], "questionOptions": ["1.N32TBK91QM0MXE8G", "2.XSBBFDOL9KK4UE01GEIVKNQXNK7X4MSI", "3.0AA5JVWA5RKG09ROH3IKR"], "answerLink": "RDWZXT3YG2"}, {"questionId": 529, "questionText": "L1SRVTUU6EXI0P75YOVA6LRRC677NR12H0CE1DO32LNWDIH3JDW6FADQRS26BYICQEJPNL1KWQ", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "3.S5XYLJPGUAJX7ZI0L66CHYPXXIM7A4M0", "wrongAnswers": ["1.8OCF7VPNPFC78FO76Q2JIWH", "2.8GWEUG3GQZ750C1CEI7KU4M5G5TX"], "questionOptions": ["1.8OCF7VPNPFC78FO76Q2JIWH", "2.8GWEUG3GQZ750C1CEI7KU4M5G5TX", "3.S5XYLJPGUAJX7ZI0L66CHYPXXIM7A4M0"], "answerLink": "HWBXLXHPOY"}, {"questionId": 530, "questionText": "MYGK9C8OUB9C6PT1M1CPRNV8HISBYSBUXDIHFLNTTRN4FDA70OP4R6G1K6Q48F1QZ4Z7S7LNVIYGI01PE6D0ARGZI1DYXKMCFCPQZJYXBDFNAAJP8ZZ661I7ZON", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "3.7UNCC8UROSPA4V27K6D6TZBRHOZV", "wrongAnswers": ["1.8RNTFOVPUSSXMW3CKFD3DNF", "2.6RYWF4QC4NLRVPYGFEC0R9ZIXB6"], "questionOptions": ["1.8RNTFOVPUSSXMW3CKFD3DNF", "2.6RYWF4QC4NLRVPYGFEC0R9ZIXB6", "3.7UNCC8UROSPA4V27K6D6TZBRHOZV"], "answerLink": "SNC0QD97ER"}, {"questionId": 531, "questionText": "AQTP56LMYAVCC1DDJHBFY64Y1L8DRRUPTWTNW26MUMYMCLUCP7DGN7EOE0LLZ0R5VL2BHQPNNLF6V7MBE39M43LLU0J7F1MQMC9RIRPUWV5HHE", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "2.955ORBYA9DN2CRYBY0", "wrongAnswers": ["1.R7TAPDTGCJH8JGIFXMIJF4H1WR197RO", "3.3GMTC7X0VRNZUUOCFHEWO5EU7A9"], "questionOptions": ["1.R7TAPDTGCJH8JGIFXMIJF4H1WR197RO", "2.955ORBYA9DN2CRYBY0", "3.3GMTC7X0VRNZUUOCFHEWO5EU7A9"], "answerLink": "BZFYMIEXWW"}, {"questionId": 532, "questionText": "W8BKQZLRUSD25Y6Z6MRSFOKYCDV76JOBJJ757JEWV6555ODO1PF53RCZRHYQYAFA9KG7HGPHJJ3SZ8L06499ONK68YVT2SMCA38O", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "1.YCDTFND8E901F3E8DXBY4L4MS30A", "wrongAnswers": ["2.MDF7TPT5QQAVK16S9Y34BO", "3.VVKU0PLIMW716B40Z3VUVWSB54OW"], "questionOptions": ["1.YCDTFND8E901F3E8DXBY4L4MS30A", "2.MDF7TPT5QQAVK16S9Y34BO", "3.VVKU0PLIMW716B40Z3VUVWSB54OW"], "answerLink": "IZ9H5CR77Y"}, {"questionId": 533, "questionText": "9WHKHV5WP8MSPEEXBZUXJGZL00AVW24F7KDDCYFCSL61Z2DW7WVA5XNIIN7SUDNERJ4RRA4TAMLND35NXGPVF941ZDX9KP22MKTVYTKNCY2V1LOCAGHSDY", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "3.14O3CSHI5H7XJH4JT76S", "wrongAnswers": ["1.QIH84N84A2ENFIEVP7WSA6WHU", "2.RYW921IRCRN3H19AYR"], "questionOptions": ["1.QIH84N84A2ENFIEVP7WSA6WHU", "2.RYW921IRCRN3H19AYR", "3.14O3CSHI5H7XJH4JT76S"], "answerLink": "Q53JZMEVY7"}, {"questionId": 534, "questionText": "FVA7LZ7LU7YZUZZXDFYMAU7CTBF905U833FEZ0Q0U4RJRHYSDCSXQDHPUSFBM44JPZEZZTTOI7SGTL648IR98Q2OTS4G885JFF35ZE7H8M5Q2T60LD7U4DLF3", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "2.TBN71KPTJ4WA8TOW7VG56CKQIYKI", "wrongAnswers": ["1.PYJ153POXBEI5W0W9", "3.6JM6NL9VGPOFE2Z6NRN"], "questionOptions": ["1.PYJ153POXBEI5W0W9", "2.TBN71KPTJ4WA8TOW7VG56CKQIYKI", "3.6JM6NL9VGPOFE2Z6NRN"], "answerLink": "9LM15YFGTH"}, {"questionId": 535, "questionText": "PAMV0HG1IOGMIAK9CTZRVCZGOZMPK1EF890YVD477EL62YLLOCAP3NY9BUP0ZJKVH7LC722AW", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "3.1Y2Q3GIVU6Y1PVWEEYNRXYJ9SXND90", "wrongAnswers": ["1.VOBKAC68SHSFA95ZQRQ9H8", "2.DITNUD0CL6LRAFP1KHHNX"], "questionOptions": ["1.VOBKAC68SHSFA95ZQRQ9H8", "2.DITNUD0CL6LRAFP1KHHNX", "3.1Y2Q3GIVU6Y1PVWEEYNRXYJ9SXND90"], "answerLink": "Q2RVFPZ9XG"}, {"questionId": 536, "questionText": "3ZHXNTHJ0TWHOR7TIO7TXTKZNHB4X4UFROCMKGQN2OQAP6HD5PDYFMAL5S74FV9MM6MJ8B2YK258JPG7BCAFUNM1W15A6NYRQMW24CXJD4VUUKJ", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "2.3153CRF6BX0FH5K0X0FJF0JOP4ICVRXI", "wrongAnswers": ["1.KZVHBYMCLSMNS4J6IYM23", "3.8YQSJZ1YD8LKDFS6GT5XARKFIFK"], "questionOptions": ["1.KZVHBYMCLSMNS4J6IYM23", "2.3153CRF6BX0FH5K0X0FJF0JOP4ICVRXI", "3.8YQSJZ1YD8LKDFS6GT5XARKFIFK"], "answerLink": "TVR6CRX5XH"}, {"questionId": 537, "questionText": "RWOQHS2K18MYILFC2KZA1RUD0OMVLFTEQMTMR1J346C8XXOECYTG6IT7HDHXF6LRCN4IUK489WIFZ84ZH4HF7FP1Z600J7NYV54L2QGKODSDR6CO8BS16V5J3MRS2YK", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "2.PKB382IZSIX2BQQ9FRELSBN1O", "wrongAnswers": ["1.4MT4HEORYCTSV9QVYC66MXJ", "3.V1QY22L84POKWHJ5G64GT"], "questionOptions": ["1.4MT4HEORYCTSV9QVYC66MXJ", "2.PKB382IZSIX2BQQ9FRELSBN1O", "3.V1QY22L84POKWHJ5G64GT"], "answerLink": "I0LK8PB96G"}, {"questionId": 538, "questionText": "OI6KK3ISN324AF28UQ2VUJ8P9X6V2J8E5JC0LDB1C82A6R4R30ZISKW92ZZRBDOJMXWBR1OSO13CVN2IR1RPXSC74OIR3LMXM93U98FBDRAA2W2M", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "1.OFSIRP94YF0RFG8YUT8OE1SP8F3R6", "wrongAnswers": ["2.7AY0XMS0PIHJQAWVZHFEH6L", "3.NTIBJB2UE7SJI9REV3D0WOY"], "questionOptions": ["1.OFSIRP94YF0RFG8YUT8OE1SP8F3R6", "2.7AY0XMS0PIHJQAWVZHFEH6L", "3.NTIBJB2UE7SJI9REV3D0WOY"], "answerLink": "IWB883XEAE"}, {"questionId": 539, "questionText": "AEIR48P1X2FTA1FRGKX0GCXVA2E515SHKNW5Z73MQZJZ4XGMSCPZI07HSIV9X8BT4AT1YSEX4HNNDW2521QUW3XI5MCKUOP8", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "3.KVY2EX4LOBB72HK3TRMR283TS7S5LY", "wrongAnswers": ["1.UP8UHYAA6LO23VTDPJ3TBFM25VQN0WOJ", "2.F2CZ9G6W7G6PPLQUK"], "questionOptions": ["1.UP8UHYAA6LO23VTDPJ3TBFM25VQN0WOJ", "2.F2CZ9G6W7G6PPLQUK", "3.KVY2EX4LOBB72HK3TRMR283TS7S5LY"], "answerLink": "0GI4MVUEMM"}, {"questionId": 540, "questionText": "FHD54Y02JLC3Y7JYZTQ599QVFKYNTVI0M8AV94VPY9PJNH10LE18PKCZOO75YB8K6AYCTKI", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "2.8EG1VE7G5PMZZ5MNF1LU", "wrongAnswers": ["1.MGDUCUYX842WLTPNL5A1B8", "3.6CZBAAFF6VSR8XYLC5KTW"], "questionOptions": ["1.MGDUCUYX842WLTPNL5A1B8", "2.8EG1VE7G5PMZZ5MNF1LU", "3.6CZBAAFF6VSR8XYLC5KTW"], "answerLink": "RK1LJKK22P"}, {"questionId": 541, "questionText": "ITGRIFEPL4CD2ZPMB50XWYMX7O8RJ8SOS9G6YZ34O3UU42GO85K5S6VT1SSYIN0VSRPM6JJYWTK2FV2NM4S9H1BSC5NFHEN", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "3.0HI0A969MWLEUQ8WAEPPSTN99", "wrongAnswers": ["1.AYHH2EYHQKXQOLOGIAJ6B2V2QND", "2.8NVHBXYV9T678Y1USHIV9"], "questionOptions": ["1.AYHH2EYHQKXQOLOGIAJ6B2V2QND", "2.8NVHBXYV9T678Y1USHIV9", "3.0HI0A969MWLEUQ8WAEPPSTN99"], "answerLink": "1E7DIQRXZN"}, {"questionId": 542, "questionText": "YNY6LIYFQ84EVJ7NJR2JXYKFWM1S8PISEJMYQ6M4TFKP8HQFIBPEGMEGIMPIJTD7ABX3OPDV3VV9NW8GGJAP9FEZSSL0DHAU0U41324J42Q", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "2.JHBF1TPW14T8IWO4NIFIDLEV", "wrongAnswers": ["1.JNZU53ZCUDSRFX1GHTLKOS2", "3.LDLIWJ89KHK3M2YTVK1HCDJO4"], "questionOptions": ["1.JNZU53ZCUDSRFX1GHTLKOS2", "2.JHBF1TPW14T8IWO4NIFIDLEV", "3.LDLIWJ89KHK3M2YTVK1HCDJO4"], "answerLink": "2VR74AGBB1"}, {"questionId": 543, "questionText": "ORQ6OYF5TV3KJP4PLM24YZPZQSKGQUYTLFGRVVQW0T45TQLTMBWLUWXU53E8B9JNDO3XCZZJL0GI8YRRDBNPXQ6CBWSG28VTRLQG8918UVWG2W7LMFM", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "2.6SULC0G19UUS9LBA0EG707QX4E", "wrongAnswers": ["1.PF2BG5KQL4652XQB8XJOX7IEBUPNL", "3.CLEHPQGHGGYD1IRDXHK60GTMGC"], "questionOptions": ["1.PF2BG5KQL4652XQB8XJOX7IEBUPNL", "2.6SULC0G19UUS9LBA0EG707QX4E", "3.CLEHPQGHGGYD1IRDXHK60GTMGC"], "answerLink": "J0L8LGI808"}, {"questionId": 544, "questionText": "DAPO119FQEJERV4I8XGQJ9LHMLSC3TNEA6EN28ZUDD8NU5HEL33N9F13TMMEL01K3C9UB2NCRYNK49BC97OP", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "3.BGRW0I6FIDVIIF6WMK4JZSOGYV2QKTWM", "wrongAnswers": ["1.2GAI61FPQWIRF56DUNTHFD", "2.XET3KMO130A3VGXCLT3M2F"], "questionOptions": ["1.2GAI61FPQWIRF56DUNTHFD", "2.XET3KMO130A3VGXCLT3M2F", "3.BGRW0I6FIDVIIF6WMK4JZSOGYV2QKTWM"], "answerLink": "CR3PJ4IUTU"}, {"questionId": 545, "questionText": "V2O4P4HZ23K1A9LABHHT0NM19Y9P6HDAA5YQW0NXRCWLOSWXI3F9NEMQIL433V3X0IOCWGKGXQVT2", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "1.H7QU3FOCB0HYR7N0ZWRFOPX94BR", "wrongAnswers": ["2.FTG3DZHCSWZDSSQFLJZOA", "3.UX5EZ53DYMVY7EOBD2XR0VS"], "questionOptions": ["1.H7QU3FOCB0HYR7N0ZWRFOPX94BR", "2.FTG3DZHCSWZDSSQFLJZOA", "3.UX5EZ53DYMVY7EOBD2XR0VS"], "answerLink": "Q94UIUSDXR"}, {"questionId": 546, "questionText": "V1QUXDFA7F6W34SF7LS8XFQS9MY0EVP39YQY8KBG45XWZXZBB5I3KSQ058T35XO2D6VCZR9DC67YGJ3213X14QN78JWYRK8JLPH0NAJWICTKI31W3M7MHOWUH3", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "3.BFGP44E2G1L6FQ1AAR0Q46R", "wrongAnswers": ["1.Y6X6PJ8RNSQ9CDP7GS78ZWP8Y", "2.I962D1CP1TL9XCPW"], "questionOptions": ["1.Y6X6PJ8RNSQ9CDP7GS78ZWP8Y", "2.I962D1CP1TL9XCPW", "3.BFGP44E2G1L6FQ1AAR0Q46R"], "answerLink": "0LFHMN1RH4"}, {"questionId": 547, "questionText": "FQD1L1XMEX8FFSLER1FZNHIF1364LB8UL283N3F4ZGSTSBWX78BZK0NTCZ1EPLQSK6249K9EWK1F9BF8CV93SI79TPQRA50LMQUC4", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "3.27CC0KJC0ACPQXQNFAVNG3XS01", "wrongAnswers": ["1.ZTIY5EZEDRZPY4PS9JITBAM6WW", "2.6EPRLUXLBJVIURAWCQJOS45PY"], "questionOptions": ["1.ZTIY5EZEDRZPY4PS9JITBAM6WW", "2.6EPRLUXLBJVIURAWCQJOS45PY", "3.27CC0KJC0ACPQXQNFAVNG3XS01"], "answerLink": "1TOYLYWCYU"}, {"questionId": 548, "questionText": "UUQV4L36WES3G1DXUN2TYIKCSE6T9Q1OGTDDC4ONO5YV303KNALFJKFQ8U9EJLD0KZB53O1TB0353DFWCFSZTRK8AP6YGH3", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "2.2G6BOGZGKQJX528BQGHEZH", "wrongAnswers": ["1.IR7MHK5AHMHKY3MW", "3.FGUFV63BE31WXH8B92"], "questionOptions": ["1.IR7MHK5AHMHKY3MW", "2.2G6BOGZGKQJX528BQGHEZH", "3.FGUFV63BE31WXH8B92"], "answerLink": "9KAPPLQ9WB"}, {"questionId": 549, "questionText": "9VFG2P7FLFMY2JWIBHZL78A7SN3C11C2K4RH5S8WSTS0UKBHS0XBFF1OA84E1TG8GFIJJ3BNX4ZM5AYXMVNVYJF65J6B3C55ZQFP99YJRKE5Y", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "2.OZKKXD1TLRVSC8TPDOH034RSK9S8V3T", "wrongAnswers": ["1.XC541KET4P3DA9VIJ", "3.4WSS6WBOMGM4V28NPA3A957Z1B9X3HB0"], "questionOptions": ["1.XC541KET4P3DA9VIJ", "2.OZKKXD1TLRVSC8TPDOH034RSK9S8V3T", "3.4WSS6WBOMGM4V28NPA3A957Z1B9X3HB0"], "answerLink": "NLBWUF6W29"}, {"questionId": 550, "questionText": "9UELWT131RV6UQ68C3MCH9ZFDS31DMR0527TF5EFAV6RNZF17Z02BJD2BOK24GZDLIX47OATTSO0EFVEDLWZKNUB5L7M9LJSD42589UN7L5VC0Z0KHT", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "2.Q4R86K80LY3O3YLX3GNY", "wrongAnswers": ["1.IXCKTTSDRHTOXKS29WSANBTN65GS", "3.LIC50EDEDQ71E5SY30XOMGDTP9LXUJC"], "questionOptions": ["1.IXCKTTSDRHTOXKS29WSANBTN65GS", "2.Q4R86K80LY3O3YLX3GNY", "3.LIC50EDEDQ71E5SY30XOMGDTP9LXUJC"], "answerLink": "P6KNZUFZEY"}, {"questionId": 551, "questionText": "MQ3TXMCTMF01XDPM53PK8IXB23P8X79IISVT420MHXD0CP8ALMRL5DX8UNSSD5KQOUZ2BN2", "questionCategory": "Regola 14", "correctAnswers": "2.FEQATOVDRDEPH682", "wrongAnswers": ["1.BNONRWUMW1GEQU8B4FASQ7JYWAXQAD", "3.XR2ILAX04PMFYWFAN35"], "questionOptions": ["1.BNONRWUMW1GEQU8B4FASQ7JYWAXQAD", "2.FEQATOVDRDEPH682", "3.XR2ILAX04PMFYWFAN35"], "answerLink": "PLK7QXQRET"}, {"questionId": 552, "questionText": "7BGZCIV1E4L3B77E1BWY1AZPSZUIDLWCTYGJO4CGL416F1V8PKGSBT7QYZZVVC2L2S05XYYD2NJBOG8RJ0Q06PA7DS", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "1.VPASR3RD3LTTYPLNT9H4UC98KP8E8MM", "wrongAnswers": ["2.0SECZ4KOS4YKQ0N5CEID51II4", "3.V81XHH5548T7HHJXPBV74DDNDGJAV"], "questionOptions": ["1.VPASR3RD3LTTYPLNT9H4UC98KP8E8MM", "2.0SECZ4KOS4YKQ0N5CEID51II4", "3.V81XHH5548T7HHJXPBV74DDNDGJAV"], "answerLink": "1KEEBETD3B"}, {"questionId": 553, "questionText": "8YDH6C38EZHD2TV077HWQL0MI0YT9UAIGZQA8L88PWRU3CNK1DH9P1ISR108I40E4LU5FVDNO", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "3.DGO6VNW2F9NWZXKJ7FQGAX633", "wrongAnswers": ["1.KHUXSYTIMFRGWNIFRGJZ", "2.UMX7Y859J05QR7GVSPNUIHXND"], "questionOptions": ["1.KHUXSYTIMFRGWNIFRGJZ", "2.UMX7Y859J05QR7GVSPNUIHXND", "3.DGO6VNW2F9NWZXKJ7FQGAX633"], "answerLink": "BJQR7GZGGV"}, {"questionId": 554, "questionText": "DVSAEKTBCMYM9OJ5DL96UYDKEJJQS0ALSE32CMGNKMOCO8I9FJRFQ0B23IPYO5CVDXGM8BFFZODGTN", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "3.IPCRS3N6SSS8DI735KWJYV", "wrongAnswers": ["1.VHSMTLMR6TSFBWBICUKYACAS1BAP", "2.9K8PLURYENAEHPS011K6UG050N3"], "questionOptions": ["1.VHSMTLMR6TSFBWBICUKYACAS1BAP", "2.9K8PLURYENAEHPS011K6UG050N3", "3.IPCRS3N6SSS8DI735KWJYV"], "answerLink": "YBW58375C3"}, {"questionId": 555, "questionText": "UAUJRBU33S6FQH2WQ0TFDGLIC63BO7DHQ6M9UFKXUKLGXXVGWXB4GHACMEYTO2NO1MNZ7M7JNXEJW3I8PB0F0WE0EU4D1YKM2MZIINJIM7RQ409PD6NDOR94UMXL", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "2.KXVZ0AI167S03GQRJ6XILJXYGZAGXMM", "wrongAnswers": ["1.LUTFIGVMDC7HLE7QAE", "3.JJGYUVTGH5DGRVBUGNZQ4W"], "questionOptions": ["1.LUTFIGVMDC7HLE7QAE", "2.KXVZ0AI167S03GQRJ6XILJXYGZAGXMM", "3.JJGYUVTGH5DGRVBUGNZQ4W"], "answerLink": "B6AQQ0OZZ3"}, {"questionId": 556, "questionText": "WOEV65BR3X7CYL52U7ODVNS6028VW2DHOPSBAJZ1PLT6GDUSYOFQVZUJRCKDDCCQY28N", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "2.KZOR2ND042J8IE8BRIB3C2K", "wrongAnswers": ["1.5TFBIMHW3SZCK3IZJR6IPQ3", "3.0PIINGOG15CUQ8XARQTVZASZ6"], "questionOptions": ["1.5TFBIMHW3SZCK3IZJR6IPQ3", "2.KZOR2ND042J8IE8BRIB3C2K", "3.0PIINGOG15CUQ8XARQTVZASZ6"], "answerLink": "KO007XMR6A"}, {"questionId": 557, "questionText": "1Z5MVHUSUERZPCT25D35PL2KIRSHH354IGZGKKYINOUX2NOIX5M623GPU8C40HRE5B0TXJBGI", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "2.ED0YSVHXYWS0IZ2AK2KC87P", "wrongAnswers": ["1.11LEBPN6SAKKGF4C1UM1", "3.C0KYR4J1O9ZKQ8D448J51G7"], "questionOptions": ["1.11LEBPN6SAKKGF4C1UM1", "2.ED0YSVHXYWS0IZ2AK2KC87P", "3.C0KYR4J1O9ZKQ8D448J51G7"], "answerLink": "Z5LS912M5H"}, {"questionId": 558, "questionText": "2IZ7B505SX2RRJE31DF237WIWCIR52ILC38XCKILLVPY46LJGFCHDALUERRQSQ8EPKCV2AZFKT3OIKVYIR5HOD443SIERSSUC2GJLYEE810GSKG0LIC6R3", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "2.3UIHJ8ZMLZYCERR9J0BZAOS2RCJW", "wrongAnswers": ["1.GYE4NNUQXYXZNYIXVA3EFYV8WV587", "3.8JQ70UQT804G9DFKQH3WDHVH0J560P"], "questionOptions": ["1.GYE4NNUQXYXZNYIXVA3EFYV8WV587", "2.3UIHJ8ZMLZYCERR9J0BZAOS2RCJW", "3.8JQ70UQT804G9DFKQH3WDHVH0J560P"], "answerLink": "17KV6WEIBH"}, {"questionId": 559, "questionText": "7X38MOKEUHI5FOHWFK8Q1XI7JLDNSRPZD7UWCBQWKYEXDTLFZXP39YMY0HCW6CW62UTW1XOH0A2XCEJNQ7Y7EPZO4JD9B84JU", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "3.R9Y09VAQO7QD635TBXW4D6TT40", "wrongAnswers": ["1.KI056QGMS1NCMQCBBXPRVRV0L6", "2.U2D5SMFGDSYEWMTD9Q7L664NG64"], "questionOptions": ["1.KI056QGMS1NCMQCBBXPRVRV0L6", "2.U2D5SMFGDSYEWMTD9Q7L664NG64", "3.R9Y09VAQO7QD635TBXW4D6TT40"], "answerLink": "T1G06IROU5"}, {"questionId": 560, "questionText": "L4XGM3ARXZA62ZRI6X3OLHB39O70KTY5VLRNWRW2BUW24BGH5YSHBO7XALUTF63W2RO5J1JAG", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "1.8TX8RRMQL2DHT9P24W4AKXYLPA844UE", "wrongAnswers": ["2.DFCXLT2EC1ETTQJUJWGB", "3.MV3BOV1NP3I94BLMA82NKKY5M0FJTND"], "questionOptions": ["1.8TX8RRMQL2DHT9P24W4AKXYLPA844UE", "2.DFCXLT2EC1ETTQJUJWGB", "3.MV3BOV1NP3I94BLMA82NKKY5M0FJTND"], "answerLink": "CQP60KSAKJ"}, {"questionId": 561, "questionText": "Y191JA3ZCOLUFTN01AGC1WK41GDA32Y9YVMNEMHKMIA3MB9WVFYSGWM8GNM7NYY550EVP2C93PUH3KO6SLFHSYEK", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "2.URI7OR9IEZ0V0X1OCS", "wrongAnswers": ["1.9RXZPXQQWS195EUDGZV", "3.S90FQ7CLDERESVPANXXS26Y25"], "questionOptions": ["1.9RXZPXQQWS195EUDGZV", "2.URI7OR9IEZ0V0X1OCS", "3.S90FQ7CLDERESVPANXXS26Y25"], "answerLink": "HHS2PI0CX2"}, {"questionId": 562, "questionText": "6AP8JR2YVNL4H5224MTTZW0BA8B4VT4UJPI1023IFXIZQJ2OXUE2Q5WWF9Z5O312NLELXK4MESS9M9YVB8FF1QFBI7XYSG4NLNRIWYG2C6NEVMSQHSONCIWS571QN", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "3.P942BWMSFTVAWV30PVQ3YC5III1MEK3L", "wrongAnswers": ["1.AQY4HTS7EQL0B2OVZZVQV6AN19HB", "2.MZM82G8GQWUE2JN8"], "questionOptions": ["1.AQY4HTS7EQL0B2OVZZVQV6AN19HB", "2.MZM82G8GQWUE2JN8", "3.P942BWMSFTVAWV30PVQ3YC5III1MEK3L"], "answerLink": "OTP597MWBW"}, {"questionId": 563, "questionText": "O1IF5B4IKZXJ1VZQ1U5XLMA2CT02HE8EA7DGO9RKS6A0XUM15BX4MQRSW0EDYIFJ0MKWWWT5PKVIOLW2OB", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "1.QWMBN9UT3GLXDFF9KUQCF", "wrongAnswers": ["2.50N53I9YYV1PPQABW", "3.51JUL6PEFNETM7AVWKID"], "questionOptions": ["1.QWMBN9UT3GLXDFF9KUQCF", "2.50N53I9YYV1PPQABW", "3.51JUL6PEFNETM7AVWKID"], "answerLink": "V1QP2DCMW4"}, {"questionId": 564, "questionText": "Z9AYXG6L6F1LM5A3HBK9HIIOED4FE33BJE1W6MPL4EY6LO0F1ZLCLPR203XM2SXO71ELD55IA7X9VRSLAOZHNF6Z4NOM9O4R", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "2.8W2QHZSQHN39M4IVF2IEQ8S", "wrongAnswers": ["1.V0WOE7LPUVTVS2X1", "3.DYZUM793I6KOTJIPGS2MMIEWQE2O5UJV"], "questionOptions": ["1.V0WOE7LPUVTVS2X1", "2.8W2QHZSQHN39M4IVF2IEQ8S", "3.DYZUM793I6KOTJIPGS2MMIEWQE2O5UJV"], "answerLink": "HPOOMU95S6"}, {"questionId": 565, "questionText": "A384QM28ETR2IPBLY70PP997190K3OJJOMT20C53SIQ7ELT7413SU6ILV0EC34IOA2T5KIQHQ2K7JIEFRJRJ9YBTUNUGPJ72LRK1IWD3N2", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "2.GL6UP5Q7HUH99976WXHH0DK7", "wrongAnswers": ["1.L7V4L5WL6BJIGMN8W9S0X", "3.Y75OLHSFG0A3DOEXQ"], "questionOptions": ["1.L7V4L5WL6BJIGMN8W9S0X", "2.GL6UP5Q7HUH99976WXHH0DK7", "3.Y75OLHSFG0A3DOEXQ"], "answerLink": "RZ30QAC40S"}, {"questionId": 566, "questionText": "D88A9SSL50RRADMZ7EH9EATRH2IWHJDQQOH9ILGFOQ7KGD1RVMRVZSXLYCG87X2DODFKHY56I6YJJ4TTPTXC7T42MTLDZY3KBPG6IDKO6JF8G0HMZHLK9ZMH0VBY", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "2.2XJE6CYTLOIHYGN1KHXBE2QI8", "wrongAnswers": ["1.D6ZXO8K30F3I1MOP56TEIG9B7IM79G2O", "3.K2AROR639P3MZJR6P5OVD9JBNT"], "questionOptions": ["1.D6ZXO8K30F3I1MOP56TEIG9B7IM79G2O", "2.2XJE6CYTLOIHYGN1KHXBE2QI8", "3.K2AROR639P3MZJR6P5OVD9JBNT"], "answerLink": "C3QPKBMGGG"}, {"questionId": 567, "questionText": "KXKRQ774GJO33RNZ0C0UIL4L01G1VL6IEVFFKAH2404YBBEZW0H66JB0DOFYBACC4", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "2.Y1OFBW05MKPR2ADWDOLED3LM3066CR", "wrongAnswers": ["1.00UFDV0YKXJWRLWYU7LDI9F44NSII", "3.A1QK5Z6JYMLYHVQI516V6A"], "questionOptions": ["1.00UFDV0YKXJWRLWYU7LDI9F44NSII", "2.Y1OFBW05MKPR2ADWDOLED3LM3066CR", "3.A1QK5Z6JYMLYHVQI516V6A"], "answerLink": "5FJ2QX1RMS"}, {"questionId": 568, "questionText": "N3TQXRZWPNN60MFKUUHOOYOE8G74Q3Q1AA6TW19LRL5T8J0ZEU8IXJC8H9E15VSEPW87L9SC8OWCBWDTGOVY6", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "1.T93YAN1YIURRF8FWS3QGQIS51C407E", "wrongAnswers": ["2.N0CSPEOPIBSQRV08R6FJKOYL32C", "3.5EC6OXH47LKK2K8F9LXMKTFI7OI48L"], "questionOptions": ["1.T93YAN1YIURRF8FWS3QGQIS51C407E", "2.N0CSPEOPIBSQRV08R6FJKOYL32C", "3.5EC6OXH47LKK2K8F9LXMKTFI7OI48L"], "answerLink": "JG13KWYOWO"}, {"questionId": 569, "questionText": "PKHM9VAAQQ1CUDZBTR79RBQ8YXLDPL0F31QLOVAMPF56BSD4K425I73D0UOQJCSL4P4VX8CQONK1M8I8U1WVKD5JOKKX5RDBNRS8DZXGZGZM", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "3.ST95FLA9VFL8MWGMZH504", "wrongAnswers": ["1.DVY6E5C6RVFED22W3S", "2.A4S388A8GL8TDE9ELMETP41CWMHCP3V"], "questionOptions": ["1.DVY6E5C6RVFED22W3S", "2.A4S388A8GL8TDE9ELMETP41CWMHCP3V", "3.ST95FLA9VFL8MWGMZH504"], "answerLink": "HRVC1WFSYM"}, {"questionId": 570, "questionText": "I7HN3G3YP3CMG2BP0Z2ADKT4VWS76CI0AH4TG1148D22JUCAXCDM5LUMJUNYFV8MPI1X7JQ1M3EMSXNIWM56N2J3UE8WPDU", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "3.BIAHYKEDOX5MOAYRJDJL8LC9YSA", "wrongAnswers": ["1.7NDOOKEAKWLOMCS9K1F1D3OY95USJON3", "2.JEV53A1YN15OC62EDI8EBT54L7WNRYY"], "questionOptions": ["1.7NDOOKEAKWLOMCS9K1F1D3OY95USJON3", "2.JEV53A1YN15OC62EDI8EBT54L7WNRYY", "3.BIAHYKEDOX5MOAYRJDJL8LC9YSA"], "answerLink": "VE24CT65LD"}, {"questionId": 571, "questionText": "6ILAIOHHGOI3AM5YUX96P5MTCW0IL3YIDA4M14LUGROMNMTLJTDOER9PVUZV3YUCVQYAB3K7MTEXHWWDCBKN9", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "3.PRTKDLR7JQO8EB1BX26FDC45", "wrongAnswers": ["1.FUWMRSKEBSH3RBQTO6FVTF4NZI", "2.7OVZZ7X0V9JYCVKNGBE"], "questionOptions": ["1.FUWMRSKEBSH3RBQTO6FVTF4NZI", "2.7OVZZ7X0V9JYCVKNGBE", "3.PRTKDLR7JQO8EB1BX26FDC45"], "answerLink": "YKUA1FEZ8F"}, {"questionId": 572, "questionText": "I927OB1TRXJ4J8YL0437OP6Y0ZY6DZDDU10DUX64YXH403QOHNICAGWRBZHOTPR0AKLI64DP64PAM2UTI5QTBGKL8XHF58D8NHQE1W1CKQZWPJ9L0VQDNBJ", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "3.DD5VV7PKOQQ7Q33XOFGZ1BB8EH30E", "wrongAnswers": ["1.CPF0CS429O501X5TLQHENENU7FCLPW", "2.AWBD5QGJ1G3P85CAYI5JJTKNV069D"], "questionOptions": ["1.CPF0CS429O501X5TLQHENENU7FCLPW", "2.AWBD5QGJ1G3P85CAYI5JJTKNV069D", "3.DD5VV7PKOQQ7Q33XOFGZ1BB8EH30E"], "answerLink": "CQKGFZCV7X"}, {"questionId": 573, "questionText": "IDHPDO8FLC93C3GGL5IC5P46S2DY8WSL9HAWVJ2FLEJQ1AOOZ78UD8TX9MHLLZB3R2FSE0FY01AJPWTAMJRZOHBDSYHHJHSAE7PVNR299PS856WPV2DA4RIK9GVG6", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "2.TAQF2SL9EZMJI21S7V3KF90JYR2PO", "wrongAnswers": ["1.7K1SQZ8U696ZL9M1ZMI6", "3.JONKS5KLF9PSGGSZR"], "questionOptions": ["1.7K1SQZ8U696ZL9M1ZMI6", "2.TAQF2SL9EZMJI21S7V3KF90JYR2PO", "3.JONKS5KLF9PSGGSZR"], "answerLink": "6J4C3FYNL5"}, {"questionId": 574, "questionText": "6PAOZ1TA7DNI27HXQPHEEKC2PIPH5QWAUJAQWEEKQR3QRQS9CGE5NLZDPWMHFAVKR5EKNYH91TAABW86IEN8KUB1IPRR3Y5XS", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "2.D4VRHTC2ICORV35UMHE", "wrongAnswers": ["1.IR50CR0HG0JGYE4FZSSTLR3T9KHJ", "3.LH1RSM9TC6AHX6G7R2"], "questionOptions": ["1.IR50CR0HG0JGYE4FZSSTLR3T9KHJ", "2.D4VRHTC2ICORV35UMHE", "3.LH1RSM9TC6AHX6G7R2"], "answerLink": "F0XRBJIPMV"}, {"questionId": 575, "questionText": "EVBI60TSYBD65UQ122WJ2HFMJHYVBMJVMNOYGJYV8T3GR8VXRNQDDRY1I03C306QS8M3AGRR9LLXYN2WRG6Y1", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "2.6W5G07F0YFLIVVK6AUC4RS9387UCAI9", "wrongAnswers": ["1.5YU5527PI78B237MK7DRMI9IKS7AB", "3.FDBIOR9GWC1POE8JKEH7TFC"], "questionOptions": ["1.5YU5527PI78B237MK7DRMI9IKS7AB", "2.6W5G07F0YFLIVVK6AUC4RS9387UCAI9", "3.FDBIOR9GWC1POE8JKEH7TFC"], "answerLink": "L7N7CPAE6X"}, {"questionId": 576, "questionText": "I744TKEBK6Y969Y1X521SZ9P3Y5TZDBZP9N8OYLTDQ1PPXNSX9RZBCRN0UTKB2PHWXOZF8W", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "2.IHAR0WNQS88ZB5J8DY", "wrongAnswers": ["1.OSC8YWCPAC0Y5GCD", "3.CN1SKGZZ035579H7IGO3YMR"], "questionOptions": ["1.OSC8YWCPAC0Y5GCD", "2.IHAR0WNQS88ZB5J8DY", "3.CN1SKGZZ035579H7IGO3YMR"], "answerLink": "2N4CP0TDQ3"}, {"questionId": 577, "questionText": "0DEDLXUND4Q1VBYVORCIYXRD935CS6ZZ55YGLVHELYSB0VW4B777GRVHQXQM8QELSARMO0EC7410H8O1H8WEF87ZM7PP13B3ZKXBQ7VWB3L23J0R", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "3.7FMRI9XSNY270KOTRQUMKMS1NU9CSC", "wrongAnswers": ["1.6SME9W4XMU95RK8QY5VIP", "2.ISPYKQ2ZBETE11SV7"], "questionOptions": ["1.6SME9W4XMU95RK8QY5VIP", "2.ISPYKQ2ZBETE11SV7", "3.7FMRI9XSNY270KOTRQUMKMS1NU9CSC"], "answerLink": "JMT3M66T8Z"}, {"questionId": 578, "questionText": "XSOKCH9OMTEABVUM0X7LOEIGHIIKZHJ8YBDNJSMQJNET4N770PX3L9WDH9PRJCIETSCHZ4APDSSFN17EV2649U", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "3.Y8I7KRJAZSNMCVVBE", "wrongAnswers": ["1.PU2SFS11VDQF1VQ50822E", "2.8JE9ARGUM016WECG"], "questionOptions": ["1.PU2SFS11VDQF1VQ50822E", "2.8JE9ARGUM016WECG", "3.Y8I7KRJAZSNMCVVBE"], "answerLink": "YBQURTDMPD"}, {"questionId": 579, "questionText": "0NYTESSAVXEMY3IJRJ2JHMVI77EQB2OFI5A5ZHT5175NNMY4GS19NBXLA2NKMBN4DPEEB16F0M1789JF5JIXW7RDX", "questionCategory": "Regola 15", "correctAnswers": "1.O0DLY8H0VVB6BZ8P9YQ85EJS", "wrongAnswers": ["2.QFM0DMBJR4WX09LVPBO685", "3.D9MUTXEGMVYJSFO6ZIZYFCB2TUQ"], "questionOptions": ["1.O0DLY8H0VVB6BZ8P9YQ85EJS", "2.QFM0DMBJR4WX09LVPBO685", "3.D9MUTXEGMVYJSFO6ZIZYFCB2TUQ"], "answerLink": "9ZNRYNLP8E"}, {"questionId": 580, "questionText": "OEVOBNO9NTDE6Y7KPK1ZI4NTMVFNDEACWFUK6U59SM6A49DVHMNL9NFCVW5VR5J14CFWP489WAPRDN0QGXPZR678NDH14P9EYHFFJ84HCRI", "questionCategory": "Regola 16", "correctAnswers": "2.6306Y776TUUY9Q2WCRO5MYWXS3GV9H", "wrongAnswers": ["1.ID072E56INZX9S4TX2DV62FXDLODP", "3.W3LQF74G8PXGBDJX99SBG8XUOYJ8BE"], "questionOptions": ["1.ID072E56INZX9S4TX2DV62FXDLODP", "2.6306Y776TUUY9Q2WCRO5MYWXS3GV9H", "3.W3LQF74G8PXGBDJX99SBG8XUOYJ8BE"], "answerLink": "H0P83D6YYE"}, {"questionId": 581, "questionText": "42E9WQ8150ZEUASKDZKEBH704DX46XF7BD496HTPWP91KER17ZDZSS0PWUS8WG8KHB0I5HYRYQAANP260BV3DQX1UCLNHQ3J81TQ51Z261", "questionCategory": "Regola 16", "correctAnswers": "2.LQNTSBO9TLHPC3MFZLLDAEP9P", "wrongAnswers": ["1.OFW373J7S8M20YW65E", "3.OGN6CNU5KFNPKQ1WNRY8IKM2V1DYY"], "questionOptions": ["1.OFW373J7S8M20YW65E", "2.LQNTSBO9TLHPC3MFZLLDAEP9P", "3.OGN6CNU5KFNPKQ1WNRY8IKM2V1DYY"], "answerLink": "UUZ8S1JPL9"}, {"questionId": 582, "questionText": "O82FS1EO1SG01FEPHU5VQ9SL7CS58PLW8WKIR621YZY93GI26NNT1SQYTE3CMQMQVSLR6PU0MH3MYK18LNI4MPWTWV7JUFFJACUE0YKFF0AQWVVH3", "questionCategory": "Regola 16", "correctAnswers": "2.HG4V89CTULGUY99ESW8JKCRCR2Y", "wrongAnswers": ["1.9EYAS0TLQJCMGHM7LFR4HD", "3.1N9GOR0GLEZYSHS3G35"], "questionOptions": ["1.9EYAS0TLQJCMGHM7LFR4HD", "2.HG4V89CTULGUY99ESW8JKCRCR2Y", "3.1N9GOR0GLEZYSHS3G35"], "answerLink": "F8O2JSKPGE"}, {"questionId": 583, "questionText": "O4PSZH87RU72MSJYBVKIPT5MS7JV6MK4TFVUC4Z7DYXDR88PROBQFTAWF4RMF0TTYDOG6", "questionCategory": "Regola 16", "correctAnswers": "2.386BY8DSHP64YJJDSU4CYU7G", "wrongAnswers": ["1.TWWS53BN65P72LIW0OCEQ4DYU", "3.6YOODZEZOH2ODNZ9035PXC1QTXSNY"], "questionOptions": ["1.TWWS53BN65P72LIW0OCEQ4DYU", "2.386BY8DSHP64YJJDSU4CYU7G", "3.6YOODZEZOH2ODNZ9035PXC1QTXSNY"], "answerLink": "J47JYQIELC"}, {"questionId": 584, "questionText": "721FKY3QZLD66TBP0E0FDXPZ99XH73S3OM96R6IX4WSZR1XAIXCQ3RQ0P6Y8R96C8GESN", "questionCategory": "Regola 16", "correctAnswers": "3.48PAJSR234K0BSM0", "wrongAnswers": ["1.XG3HXFQ2WEY9LN4KN0KNG", "2.8WTVECDF6X9VCD8C0X2AX6OYCXBDTX"], "questionOptions": ["1.XG3HXFQ2WEY9LN4KN0KNG", "2.8WTVECDF6X9VCD8C0X2AX6OYCXBDTX", "3.48PAJSR234K0BSM0"], "answerLink": "BHD3AU2ZQ6"}, {"questionId": 585, "questionText": "S00H0WNDJ38HRT1897CAN3UT4C4PZYSLM4OMYGA25HP5FFN3LFZGTPIP8IGB99CUXPIFNPNBURD0R1I3FAXXDNKI4G4K822W1K79VQGOQNFJTEK8T", "questionCategory": "Regola 16", "correctAnswers": "3.JCTN4UZTBA570F57GX", "wrongAnswers": ["1.TIYNY3OMU5PVLXK9J0XSXF29ORW", "2.5MYZ3L58Q4UUXXLQI5XS7LOPWL2SAH"], "questionOptions": ["1.TIYNY3OMU5PVLXK9J0XSXF29ORW", "2.5MYZ3L58Q4UUXXLQI5XS7LOPWL2SAH", "3.JCTN4UZTBA570F57GX"], "answerLink": "NV55CGF7V5"}, {"questionId": 586, "questionText": "9SSE1XBUD9XMIDL8N3P9549BX7K1NLEYC8DNCAVAL4CG03XYHQA9K1JKFC830C2S4RAMIUN2IYB8F0XBB16YB9J5MQWM29H8X3U1ON80WA68HJD4A5QWS", "questionCategory": "Regola 16", "correctAnswers": "3.Q4AI8RY16WF4RNX13", "wrongAnswers": ["1.O0ZSAX4UIEPKTKU0BJIM1YBQ37", "2.LV3536IDL0XB6PYE"], "questionOptions": ["1.O0ZSAX4UIEPKTKU0BJIM1YBQ37", "2.LV3536IDL0XB6PYE", "3.Q4AI8RY16WF4RNX13"], "answerLink": "K9V8LLQOHM"}, {"questionId": 587, "questionText": "E1XJGCZTVNEMF1HYKTA5B5K89RU2N07ADZ6W3UUGASIU5NBNU96A8B55HCG351UMEOXTTOXX59RJCP6OKCZSLDXSIXPD55HZ8RZEHPCQY6MN99CMNJHI59BW78VAF", "questionCategory": "Regola 16", "correctAnswers": "1.3MWVTY9TJTVZZTUH2IUZEBNSG9ELT", "wrongAnswers": ["2.EWR5CO6GUI3N139XQUECP", "3.8JT3U5Q1NO6BHCNP5YSHXA9T5NYH1"], "questionOptions": ["1.3MWVTY9TJTVZZTUH2IUZEBNSG9ELT", "2.EWR5CO6GUI3N139XQUECP", "3.8JT3U5Q1NO6BHCNP5YSHXA9T5NYH1"], "answerLink": "PQGT5HXVAZ"}, {"questionId": 588, "questionText": "EN7CZHRQAQ7BB4OXH33HT7KHMJDLTUSKYQ30GM0SP876HC8S7GXTD1TPQB3HZFRZTJEIF7T51TF3V2G8IKKW7764SK0P6FE", "questionCategory": "Regola 16", "correctAnswers": "2.Q8CKXSAM57K0R6XZ2RNALDX5EOP", "wrongAnswers": ["1.5PVEJNFE7SDYJQ978DU", "3.GGERK9Q8Z1LMCZRM"], "questionOptions": ["1.5PVEJNFE7SDYJQ978DU", "2.Q8CKXSAM57K0R6XZ2RNALDX5EOP", "3.GGERK9Q8Z1LMCZRM"], "answerLink": "L93QS5GHXR"}, {"questionId": 589, "questionText": "PHP2V15PO9JADHE7DDE6VQXYQRCPH6915OCKBD56RK8DCO880AJSX8F2Z6QC16IA5WDMWRC0NCLH7G2XS1FV10O", "questionCategory": "Regola 16", "correctAnswers": "2.E1XOX4J3JNTSVN9SB8I8S27SBG", "wrongAnswers": ["1.WDRWXJ2HH9OY2JEGN5NRJLC0J3AJ", "3.SOCV8A78IXMK4EY7AW03KJG1VGYE59H"], "questionOptions": ["1.WDRWXJ2HH9OY2JEGN5NRJLC0J3AJ", "2.E1XOX4J3JNTSVN9SB8I8S27SBG", "3.SOCV8A78IXMK4EY7AW03KJG1VGYE59H"], "answerLink": "3Y5D8M9WZA"}, {"questionId": 590, "questionText": "SG3UMSKIYFYZ1BPEX2TMHD2PYRCSU903DOKALH5PABBWPM9R42FUILSLYF216TE1YEMJ8RT7L0851JKH3AQWAH", "questionCategory": "Regola 16", "correctAnswers": "2.BCJ3WZHCOMIZKCUVIH", "wrongAnswers": ["1.DE51QXEQB1YM502POPZAQK78", "3.KH1NDF0B0TCLF8N1Y4N7EN7K0W"], "questionOptions": ["1.DE51QXEQB1YM502POPZAQK78", "2.BCJ3WZHCOMIZKCUVIH", "3.KH1NDF0B0TCLF8N1Y4N7EN7K0W"], "answerLink": "RIOP9GB6PI"}, {"questionId": 591, "questionText": "CNLZ1MWILN3X1ECOJJC2B590SRH1B4PVSVT5QNHK2CDKFOO7SQB06KMBCQSLU9RQA5F8SFM2X02JLOIXFZUNZVD7OK7FVCZ08SD5YVBTJUYGW08SMYNQBZOW2LCU5", "questionCategory": "Regola 16", "correctAnswers": "1.IPPCSCJB97V5BWJG5G83JO", "wrongAnswers": ["2.5N367XQBFGQDFRMS", "3.KKF42BN3K38I83XQJXJ4E7NEHU"], "questionOptions": ["1.IPPCSCJB97V5BWJG5G83JO", "2.5N367XQBFGQDFRMS", "3.KKF42BN3K38I83XQJXJ4E7NEHU"], "answerLink": "9AJJPO62E0"}, {"questionId": 592, "questionText": "N3PLO6MMZD0TOTJ0B3FVKOF0VYFC7JAFR81WZY3GRUDM7DZ74P97PTZKIUHLJ6M9XHAJ2XTURQMX61OCEALB157K7J", "questionCategory": "Regola 16", "correctAnswers": "2.5XP5AKKZFMQ7MK11N7YOZX1VO", "wrongAnswers": ["1.ID8UZR1JXVBS57PBXKJJW1F34IU6", "3.JRBQ5NRH19WOV1TF8"], "questionOptions": ["1.ID8UZR1JXVBS57PBXKJJW1F34IU6", "2.5XP5AKKZFMQ7MK11N7YOZX1VO", "3.JRBQ5NRH19WOV1TF8"], "answerLink": "ZW07I1EWC3"}, {"questionId": 593, "questionText": "1RPWQM2EUQHJHUJ3RWN1F5NRV2U7L8J4TQ31Y9CLFSQ936N9SOCG22YEL6P3OAO7AQWI", "questionCategory": "Regola 16", "correctAnswers": "3.4ZWR3HTZFFR578JIW", "wrongAnswers": ["1.SUMAI3O5P7MWK6UTD3EBK20U", "2.11LQGH89PLFRRMYLQ540EMCAY9"], "questionOptions": ["1.SUMAI3O5P7MWK6UTD3EBK20U", "2.11LQGH89PLFRRMYLQ540EMCAY9", "3.4ZWR3HTZFFR578JIW"], "answerLink": "FLZ1C1G7YX"}, {"questionId": 594, "questionText": "EF4ROZ0T1CKZ23S48A7D7Y1FLLQFDWQ0QNOBY7MNBPMNWWKETTTGY5JVSXUWY7VZGF", "questionCategory": "Regola 16", "correctAnswers": "1.CB3XKDAOV31UTKXJJ4Y9Y0T4LEWDH", "wrongAnswers": ["2.98ARTLMCWE5SKOA0", "3.APYRDKO345M1RAVXKN2J7KR"], "questionOptions": ["1.CB3XKDAOV31UTKXJJ4Y9Y0T4LEWDH", "2.98ARTLMCWE5SKOA0", "3.APYRDKO345M1RAVXKN2J7KR"], "answerLink": "T13W1JT4VQ"}, {"questionId": 595, "questionText": "QGKL5NGHHPU0PUNHBA7X72I0LQ2NP7COGEAA5W6G1U9NKFWJHLINDVKFZINIOUQNGUECR1TMFTOTQ6O25P27Y5E3SQIK", "questionCategory": "Regola 16", "correctAnswers": "3.HDPM06OLIILT3SPOEUO", "wrongAnswers": ["1.3N5U3PJTP3QBDXFN", "2.1ZRVZ2N6ZZ1LTBXGCJ4"], "questionOptions": ["1.3N5U3PJTP3QBDXFN", "2.1ZRVZ2N6ZZ1LTBXGCJ4", "3.HDPM06OLIILT3SPOEUO"], "answerLink": "KE4VDDCDHF"}, {"questionId": 596, "questionText": "DW0KNX6DBEXPTUKDZ6JI07PO4JE4RTXK21Y6223YEHUCIE7G8AZX6WSNE0OYBA35YR55GDKTGKCYBQRMHO5PV", "questionCategory": "Regola 16", "correctAnswers": "1.97K657EGFBOXPSGZEM7V3VEN", "wrongAnswers": ["2.E0V1UTEFYTR8G89Q6NOSGM606", "3.NJ5COO8M15F2P0YETRXOOHZBP"], "questionOptions": ["1.97K657EGFBOXPSGZEM7V3VEN", "2.E0V1UTEFYTR8G89Q6NOSGM606", "3.NJ5COO8M15F2P0YETRXOOHZBP"], "answerLink": "TAXKNJLV53"}, {"questionId": 597, "questionText": "0UENXE8DLYGTMIN7UQHGSYSX1M2B1XVDBBNE1YMRGY0I7YRLU9NDC2E8GMJZN7V9OO0AJOV61CDAZ021N3W08G1BFAWKM", "questionCategory": "Regola 16", "correctAnswers": "3.CIAQ4TUJ63QO1YGV3ST4SDCNWRINL", "wrongAnswers": ["1.I88RL5P7PZQ7QH5X", "2.BR6KAZAQ4JD4KKMK8G56WQYY38Z"], "questionOptions": ["1.I88RL5P7PZQ7QH5X", "2.BR6KAZAQ4JD4KKMK8G56WQYY38Z", "3.CIAQ4TUJ63QO1YGV3ST4SDCNWRINL"], "answerLink": "N41MX8BF9L"}, {"questionId": 598, "questionText": "VE0NI6NBEXQDUPN32704QOWEHQMINXPVE35OSDZJSXDTX7YWG4MTZWKGJM99N1GNH8DWAFHWJ6QYMB67CJLUDN9P6JYZ8GX27W5IYVK49FIE2UIBC1ATZV4", "questionCategory": "Regola 17", "correctAnswers": "3.U0CM8O745NCMDQ2SRO", "wrongAnswers": ["1.7CHXP2TDVBFHFG0P6XB7JR0RV9YQ", "2.GVWWNJ8RY0Q7OEAT2ITNS"], "questionOptions": ["1.7CHXP2TDVBFHFG0P6XB7JR0RV9YQ", "2.GVWWNJ8RY0Q7OEAT2ITNS", "3.U0CM8O745NCMDQ2SRO"], "answerLink": "VC4UDVDA2U"}, {"questionId": 599, "questionText": "U6LVEWOZBF7QOTEF33WAA8V5778ZCXXCGM82VWEC27FO1EVMXZM0FBQH1DKOLY5W8O127O9H70XKJQG09UQ8R57BM1WG5GS9TQNFR9X41Y9SH99XMXOWOVBWDLVOS", "questionCategory": "Regola 17", "correctAnswers": "1.I7I1NXO1YVD6IUOM1WRN4J42PZBFMPQ", "wrongAnswers": ["2.9IVP0UAGLGDS5YEI7BCFEM2N1X9DIZ", "3.SSLS84FJXA1FTKZNA1BS9"], "questionOptions": ["1.I7I1NXO1YVD6IUOM1WRN4J42PZBFMPQ", "2.9IVP0UAGLGDS5YEI7BCFEM2N1X9DIZ", "3.SSLS84FJXA1FTKZNA1BS9"], "answerLink": "LH31B9WO82"}, {"questionId": 600, "questionText": "TYWG46WV3LBTFP5BY20DNMBV6RD9WQ4SUTS0WOL58ST3GBZYK5H0CIA8CA2KG6244KKMJ2FT9CA", "questionCategory": "Regola 17", "correctAnswers": "3.LLR4VEMCZGT4AAOI1L", "wrongAnswers": ["1.AB3VGA6EM4HJ378JPHT9HAN5MJ", "2.TAXKU3W4NWFPYJZEG7JF173"], "questionOptions": ["1.AB3VGA6EM4HJ378JPHT9HAN5MJ", "2.TAXKU3W4NWFPYJZEG7JF173", "3.LLR4VEMCZGT4AAOI1L"], "answerLink": "LG3E97J2ME"}, {"questionId": 601, "questionText": "MQKCB2UZ5CMIOF6NWBBD6T0CTRMNTOO33XJOV939U6J73TL4Q1UQJ9CLGOVLG5UAOTPO7LA8NDOHP5OVDO4XMARYNZJCPLVD1W", "questionCategory": "Regola 17", "correctAnswers": "3.YBCTZYOH3XS78OVONC8D", "wrongAnswers": ["1.HSPE8XST4MZDXIVG9C84W5GT0LW9EN", "2.FZBVB9F8DGXTWUDBTIKM47"], "questionOptions": ["1.HSPE8XST4MZDXIVG9C84W5GT0LW9EN", "2.FZBVB9F8DGXTWUDBTIKM47", "3.YBCTZYOH3XS78OVONC8D"], "answerLink": "3K3Y5DFKSA"}, {"questionId": 602, "questionText": "BWF3CR9UZ2NQ7CFNWVURXV49R2X8GNM45WAKT2P6SNRVT11DIHHQUS0D7QN9XX4V4IRVP7XMSRLG3S05GLA7O0XRNVF50I1K247", "questionCategory": "Regola 17", "correctAnswers": "2.JMA0VNYWYPMXY4S179BS", "wrongAnswers": ["1.DEEXSX4YY8QVTLVZZRBKGCP", "3.8KPISYK46HZXEF5IEY"], "questionOptions": ["1.DEEXSX4YY8QVTLVZZRBKGCP", "2.JMA0VNYWYPMXY4S179BS", "3.8KPISYK46HZXEF5IEY"], "answerLink": "0AJ346C4YN"}, {"questionId": 603, "questionText": "F5X4YSFYQU7OCCD1U2AS2WO791MWX63EX855STQ730JLCQS3TJQ8Q8ODQPR2WVTYE9D3JXON1C5U8L78POTC8ILL555ATUJ2V1FNWCFY48Y", "questionCategory": "Regola 17", "correctAnswers": "3.ZNS77Z380BJZL0QXZ3", "wrongAnswers": ["1.48G1058AQYKQOAU78HHH", "2.IMME0Y9YB5ZKSSZD16WGU"], "questionOptions": ["1.48G1058AQYKQOAU78HHH", "2.IMME0Y9YB5ZKSSZD16WGU", "3.ZNS77Z380BJZL0QXZ3"], "answerLink": "V721Z4XZY3"}, {"questionId": 604, "questionText": "H8AJGIDWY54AMBZ9GEH3MPI9Y07CE4QAWGMSZAKG3PB8RX6ADTLPPSZHUYM5XMNOU61XE1MW68RISOIKZ", "questionCategory": "Regola 17", "correctAnswers": "1.1IAELHNAYMLB0WD6NP0Q6J", "wrongAnswers": ["2.0E3NUWQ18BRC4Y956CBELG68ZDX40C2", "3.WNAYGTOVFYVXOLE7RZNOLC"], "questionOptions": ["1.1IAELHNAYMLB0WD6NP0Q6J", "2.0E3NUWQ18BRC4Y956CBELG68ZDX40C2", "3.WNAYGTOVFYVXOLE7RZNOLC"], "answerLink": "YW5AIW43E1"}, {"questionId": 605, "questionText": "AN56OMMB3GF1ZSQPHLAL3W9LNVXWHOP3GHZPSGTPLHN5ZTRBA522X09FK0ZXKQ4T3P4E7972QV", "questionCategory": "Regola 17", "correctAnswers": "2.OMC8IVONVRPEKILCU5KILM", "wrongAnswers": ["1.QP728RYP1RR1YFPZWGZTFJFF", "3.5A3ZKSLUNX3OWH64TYSR8CBZ7XUZ61UY"], "questionOptions": ["1.QP728RYP1RR1YFPZWGZTFJFF", "2.OMC8IVONVRPEKILCU5KILM", "3.5A3ZKSLUNX3OWH64TYSR8CBZ7XUZ61UY"], "answerLink": "OY4ZXI38HI"}, {"questionId": 606, "questionText": "9A0J5JUO22D130A9QLZNZU60HSJX4SZOARLZRMTHEYL51CQ4V3ENA4YDS07BQROXPP7FGXGWAEVZ5QIM3JEXH", "questionCategory": "Regola 17", "correctAnswers": "2.F7279LTHX3WHBAZO5FFCRNXZC2Y7", "wrongAnswers": ["1.99JY41G7QSPPZ88DJ", "3.35BI4DZ6ZC6VSMPB31CUBDF5JPV0ON0"], "questionOptions": ["1.99JY41G7QSPPZ88DJ", "2.F7279LTHX3WHBAZO5FFCRNXZC2Y7", "3.35BI4DZ6ZC6VSMPB31CUBDF5JPV0ON0"], "answerLink": "YLUMCA6HU2"}, {"questionId": 607, "questionText": "IKCKWTYTYFP2TWQQKNITVLKU9GNWUSY9DTIFFK1TZH58YQRQV050T3UZL2WP2ZKH3WBNOTDJ13O1FKNPZB0JTPUAG1SGT7FQST0VSEQK7", "questionCategory": "Regola 17", "correctAnswers": "2.J9PPAZL00D4YTAY8LEM0EXUN", "wrongAnswers": ["1.GUXUIIV21AATH3DNELAK5CNLTS9", "3.OMN6RLQP4KYOM2J3K2R"], "questionOptions": ["1.GUXUIIV21AATH3DNELAK5CNLTS9", "2.J9PPAZL00D4YTAY8LEM0EXUN", "3.OMN6RLQP4KYOM2J3K2R"], "answerLink": "BZOFEB4E8L"}, {"questionId": 608, "questionText": "70FNCU8WWA1KTW4TJSZ7KW1LX25ZEKFDL1OADDOH5JD8Y3DCCAPGRITNITDPRELBHPHTH8F3GQ9", "questionCategory": "Regola 17", "correctAnswers": "1.EMMVVYCBKS6PIIXG7P", "wrongAnswers": ["2.Z8NAAZXU0DF0F8SOT32IBCA7GQL6", "3.MQQXOJVQ1S66LQ9T5GRH3FUO9"], "questionOptions": ["1.EMMVVYCBKS6PIIXG7P", "2.Z8NAAZXU0DF0F8SOT32IBCA7GQL6", "3.MQQXOJVQ1S66LQ9T5GRH3FUO9"], "answerLink": "G2UE83TPG2"}, {"questionId": 609, "questionText": "1630YVDINZ6JL3FQMB9T5W32OVF2AGCOZDVX7XF754FFK14KGYE6PKKIP6J8NTPXH1TM4BU5UZGTHXZOYJV4NYSXQX3KBQUP3", "questionCategory": "Regola 17", "correctAnswers": "2.GMC6BFZN7DBOXCXY0PBLXKHYE", "wrongAnswers": ["1.R0G5RW98IRPA3WTNVHPM94TQLT1", "3.O8GQOUVJFVEBY0AP637JW0JXFXA04JK"], "questionOptions": ["1.R0G5RW98IRPA3WTNVHPM94TQLT1", "2.GMC6BFZN7DBOXCXY0PBLXKHYE", "3.O8GQOUVJFVEBY0AP637JW0JXFXA04JK"], "answerLink": "VKRS9H6EYY"}, {"questionId": 610, "questionText": "SRFC3SIAA8APXGWRLA8IVAMVOCOF7WG9T955GJ3G56FVI748APV909B3XEHVVI1JA6OHFW76RAB0GZK431LAXGEOZAAC", "questionCategory": "Regola 17", "correctAnswers": "3.U4CAM15M1ZWFR0RU24P6QEXRD7E1", "wrongAnswers": ["1.SXERNYYBXCQ49JC3E6PZP", "2.HNB5Q6VP2PYL0JHJG7J"], "questionOptions": ["1.SXERNYYBXCQ49JC3E6PZP", "2.HNB5Q6VP2PYL0JHJG7J", "3.U4CAM15M1ZWFR0RU24P6QEXRD7E1"], "answerLink": "G91E62N9GF"}, {"questionId": 611, "questionText": "1EQM9NGDQGTYM5KBCPWKN2R5HUKX9792EXFY3IKKRC2QMQMUHE7BGHAYFT52W8U0HP4O7V4AR0I", "questionCategory": "Regola 17", "correctAnswers": "2.TMP4HVEVUZ56JH7S5YFMNE6O", "wrongAnswers": ["1.AE06XQ2J4PXB4G8SFZNNQGSTQ0", "3.W8K63AGREYEWXSWKX9VKGGUX4R"], "questionOptions": ["1.AE06XQ2J4PXB4G8SFZNNQGSTQ0", "2.TMP4HVEVUZ56JH7S5YFMNE6O", "3.W8K63AGREYEWXSWKX9VKGGUX4R"], "answerLink": "7XS8TLB1NJ"}, {"questionId": 612, "questionText": "IAF9P9WCIPCYIPX49EVCW1IITATDKYQPKXOLRN614919UNE5OC33OLZMYQ4FO3AR7FKWG3GX92DVI4S9APIPTN6DYYDTBBK3GJUDS649ST6J9Y64GSJ3QR0NFUYRNP1", "questionCategory": "Regola 17", "correctAnswers": "3.LNTGMVXIJ3HI2OKOUZHK7KTV", "wrongAnswers": ["1.BA827GM02KCSH2ODLGDM3JJZ6NG", "2.8GRXCIEF3ANFZ7V2D0N"], "questionOptions": ["1.BA827GM02KCSH2ODLGDM3JJZ6NG", "2.8GRXCIEF3ANFZ7V2D0N", "3.LNTGMVXIJ3HI2OKOUZHK7KTV"], "answerLink": "LZMXKPKTVY"}, {"questionId": 613, "questionText": "EN7L7P8EEGNRNPT8DDGW3GTD4ID8YY7QJK85DYXJ7OEE747FJPOEVRENBF2N83WWJ6V4UYKH5HWQHZQ9170PZURJYMSS8TB8D5YS53GD7NLYDVPC7KQ9TF02BQESXEXG", "questionCategory": "Regola 17", "correctAnswers": "2.SWJCTS3758DSBXA8FS1Z1K3KNGL", "wrongAnswers": ["1.9XILVU2OR6PNUJMH354PYYD", "3.ITVDXYQ1U4RVFCYX6QT6JUMJB0IE"], "questionOptions": ["1.9XILVU2OR6PNUJMH354PYYD", "2.SWJCTS3758DSBXA8FS1Z1K3KNGL", "3.ITVDXYQ1U4RVFCYX6QT6JUMJB0IE"], "answerLink": "5VRJK2DSR5"}, {"questionId": 614, "questionText": "A7SGA3W5B8LTRRGMUSF8XU56H873UD44TK097ZCCKD3JHTKIBE7WVUGWHPPOFLOXVBOBVAKWR9NYGVM10ZKZ9R61LRBSYSHDEZWX5V1C309TUC997ND3", "questionCategory": "Regola 17", "correctAnswers": "1.CTNN1WESYO1A2G0MX7IHQR", "wrongAnswers": ["2.AEGLT6VJKKRA1NSU3K2N9", "3.5SO57KGSCXDDPOZRLS"], "questionOptions": ["1.CTNN1WESYO1A2G0MX7IHQR", "2.AEGLT6VJKKRA1NSU3K2N9", "3.5SO57KGSCXDDPOZRLS"], "answerLink": "Q8WWF061ME"}, {"questionId": 615, "questionText": "RDY61ASCY9ASCWPVQ17QC56ZYPQOQGCYISRJWBDILCV8QZFI87ITC6MP8HS7U0TF48UPV9QV42J2OD9EXHNX8X95LXILTFHZHFP875LIY6", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.1CJKT51YS741AI4BGKJ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.76VXLJ1O14UEGPZR53Y8WYWVHT54L3SC", "2.H72KNCQ6KWP11IKVGRXIO"], "questionOptions": ["1.76VXLJ1O14UEGPZR53Y8WYWVHT54L3SC", "2.H72KNCQ6KWP11IKVGRXIO", "3.1CJKT51YS741AI4BGKJ"], "answerLink": "KYBXUP83YQ"}, {"questionId": 616, "questionText": "JAHO2DJ1IIREWJQ8CA0J6F399E9IE93ZSPEBSDXHZ93EDBAHY6CFU32S2UWKE6JPJ1T62EJX8417WN2AUQ5OIQZACZI4B", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.E4Q7VXEF66U4KMOQRLAZPDGQZ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.Z58DNL32HYAAEU9YB8JPH", "2.ZEY0C79AKO5U24WJENZJ1C3"], "questionOptions": ["1.Z58DNL32HYAAEU9YB8JPH", "2.ZEY0C79AKO5U24WJENZJ1C3", "3.E4Q7VXEF66U4KMOQRLAZPDGQZ"], "answerLink": "5SYRWIUXEX"}, {"questionId": 617, "questionText": "7SUC8M9NKYO9PDKWVMSJD6Q874ELYJD8KEMPDWCONTLV5BDSP3BPJE3TQCGIDF2MCBDDT5UIHF45WN1D4I7W2YOLLGA3R6KTBX1LLVLJ4", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.UT49ZGGMD9Z1K259", "wrongAnswers": ["1.1EILZVX2KQ5IF41PCT93NDR9WU45VLD", "2.KIDDSIAIJ1B3E7ST6P0XE30YB7T2N3I"], "questionOptions": ["1.1EILZVX2KQ5IF41PCT93NDR9WU45VLD", "2.KIDDSIAIJ1B3E7ST6P0XE30YB7T2N3I", "3.UT49ZGGMD9Z1K259"], "answerLink": "4P39UON50J"}, {"questionId": 618, "questionText": "OKIZKZLH3G8VSIVW34MN2YO41EAIMRE6CDLBQKIQUSZAUUBY27SO5PR5RFTU6EO9TH7S6B22P7O4VU", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "2.DQX5H3UP09E7T0VPXGHGXEVG", "wrongAnswers": ["1.FI3Q5VXWZ3R0EDCT5S9IFHDW3Y", "3.PN3CZJ2J3FJRQ10A0V"], "questionOptions": ["1.FI3Q5VXWZ3R0EDCT5S9IFHDW3Y", "2.DQX5H3UP09E7T0VPXGHGXEVG", "3.PN3CZJ2J3FJRQ10A0V"], "answerLink": "0UB4BH0HWI"}, {"questionId": 619, "questionText": "ERTK6LN0H8PTTKAUXOW3UJIUWITUB5VEB4WSWZ3MZFCIHTR854I2LHGQLPAK7ZF4SE55SECPZSEIPEOTM8OIEI9H0G02FZSSC92S34CEPC9X7TV0TGQI69EVKG", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.YK4WMIBEL9QOKE0ZC27S84ZD7SC2MSG", "wrongAnswers": ["2.M0IWUR91M1EYS48CN9WLQCLK96NY", "3.QOLP78VAA44JFHLW2"], "questionOptions": ["1.YK4WMIBEL9QOKE0ZC27S84ZD7SC2MSG", "2.M0IWUR91M1EYS48CN9WLQCLK96NY", "3.QOLP78VAA44JFHLW2"], "answerLink": "6Z9112X1XK"}, {"questionId": 620, "questionText": "Y3WK02OEUZGZ7JC7RRAM8U0C3SC8IRHNBY9VD8DVJEKQGOIJBG1329QY10R2FPNUG5M9ONJL54EMP8IS0", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.JUP7Q7OUTCYVPZ5V6ULZQ5JY5RET", "wrongAnswers": ["2.V4XGZUEDE37HWVAZDFNXK30L8", "3.HX89MSFOO1FHP5PPE"], "questionOptions": ["1.JUP7Q7OUTCYVPZ5V6ULZQ5JY5RET", "2.V4XGZUEDE37HWVAZDFNXK30L8", "3.HX89MSFOO1FHP5PPE"], "answerLink": "AYC4A0ZBY9"}, {"questionId": 621, "questionText": "28JCMH01HXFOQFFZVV0T04LO3IMNW7D182PY7SLBVEKD9GWJRPJ1XOM4QSC15O2GYJYCXA5V1TBW6FHRNIKUZW8EVVF5YIY9RN0IWKW07IBSEJEV222AT", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.95G9M4RFM53RIZIUR5LP1YL508CH4A8", "wrongAnswers": ["2.1VR2WJCJQ0F6WXGDE4EH3O1AMB3MG7L", "3.10FG9UO2BXZNOW7F"], "questionOptions": ["1.95G9M4RFM53RIZIUR5LP1YL508CH4A8", "2.1VR2WJCJQ0F6WXGDE4EH3O1AMB3MG7L", "3.10FG9UO2BXZNOW7F"], "answerLink": "8UJAD8NHVZ"}, {"questionId": 622, "questionText": "4WML42KNPY2XAGS9IT6C6JOX49MD6670DCUT0TKUB0KV32CWAPZ4BR53L4SE6J64O4MEB2KZYVSTJ9PK0L03FHD27VC", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.7J4FIX8M2KQ18OXNG352B", "wrongAnswers": ["1.XLRX6TO1RB4QPGCB5BAJG", "2.GV10KGAWRFJLWQGDLA4F"], "questionOptions": ["1.XLRX6TO1RB4QPGCB5BAJG", "2.GV10KGAWRFJLWQGDLA4F", "3.7J4FIX8M2KQ18OXNG352B"], "answerLink": "U46EWQPMIH"}, {"questionId": 623, "questionText": "1PPWRFR4Z3O8282XHZEY81ICA1A1NHB3XWCQJO6UVY7BWD3Q40GNFOSRH3ITYYM0VXB1QDH109485I", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.B3OQPVL18RLJQ60XICD", "wrongAnswers": ["2.LTC05DRNTRXMRG9P", "3.X83H332J3V6BWXT48TQBQQ7I8IH"], "questionOptions": ["1.B3OQPVL18RLJQ60XICD", "2.LTC05DRNTRXMRG9P", "3.X83H332J3V6BWXT48TQBQQ7I8IH"], "answerLink": "XYUXPJSIQT"}, {"questionId": 624, "questionText": "AX07R8BU4BJSAS0KMY7J9QEABXNZ9ZVTXLB87X9Z4YPUI9QGY11TLCTLKJ23M6S9LCMVBMDDETD9MPSO8L81R2M28NQO31YRJPGJ4AEO8Q0DET", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.SSIFL7QRRDJ59L3NQ5WNODG0RCUS", "wrongAnswers": ["1.6U5EFX1JPX8C2BLN314BJ3DY4BNMF", "2.ITPJHQNDBH4UH8QO80SR6J5LP26NBI7"], "questionOptions": ["1.6U5EFX1JPX8C2BLN314BJ3DY4BNMF", "2.ITPJHQNDBH4UH8QO80SR6J5LP26NBI7", "3.SSIFL7QRRDJ59L3NQ5WNODG0RCUS"], "answerLink": "9SUZE1DIR8"}, {"questionId": 625, "questionText": "6DTCNJNIOHZBWTCHR1504OM9VHILMOF2Q3SGW4NTD8N8N3KH1GUQSZJ529QG8GKVFOOERPQY7EOWKJZVSYTY", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.EWN9EQT4XKE1IM3HS9YCL6BALUX3HOO", "wrongAnswers": ["1.510HZQLNZEXUYZFNTVY", "2.MAX5U0L08IQQY23I930QNPA"], "questionOptions": ["1.510HZQLNZEXUYZFNTVY", "2.MAX5U0L08IQQY23I930QNPA", "3.EWN9EQT4XKE1IM3HS9YCL6BALUX3HOO"], "answerLink": "AQVL5WYDZX"}, {"questionId": 626, "questionText": "BTGUIHQ8QBH13LEZ8TMK3RQZ5K86OQI4KOZ48HBM9SZIBOMUH70P68L853K6D1A5N2BIM8NIFF7TN3RCHZCPL0WH8R1MCXOJJ0JPR9UMPXBF48VXBJHUJE", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.JDH8SO2CHQ7T4KNMVGSYA3K0LRZLSOI0", "wrongAnswers": ["2.9PX5MVY8FYMHY1P1DLX", "3.J7MD9BJA0UOIQM3PLFYN4"], "questionOptions": ["1.JDH8SO2CHQ7T4KNMVGSYA3K0LRZLSOI0", "2.9PX5MVY8FYMHY1P1DLX", "3.J7MD9BJA0UOIQM3PLFYN4"], "answerLink": "41T5BUCJD7"}, {"questionId": 627, "questionText": "16J1AHYYIQUDXYPO0YG1C8B3SOHQKGZH278S1I5ELXXUQ756D44N2QQLDZMMBIEZ6CELKAVDV7ULGLV25SZWO", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "2.7S0ELXN3LLECR0DW13ZV", "wrongAnswers": ["1.AIBISDQSVBHT2V4HGUF6D04", "3.P409S73WA198NGQLL1S2BWH6JJI3B"], "questionOptions": ["1.AIBISDQSVBHT2V4HGUF6D04", "2.7S0ELXN3LLECR0DW13ZV", "3.P409S73WA198NGQLL1S2BWH6JJI3B"], "answerLink": "93HXCFI0UP"}, {"questionId": 628, "questionText": "FV40W65DB6UH8WW00QVDBQIXOJ6JP645MEPKLQLSDOINOKXIOIAZJWCX4XD5WBWRU2PF4E062R5HAN8KOSWW3C4", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "2.78E9U8GTKHG6C5IIGAFAW", "wrongAnswers": ["1.GBJYWPO0MYC464JTHGE", "3.WRTPWW8T8VE5SAU1VJNN6D8XF0Q"], "questionOptions": ["1.GBJYWPO0MYC464JTHGE", "2.78E9U8GTKHG6C5IIGAFAW", "3.WRTPWW8T8VE5SAU1VJNN6D8XF0Q"], "answerLink": "QX2M1RB260"}, {"questionId": 629, "questionText": "V9B2Y9D7K9XCAERYRJSVTOS5RA1GY6FHQOXXSL9OH6V60HLVCWFCUVMUM9RSUSBR6VZ4T", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.NPT9D7BC1VU6F7IG88S19", "wrongAnswers": ["1.DZMX9VZTLP1M4E1XS51OINTTFTE", "2.7UGWH9LK8IJT28Q8P5SM5F"], "questionOptions": ["1.DZMX9VZTLP1M4E1XS51OINTTFTE", "2.7UGWH9LK8IJT28Q8P5SM5F", "3.NPT9D7BC1VU6F7IG88S19"], "answerLink": "LA5CX084D7"}, {"questionId": 630, "questionText": "CIFSFFY9XZFOQ3KKV8PB6K8O0Z3BVJTK2QNJT57RSS0XLT5KCIZW94BVV50UJD5B8YP0B0OYMQL22X7OTSLC7Z4PLQCM8BD3BJQKAB37GKGH59N1VXEK94", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.OBF039633USQ9U9ZG4QJRN28GXM0P", "wrongAnswers": ["1.6NR01KCJCSHD89ETY5YOQN8", "2.1A36NH5AG5CPFJYDFCN5EW2H28"], "questionOptions": ["1.6NR01KCJCSHD89ETY5YOQN8", "2.1A36NH5AG5CPFJYDFCN5EW2H28", "3.OBF039633USQ9U9ZG4QJRN28GXM0P"], "answerLink": "QPZOZAL412"}, {"questionId": 631, "questionText": "D8FC7C40LZIK2SRSM2B4K2G17KI0CA5KVB4F70BJV8IQTH0P5ZQATKT0A1TJHG7BY0HBJU9HVR1", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.VW1NT12R2O37PDZKFHL1J50V", "wrongAnswers": ["2.J2TRT83XL0HY1C2SUPV", "3.J7Q2FLDZGV0D2SPCJ06HS"], "questionOptions": ["1.VW1NT12R2O37PDZKFHL1J50V", "2.J2TRT83XL0HY1C2SUPV", "3.J7Q2FLDZGV0D2SPCJ06HS"], "answerLink": "7QJ272U9OI"}, {"questionId": 632, "questionText": "QBDQPQGC94D7RUGFEZ30DL2WLFSFP54IFDHBI41HIMXL26YK2TMZ63TIBBPVY44MHC1Z3D17ZQ2IUO0M2YWF5J", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.5JCTW6JS9C5QSFAAXWR75", "wrongAnswers": ["2.ZMN8P4KAR60QRAFFYR4DD8", "3.W1D0KG22QADKLTVPK4Z3NJUSC0JE1U"], "questionOptions": ["1.5JCTW6JS9C5QSFAAXWR75", "2.ZMN8P4KAR60QRAFFYR4DD8", "3.W1D0KG22QADKLTVPK4Z3NJUSC0JE1U"], "answerLink": "8RJ88Y5844"}, {"questionId": 633, "questionText": "KMEG4HWXGVI9RMVSAB7E5XAQCM8M11KLHQAQFSYTIGCNND0SHYRYBAJH7PIPHFO2MCOIHDNNOM", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.NUGJORLDQKMT7C11JB", "wrongAnswers": ["1.21HJBZPGYP12TVBL4UU", "2.62EGK6ULS1G79N50V5NWT0F"], "questionOptions": ["1.21HJBZPGYP12TVBL4UU", "2.62EGK6ULS1G79N50V5NWT0F", "3.NUGJORLDQKMT7C11JB"], "answerLink": "3CLGNQ8OFF"}, {"questionId": 634, "questionText": "OUFLMHESBJ8O77AAWC39TR69L3BNQHDNNUD751WBWNU1X2VMSO3E5S9B4O5QVQ2K650WC920U04PPXE06ZFH9N", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "2.MUZLAV7PEIQ3FEOQZFL", "wrongAnswers": ["1.6RU1FTLM3BUU3TR2ZAKW80GSAC5C1U", "3.LC6CA9PJKYDRKHO6VWN3G"], "questionOptions": ["1.6RU1FTLM3BUU3TR2ZAKW80GSAC5C1U", "2.MUZLAV7PEIQ3FEOQZFL", "3.LC6CA9PJKYDRKHO6VWN3G"], "answerLink": "KWNPZHKSWL"}, {"questionId": 635, "questionText": "9RVOUXYVCBF6G08TAQ2J8SCDJKSQY31GIUG42RIW1AUX5PWLU28UPUGDUC4IONRLJSPGXKH6BPA7DQ45", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.6UCPONSDJCDWE6G2ND496", "wrongAnswers": ["2.6SK4RYRRHDNA9EQZJYMEHSCCHVYO", "3.NKO6HE8HZZHECWYUHO"], "questionOptions": ["1.6UCPONSDJCDWE6G2ND496", "2.6SK4RYRRHDNA9EQZJYMEHSCCHVYO", "3.NKO6HE8HZZHECWYUHO"], "answerLink": "RR41BL3A7R"}, {"questionId": 636, "questionText": "R486GPS85GOEJQ25R4IS2FFJW2NB8KQ99RYSHDQWBPDK22Z2HXU5NCDW4MQ7ITO9YM2PUDALCRVY80MC2EQ6O4FLADYFR8YIT2MBIZDHD", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.ZRF68VE5EAQ0O4UVROEWVCC765", "wrongAnswers": ["1.A09Q681OA38IKPQ8L72WXYHCMMPRERM", "2.PPAPN7DIOFIMQIIQEMWLHL8YZV9OE36"], "questionOptions": ["1.A09Q681OA38IKPQ8L72WXYHCMMPRERM", "2.PPAPN7DIOFIMQIIQEMWLHL8YZV9OE36", "3.ZRF68VE5EAQ0O4UVROEWVCC765"], "answerLink": "7S6JIQ102J"}, {"questionId": 637, "questionText": "WZBMDLQTV5CFPCVJOBHMNIVCEN49FEA3533F1FVUAJ84SHMNJCEH30872X1BJ7ALGDL4BQ0KY0H52X6AMY04JML3VTR55PB4GDKA8V4ASVGWQEPMV6", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "2.QYB9FF4TR6NDGB152GB", "wrongAnswers": ["1.GENDQNKOVPR0YULAAIZKOYLFY40PKG", "3.QV0LE31LPK8UO09P827Z1945ANBQZ"], "questionOptions": ["1.GENDQNKOVPR0YULAAIZKOYLFY40PKG", "2.QYB9FF4TR6NDGB152GB", "3.QV0LE31LPK8UO09P827Z1945ANBQZ"], "answerLink": "3HHHWHA8CI"}, {"questionId": 638, "questionText": "NTKL0N3H99KVUPAXAZDIYPMEMP3UQX9O8DKFG6RQ3WBLGKU754LJ1YQ4DCN36X6A5BQ10BVDQ8CZHWJDOAH755WOI7O8SVM", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "2.R3LGEGADVLWQZHIPG363XV2R6GB1OT", "wrongAnswers": ["1.5O1JPRW2VVZMTJOR84J4", "3.YT7AWMU4SYNC0BBPNEQ030I3XNZOD3"], "questionOptions": ["1.5O1JPRW2VVZMTJOR84J4", "2.R3LGEGADVLWQZHIPG363XV2R6GB1OT", "3.YT7AWMU4SYNC0BBPNEQ030I3XNZOD3"], "answerLink": "BPAYV7Z573"}, {"questionId": 639, "questionText": "2E9PTALX59TE8Q3V00G3XLVC1Z8GUYFEMXC7MF3DSDG7E9VKDE7OZ41V7XD7NRFWVRXL5NF48IJO0JFIGFEJALB97", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.26T12HIKO2UYCKBJD9VANH3OVO9IKIWK", "wrongAnswers": ["2.BX3LL3E6PJQ4PTEVHDZL9T", "3.L1I9GNC404MUQ8SGJBHEXEYO"], "questionOptions": ["1.26T12HIKO2UYCKBJD9VANH3OVO9IKIWK", "2.BX3LL3E6PJQ4PTEVHDZL9T", "3.L1I9GNC404MUQ8SGJBHEXEYO"], "answerLink": "507KK4A6II"}, {"questionId": 640, "questionText": "869B04IXQ4A4UF37QX684U676TZ648TWIZ6G6PJ787Q0D2IMBTCGEV1AOB9UCRFIFW8U11B5FHPCOS0RQGCBTUCICTR1CG0WGCL7833D", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "2.WNI3M61EU8QE1MST4HIXK8NYZ4H3IK", "wrongAnswers": ["1.WAMEKPHKVXTL33ZZQCMOSAQAVX9", "3.JRHBVMYIL9NW8JPZUXWO5PND4E"], "questionOptions": ["1.WAMEKPHKVXTL33ZZQCMOSAQAVX9", "2.WNI3M61EU8QE1MST4HIXK8NYZ4H3IK", "3.JRHBVMYIL9NW8JPZUXWO5PND4E"], "answerLink": "X9CO1G31Z3"}, {"questionId": 641, "questionText": "OJNISVSGQPZ1RM2WX9B48K07YJEQ088WZZT4S247MOJKZ9DW95TM9WWJERGJ29HJISY958OC695HLKLNASXKKAZPX6U9CLSGFPJBZBUIF6WYQ6B5G1WLXVAL4845S", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.I4B20MVV96DDDWQHIJ50JGDM1I658O2", "wrongAnswers": ["2.ZXETZM5EXKGJKB7RXVQ9QSM6ZYO4XVL", "3.ISTP1OD9PHMX4FI1W2XP336"], "questionOptions": ["1.I4B20MVV96DDDWQHIJ50JGDM1I658O2", "2.ZXETZM5EXKGJKB7RXVQ9QSM6ZYO4XVL", "3.ISTP1OD9PHMX4FI1W2XP336"], "answerLink": "T60GT52SXH"}, {"questionId": 642, "questionText": "GPX7ZXFSBA5ETAL7MOHSIVAY9VPVXY7401AJIGNDFGEWNFLHXMPRVSHPSZ98TOYW3EN23C01XABXSECPN1Y8FEFE866GLOF88ZEOWV185ET", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.10XXNEQ51VMOMZSHK9Y9N1G", "wrongAnswers": ["2.L6LAVL446H1MDA95QM58B61UD", "3.29GJOZQRTGN5NB5V"], "questionOptions": ["1.10XXNEQ51VMOMZSHK9Y9N1G", "2.L6LAVL446H1MDA95QM58B61UD", "3.29GJOZQRTGN5NB5V"], "answerLink": "6BCGL7OEF2"}, {"questionId": 643, "questionText": "DK6BN1BW69Y32PADL99MBB1U7BEWBY1RMC3GDP3YN0BWW9V2AVP97NHI38ZBLZR0RHZ75NQ93HM934JN0OAJO4F35B7I92CL3NXNGQ", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.Y4TL9PXVHGF9ZOQYDPXNG8ZXW3VJ", "wrongAnswers": ["2.NYMZKV20N9IPJ9N4IJ", "3.2KOVYVUYG7AE4883HB"], "questionOptions": ["1.Y4TL9PXVHGF9ZOQYDPXNG8ZXW3VJ", "2.NYMZKV20N9IPJ9N4IJ", "3.2KOVYVUYG7AE4883HB"], "answerLink": "2T8QELKNP8"}, {"questionId": 644, "questionText": "40P2JOL66LUQUK5GSDGRJD02UPDIWTFT3ZY0Q0FE2B6A626BYK55QYNOJIMF7DH0R0N9WEGUSZTGX", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.NMS1AV0QS9G0GJVCD383R98GCQ106BY", "wrongAnswers": ["2.ZYYIT5568KV82D49K8JPOC734CGEU9", "3.897CSJ1OPOLP5L1SXVWO"], "questionOptions": ["1.NMS1AV0QS9G0GJVCD383R98GCQ106BY", "2.ZYYIT5568KV82D49K8JPOC734CGEU9", "3.897CSJ1OPOLP5L1SXVWO"], "answerLink": "R5IIEKE0N7"}, {"questionId": 645, "questionText": "PMJ28MEQB95KB442IJJDOWVME6EPM3O7SOHQQSXIVO2X3LDF5D54MJA8UKXZZ9XSB94XIAN1NIWE8XRZ9SLJJ7OI", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "2.N7ABKRBVPUF00LVXCYOJLI2", "wrongAnswers": ["1.UHQPN41756GRH8RMJI7U8RZSJA1DUT41", "3.IYRQ90JJVTIFBZX89"], "questionOptions": ["1.UHQPN41756GRH8RMJI7U8RZSJA1DUT41", "2.N7ABKRBVPUF00LVXCYOJLI2", "3.IYRQ90JJVTIFBZX89"], "answerLink": "KQBPGOK9KY"}, {"questionId": 646, "questionText": "3D06FTI11F3WWHXK316K3HMS3MTJS9NPH34QQCXOGN3S2GUY1YO2GEU5QY34D4TDTOA2K5MC7HM1SIOAKLENSV8QI8BBI6VJN", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.1RALZYH7JFIZ5K0C3UMY2ZK5YD3Q", "wrongAnswers": ["1.P910W9NMVP52MTSYRR6W", "2.L8BTBMITX0EPT6SWPYU8"], "questionOptions": ["1.P910W9NMVP52MTSYRR6W", "2.L8BTBMITX0EPT6SWPYU8", "3.1RALZYH7JFIZ5K0C3UMY2ZK5YD3Q"], "answerLink": "LV5R11ZYK4"}, {"questionId": 647, "questionText": "PL3WEGO44EGQR1OV4BQ1UTV8WNGVYG3HVW081AIR3TR11N4OC7IS5T56EZJEVDWJS0791141EHF9IGUBSFMKW16Q77V4Y5VMAZB2ORLVYCVL6NFK9I6YO861F0M2", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.7JZXUMWZ4O4ON06XD", "wrongAnswers": ["2.VQ10QMQ2M1O46UCQRS3BKATAV", "3.GDID1JUKTU83O8E02V5U9ZERROZVBX"], "questionOptions": ["1.7JZXUMWZ4O4ON06XD", "2.VQ10QMQ2M1O46UCQRS3BKATAV", "3.GDID1JUKTU83O8E02V5U9ZERROZVBX"], "answerLink": "WLL7JS7L6S"}, {"questionId": 648, "questionText": "XB1Q2NKXBCXKMAYSQ7FL4LHRW85V528OE4E89IBPFS3DNE28V1DRML47U4YMNXATX48NBXM4VA0PCJRADZGG41G1CWLD", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "2.0OK7G09MAIP8YQJC1Q7P0V9KU", "wrongAnswers": ["1.S9DAKZSP8FVMQ6TK6P", "3.H4D4JUI0XRFAV2BC1M6V8E7GV4"], "questionOptions": ["1.S9DAKZSP8FVMQ6TK6P", "2.0OK7G09MAIP8YQJC1Q7P0V9KU", "3.H4D4JUI0XRFAV2BC1M6V8E7GV4"], "answerLink": "3QMNCZDTZ5"}, {"questionId": 649, "questionText": "L4FPJX968QIDLZPDZFYY8D9OOW4H3V989BJ1Y2V9DO1DFXE5XFOYRPR25Q930A7FDWVKGTOLWBC1QFXY4ZR87A6HTA4BNDV6E", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.7ZXT8MT874LDD65PJ8HJC", "wrongAnswers": ["1.PGJQ7MBONKYRIKOCIRQ0F", "2.Y89KUWKXP5QRS6JQ"], "questionOptions": ["1.PGJQ7MBONKYRIKOCIRQ0F", "2.Y89KUWKXP5QRS6JQ", "3.7ZXT8MT874LDD65PJ8HJC"], "answerLink": "30NWQB7HU2"}, {"questionId": 650, "questionText": "GFLMRQ3VF4A0N8GNF0BTTLX73D8XT5GAVJDW92ID32C9X25WVKEP1JG7MKEGI0DB2O170PVF9BXPHWDJ9M3S1OECLXAW14EUBVCID2R0JA", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.Q4TCG9158I8ZPNPNJ371CQ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.MV3A0PREQ1HIV83I", "2.EJ36CS42RJSIC2J0FVQYO"], "questionOptions": ["1.MV3A0PREQ1HIV83I", "2.EJ36CS42RJSIC2J0FVQYO", "3.Q4TCG9158I8ZPNPNJ371CQ"], "answerLink": "SE8GIZZE9F"}, {"questionId": 651, "questionText": "4LVZ4ITE253RXJSH8JDFWXTZY6EH8OUK2THMQ7JPJ30U3MGNCBMOOOIOJC8C6OVAH632", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.BTDSBLPTKBDO9A23CH1142Q37Z60", "wrongAnswers": ["1.1953O5VU1XDS8A15MFJ27XIN3ZJWR", "2.TAHX4IRVFCCFV0CCMFOA"], "questionOptions": ["1.1953O5VU1XDS8A15MFJ27XIN3ZJWR", "2.TAHX4IRVFCCFV0CCMFOA", "3.BTDSBLPTKBDO9A23CH1142Q37Z60"], "answerLink": "OL0XURBUAH"}, {"questionId": 652, "questionText": "BGDYP3M4O2KKUQ4KY1KT5PC2SRR7SE0NGW8XGD34N8PGD6FH9Y2R19C8XEJB81SWQQ4IKSTLYDEK", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.SNJI24VNR9RDQ8WYS70WUWXZD27G", "wrongAnswers": ["1.29AVN27F042OJ8CTM5O", "2.G6A6YFBOJLSB2ZGR8N215UF"], "questionOptions": ["1.29AVN27F042OJ8CTM5O", "2.G6A6YFBOJLSB2ZGR8N215UF", "3.SNJI24VNR9RDQ8WYS70WUWXZD27G"], "answerLink": "30J1VGMG6E"}, {"questionId": 653, "questionText": "L2Q27L2F2RB0PFNP0FGIQ2L7XI60J39F12FZNE5VSOG5FAZSP0S4LWT0EAZJCTO12OMQ4ZYHPRW2DBRNXGR6R52HR45CBR0OKKI", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.P0X7SNY7KRNAQZ4HJFZ7", "wrongAnswers": ["1.PR3BZ782MIFQ91ORSM6OE", "2.RVUJHH5J7ISN3RUEHPJV"], "questionOptions": ["1.PR3BZ782MIFQ91ORSM6OE", "2.RVUJHH5J7ISN3RUEHPJV", "3.P0X7SNY7KRNAQZ4HJFZ7"], "answerLink": "2EOX4WH8G3"}, {"questionId": 654, "questionText": "SUE8BFXD04XNCAIFGZ9T3MNBBBBNZ7XBEPNHTRZWKQLIYUYK7M9L7IN8WFQVRIRLAHPK11SGHMVPNZX41WK20UE1MVV4436OIX0X12H8W7ODYJBJZ9ZPIOF37FQ8XP9", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "2.6CPNWHDA32IL2ED40B4Q8OKLN1R", "wrongAnswers": ["1.BJP63RP9M0DC5KFV7ELJCV13KZ", "3.NYSA6IKN6N5KUJC9KH9J0JMGNIQHL"], "questionOptions": ["1.BJP63RP9M0DC5KFV7ELJCV13KZ", "2.6CPNWHDA32IL2ED40B4Q8OKLN1R", "3.NYSA6IKN6N5KUJC9KH9J0JMGNIQHL"], "answerLink": "S6MRVISUGF"}, {"questionId": 655, "questionText": "8J81CU46XPGF3195AYRK70MWLLDNRXO8BGPOTAGNAB27PKRITXEV5E84P8DSS2JVJ9ILMWMYBKIWL8EB8O3IPM2JP5E5OOIWDO0DW3R", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.URXI034DBT9S4WXXJK7", "wrongAnswers": ["2.23E8FFGN9CR0MDR0G", "3.TVGJD24L30A10KGIZ2G1ZVFSW1NUZ"], "questionOptions": ["1.URXI034DBT9S4WXXJK7", "2.23E8FFGN9CR0MDR0G", "3.TVGJD24L30A10KGIZ2G1ZVFSW1NUZ"], "answerLink": "EL6J100YEZ"}, {"questionId": 656, "questionText": "X72TZWIEF2PE3PEJNCDVA0LYZ9442XWMUQHESR0E3AWSZHV71NXXUCZ6Z0CSHM9LVS5HKVFAIPJ5KTI0XYEF9R0MAETRW5S51VB4DLH5D4640S16PEQF5IU", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.WF132MMVT1SAS908TQEQMCLGPZX", "wrongAnswers": ["1.XNIAB66WHSTX3I6ADDGXY6JVRX", "2.S79C6VBKE6VE8L5SWEDPC6I95"], "questionOptions": ["1.XNIAB66WHSTX3I6ADDGXY6JVRX", "2.S79C6VBKE6VE8L5SWEDPC6I95", "3.WF132MMVT1SAS908TQEQMCLGPZX"], "answerLink": "RPWIYFNPRL"}, {"questionId": 657, "questionText": "KTL2ZGHBX34II0MF8OE7GGU5LM71R915LYGFX2BR5T1IRNUQ69DX5YG5OXCPBDZ3WGCOHCL65F2VCKSHV388UQIVA4FE3X1OF679", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "2.MOXKZ8P3PKK6F8313JVPN5Q2FNHXAT", "wrongAnswers": ["1.36D11D8S8DI776RMSH3Z7A6RYGP24E", "3.9X0JU2G50QEK8LHQ4S9GPXBBS4UIVZ"], "questionOptions": ["1.36D11D8S8DI776RMSH3Z7A6RYGP24E", "2.MOXKZ8P3PKK6F8313JVPN5Q2FNHXAT", "3.9X0JU2G50QEK8LHQ4S9GPXBBS4UIVZ"], "answerLink": "FFMMSHJKRH"}, {"questionId": 658, "questionText": "L2DB3N7MCPRX74B6CB82OD77QP59PXAA413HJTK9FXWZV3LZ0OB8X4CU60GK0H3IHIILKL69SUKGM1PKIAGDTQ1GW", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "2.T8IJ8TZ2PM0UUPQ21X1FOOAXS6IKB", "wrongAnswers": ["1.JGDFGHI8X7JU6U21B4K5S1K", "3.MGUPB9FDNSWPYOA6PI2HXUY9A4FX3JNL"], "questionOptions": ["1.JGDFGHI8X7JU6U21B4K5S1K", "2.T8IJ8TZ2PM0UUPQ21X1FOOAXS6IKB", "3.MGUPB9FDNSWPYOA6PI2HXUY9A4FX3JNL"], "answerLink": "S0TY6PDD83"}, {"questionId": 659, "questionText": "7WM02AO7QOYCSLXHTWYMP4WGOENFQ87OFQ4U2QSQIQTVE2K7QMW83XIJQKRVQRE5T67OAUIOFI1C", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.4SQDEA5OWZSOEPMU0EUZDXHERZ", "wrongAnswers": ["2.EJZK0LYXRX3WWV75MQM3T3SNN8", "3.OH1YCE3JF0VYXVG010L7GD4QGA412"], "questionOptions": ["1.4SQDEA5OWZSOEPMU0EUZDXHERZ", "2.EJZK0LYXRX3WWV75MQM3T3SNN8", "3.OH1YCE3JF0VYXVG010L7GD4QGA412"], "answerLink": "HHZ4HIP0GD"}, {"questionId": 660, "questionText": "4JT634Q3F4Y02VZTM8TNK2DD8YY060ABZRCZR8AMY2AMFINW4ZXXTF25QC3A9BD4M0X524VVY7Q4D1KRW3BAM12LAC7WS141UDRIP2MTP3D9DHQZW7CE6X", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.9QKVUWIDD5BLZEZD5GS59XAV8D", "wrongAnswers": ["1.FMMMACPXPCKTBJCO0O16UW100", "2.GR8IV7OUUTZHVKXRDQKSN"], "questionOptions": ["1.FMMMACPXPCKTBJCO0O16UW100", "2.GR8IV7OUUTZHVKXRDQKSN", "3.9QKVUWIDD5BLZEZD5GS59XAV8D"], "answerLink": "IQVOU8HYM6"}, {"questionId": 661, "questionText": "IIUCBGDDDAMH1V91O64A2K4DYHEQDZ051D0JLGFHSHRRQJYC1P03GDOOQ9OGBJ9FIQ7DL08RY4EUCEL3XKSH9HO4S3", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.S1QQ2ET682NO0OD4PQV589Z0NH4TPQ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.7XB5O9OBQZPQ6DIWJQG9D", "2.XT8GOXHRX6AEVPK3KVF"], "questionOptions": ["1.7XB5O9OBQZPQ6DIWJQG9D", "2.XT8GOXHRX6AEVPK3KVF", "3.S1QQ2ET682NO0OD4PQV589Z0NH4TPQ"], "answerLink": "KN88EH68KQ"}, {"questionId": 662, "questionText": "GJ776H67X2Y9LGSF1RQH9POHH2TNMGDDV2TS8OIBT7KJKXYYUWH43FY9CMCM34ORGLM8ZRY43AAU536TNXR0Y", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.WVRLBSL73DK5DLFSXU3J3VLPEQCMR9", "wrongAnswers": ["1.FDU3OKNDVGMSLUA09VGZY43", "2.GW6TVU814VYG714IWY6P4J4V2Z7ZY"], "questionOptions": ["1.FDU3OKNDVGMSLUA09VGZY43", "2.GW6TVU814VYG714IWY6P4J4V2Z7ZY", "3.WVRLBSL73DK5DLFSXU3J3VLPEQCMR9"], "answerLink": "1Y9C7TYW1J"}, {"questionId": 663, "questionText": "WS9LSZ50GEVXVZ4W3FDHFBTKT2DE438LJUECNO0963440MO9X28LQKL4Z3WBTR57060HS1HMUNU2BPJVCB86P5V8KA", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "2.Y5C131FKIN5BO8DX2IJRBBDXVHRD4", "wrongAnswers": ["1.N06W89389970EQD8C", "3.J774PUIAULXZ11VHG4YO3L8CPRN0EMX7"], "questionOptions": ["1.N06W89389970EQD8C", "2.Y5C131FKIN5BO8DX2IJRBBDXVHRD4", "3.J774PUIAULXZ11VHG4YO3L8CPRN0EMX7"], "answerLink": "N3DXBLNHAI"}, {"questionId": 664, "questionText": "RX9AOSEQPWXFRH3DRFPHW48DMHKJHU7QMQF0M5ZPKT0V1QJ0MYURQJ8RFH8NPZPX3YQWMI2M1VWTNY05AGBVZYYAZAOCHYCPHZYI", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.RLLS67L3EM234Z14AJNPKMGJ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.9R6IUGNCAF71WNPIB3MDRGW8I1IE", "2.53P96CFL4SIOPG07U5VI6K99F3ILKFC"], "questionOptions": ["1.9R6IUGNCAF71WNPIB3MDRGW8I1IE", "2.53P96CFL4SIOPG07U5VI6K99F3ILKFC", "3.RLLS67L3EM234Z14AJNPKMGJ"], "answerLink": "XHXJDRSDFG"}, {"questionId": 665, "questionText": "J8KBKRH0TC4WZCVT69X5M3S54DTKA2AIDD96H8OTE81609XOCM0PAILZTQTF61CZ1YUKC7Y3RILFA8S98E0GET6XC30FUELMM1NT7O2FQCWVENZ9BZBT1J61CQ5", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.BTZUIAT2KH30H45A7TZ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.URW32XQ8Q118B7IIEFZX", "2.OIPNYZT4MNCPRCDZPM366"], "questionOptions": ["1.URW32XQ8Q118B7IIEFZX", "2.OIPNYZT4MNCPRCDZPM366", "3.BTZUIAT2KH30H45A7TZ"], "answerLink": "NQ55Z6IFZG"}, {"questionId": 666, "questionText": "NVHY253Y50JHAKCYKUBHNW2NFY31CVUEFI31G58TD1FPB5LZKY5VG034HEDI5RV8YCK9Q063GY2MD3SPBE1TA0YJ5ZNQCHXJXXV8WQ8", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.FXU3LS65R66KUN73PMVOL", "wrongAnswers": ["1.N5JXZYY40CB3IDK24QK2F", "2.7NIEVJ809SOLZIJVFYV6"], "questionOptions": ["1.N5JXZYY40CB3IDK24QK2F", "2.7NIEVJ809SOLZIJVFYV6", "3.FXU3LS65R66KUN73PMVOL"], "answerLink": "T5IK4N2MT0"}, {"questionId": 667, "questionText": "6Z3O9GEMHF1JIACWAEY8KAQUK3I7PUIK2YH3LE5RNNUDY6H4JP3NO9USAEFO65M9E9FUMG6EZ8D4HII4FDFQ2VLV5K6ITEFM1VJ0", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "2.2X854GOYA4Z9HYY9PCU893PO", "wrongAnswers": ["1.0DHKFUITJPGE0KE77834JPJI", "3.482NQWGOUIOWEEG5MRQM"], "questionOptions": ["1.0DHKFUITJPGE0KE77834JPJI", "2.2X854GOYA4Z9HYY9PCU893PO", "3.482NQWGOUIOWEEG5MRQM"], "answerLink": "FSCFS74OF1"}, {"questionId": 668, "questionText": "YQNRWL4Y1F9VZRIBIH65BTFAVUQ0U6MWIZJ2KFR7OX7JP7ARPS2HB2FDAXCFI3TH2", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.W5HV2R3W0I1QB1B5RPY1EZVJMF", "wrongAnswers": ["1.G85FGWCWHSXLGMVO62CEOQZT6FPX0NEX", "2.KMWUOQJOXK9TE8JPRF"], "questionOptions": ["1.G85FGWCWHSXLGMVO62CEOQZT6FPX0NEX", "2.KMWUOQJOXK9TE8JPRF", "3.W5HV2R3W0I1QB1B5RPY1EZVJMF"], "answerLink": "HVTUORUEJF"}, {"questionId": 669, "questionText": "JT4X1YBLBQH7GQ5H6OLLQIGXEWIZ3NVAGBMIS3X1MM2I57L0HXD51CPRXRQQQ9JCGLLCLC7ANY6JOU1LJ0UGDADDO5I2IWIV2JP4AO03F02MVVP", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.YKLNFABONCE1LF0ECCU9T636R", "wrongAnswers": ["1.36VSTXPLH86D43ZY44KPO4", "2.0IBFX56SNJGJ7RNFC7H48XZ5QY4"], "questionOptions": ["1.36VSTXPLH86D43ZY44KPO4", "2.0IBFX56SNJGJ7RNFC7H48XZ5QY4", "3.YKLNFABONCE1LF0ECCU9T636R"], "answerLink": "I9F2N1MM3V"}, {"questionId": 670, "questionText": "HNJM72ZGDRD2Z4V0EY0HB2KLSFEZ7VRW88QOW2AY8N89RKXX8RPM8DV76ZMIMQ8MVMD4L4KQ98AJAYYAKLYRKRNPV8KD72CVUAG71DI1V8F", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "2.TDH4EU384LXW1UW7CX", "wrongAnswers": ["1.8KWANR5ZYZV1NF0ITNWA28E", "3.QYENA86XZ25RU8X00F9G1WP60"], "questionOptions": ["1.8KWANR5ZYZV1NF0ITNWA28E", "2.TDH4EU384LXW1UW7CX", "3.QYENA86XZ25RU8X00F9G1WP60"], "answerLink": "1ZPBTVUOV7"}, {"questionId": 671, "questionText": "79UEGP642TTTLPZ279TH1QLSJF4CPHMXEK3YXIOP4RXGBFBNS4DBFE1PMFP1CDZZSLO4I7TY4JSD5L69ICCP8EVKLLHKAH29UUWLE4VUZXY", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.LNG5BFMP8A3VZLD9N6C7XMMKJMJ", "wrongAnswers": ["2.0PO6APKL53XP3ICMIZM", "3.7OFXI4VSXOFOYL6MCX89KDZFHYYD"], "questionOptions": ["1.LNG5BFMP8A3VZLD9N6C7XMMKJMJ", "2.0PO6APKL53XP3ICMIZM", "3.7OFXI4VSXOFOYL6MCX89KDZFHYYD"], "answerLink": "S85D0E12A4"}, {"questionId": 672, "questionText": "38P22D408VTMBMYFIYD87CARR5OAEFNFSLGNRFTGPTUUDYCMVYEOTI6I47IK45Y8D", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.ZUQTHCNQTXH339ERP0Z3MW", "wrongAnswers": ["1.JOZ1EIOPF16YS1Z2MODXITCMD2VA", "2.XHU3OIVKWB0P6NR65EQV6"], "questionOptions": ["1.JOZ1EIOPF16YS1Z2MODXITCMD2VA", "2.XHU3OIVKWB0P6NR65EQV6", "3.ZUQTHCNQTXH339ERP0Z3MW"], "answerLink": "3WQK8FXN5C"}, {"questionId": 673, "questionText": "PLK1JSITRMAQ0A5MJ4Z3OPJ2HRFJS5QPZRMX9E75SJXPJLTEU2YU1XLQPNLBU9P1ER2KRFTVYGZN12R4XMFQ0Y08SJ8UGTCLQNPDXEXL3ZX0", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.7L5QDE8U9I1UPMCX0P4", "wrongAnswers": ["1.MY6TI3UKLH1QCR12NHCNVLI64LNRY", "2.RGTAXEJ9C8B2TMTT5VS4WLW4MLGHRI"], "questionOptions": ["1.MY6TI3UKLH1QCR12NHCNVLI64LNRY", "2.RGTAXEJ9C8B2TMTT5VS4WLW4MLGHRI", "3.7L5QDE8U9I1UPMCX0P4"], "answerLink": "NJ4LMJ9EP8"}, {"questionId": 674, "questionText": "912T71Y4586ZU1VHN22Y3BL043S7787NAVQ75548YHFHGMVQ7RX263I2DA6IZY478JB3WXFC1JR11BTD12YP3CN39ALPDBI0M3RYWCI9VHFCLX1JF9MU2HRL", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.XA5J8I3J3IP62CZDA6QG3XSPCAC6", "wrongAnswers": ["1.SONYP62EJQ34FG25L242MA", "2.WYQHKXI9DOBGYQ74EKL5"], "questionOptions": ["1.SONYP62EJQ34FG25L242MA", "2.WYQHKXI9DOBGYQ74EKL5", "3.XA5J8I3J3IP62CZDA6QG3XSPCAC6"], "answerLink": "XTMT460622"}, {"questionId": 675, "questionText": "NNMVZ3VE89XHJTY92D6MO4MPQXY9VOAE4CPCOYRE8BDEWBJJEC4GQFQPSCI713PDTN8C1F3C1ZKBANJ22DFTVDKA7BM9C9GM57Q5UHS6JISTZ7DO4", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.37QJ7YWN56PB6YXY07RME2", "wrongAnswers": ["2.A9ZR6GOXMTQE5EPUBCB8WST3M7", "3.GDGWWWP0QHGFTSX6WCZKKK7O8VN4O59"], "questionOptions": ["1.37QJ7YWN56PB6YXY07RME2", "2.A9ZR6GOXMTQE5EPUBCB8WST3M7", "3.GDGWWWP0QHGFTSX6WCZKKK7O8VN4O59"], "answerLink": "E93225VMX0"}, {"questionId": 676, "questionText": "1C2TWQ0CQH6WDFACJYMJI6ZYQO0FPRW4NIS0JN8P9Q7A8TBJ2XLEJ3LO9XAJTCG651041PACSB9YXERKGUP53WOOGSSI44JDA43TZ65HZNEPQRVX80E5AX", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.ON8ZKWD158GNNSMH", "wrongAnswers": ["2.ZMB2UZMPTGIOA5Q1TY1HSM8", "3.N93PDVDS1VCSN77SLW9W340PV"], "questionOptions": ["1.ON8ZKWD158GNNSMH", "2.ZMB2UZMPTGIOA5Q1TY1HSM8", "3.N93PDVDS1VCSN77SLW9W340PV"], "answerLink": "NSQD0TCVPC"}, {"questionId": 677, "questionText": "KW6FJRNOTCT5CPLYCURQKSMC1CNFG145L3IYH6V4CBC3CR46PP2M2RZH6QZLI84Z9LRD4EFX866ZEVO3DLSBG9L6BZQXG7Y52NG6HXM", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.GS5XEC1ZBCS0F8JWSNAQQ4U85UWO", "wrongAnswers": ["1.EZ0TWB8QPWDDZ4DB", "2.CC0UCE1UVT8GD8UBFH8A8P54H16G"], "questionOptions": ["1.EZ0TWB8QPWDDZ4DB", "2.CC0UCE1UVT8GD8UBFH8A8P54H16G", "3.GS5XEC1ZBCS0F8JWSNAQQ4U85UWO"], "answerLink": "XCKS74PGGH"}, {"questionId": 678, "questionText": "TPTKYE1UC0XE5LUD9BBR4L19KVBMSCOYQX26WKISZXU8SNFJTYUQR19RCXYOAH9X3XO", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.AYK5X5HRN5T6VBCWYWAWASH14QRCV", "wrongAnswers": ["1.NGNYJAPDN3HXNWN7RWH7AKYVU40PM", "2.GIXNUK6GSCKJCFY71OEXWX"], "questionOptions": ["1.NGNYJAPDN3HXNWN7RWH7AKYVU40PM", "2.GIXNUK6GSCKJCFY71OEXWX", "3.AYK5X5HRN5T6VBCWYWAWASH14QRCV"], "answerLink": "L2W6P0PWZ2"}, {"questionId": 679, "questionText": "1M7KLCD0IH02808V52NSZWBYZBJETNJC6JG4NH8D9PNL8LYND8HYVE38SOY7MVO426CWXCPEGRT", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.4NAASWAID2QFH6CZIJ1CV80XIQ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.9TR7N8HS2UDYG8JLU9B1BNU84CE", "2.MFUM8JT7ZRP9NUOSSXF90FDG"], "questionOptions": ["1.9TR7N8HS2UDYG8JLU9B1BNU84CE", "2.MFUM8JT7ZRP9NUOSSXF90FDG", "3.4NAASWAID2QFH6CZIJ1CV80XIQ"], "answerLink": "9CNCU4JVJI"}, {"questionId": 680, "questionText": "JJB851JY1I5VPPGW9T98U213KV8C7GTLJ1UX78RK4DTLUPYJE6LXOOPZHV461YB0ARCY310FASE44KZEJIZ10841RZ", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.BPV5HOY58O38KPLOR3U5XBZGK2MPW", "wrongAnswers": ["2.4I7J0P4X210IQEGCBEXE8PRMNG5", "3.NE00Y5KB6Y4C9VONIXL40GRNCVIX21"], "questionOptions": ["1.BPV5HOY58O38KPLOR3U5XBZGK2MPW", "2.4I7J0P4X210IQEGCBEXE8PRMNG5", "3.NE00Y5KB6Y4C9VONIXL40GRNCVIX21"], "answerLink": "YS118U3RA6"}, {"questionId": 681, "questionText": "FJ0I85CR8CEMFA6SLGB8BP530SMFHPPQ4RDF8STXJA2D964G9NXQD3E2F18JBF4SSP6R23LA4467YYJQSUDT2EQ8I", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "1.0N4CF4HS5HWA6ZVIMU2DZHJK", "wrongAnswers": ["2.8XNO05V0M48NZV0O3", "3.OVCV8Q0GM4MDY5TK4RMUD4DGWRH446"], "questionOptions": ["1.0N4CF4HS5HWA6ZVIMU2DZHJK", "2.8XNO05V0M48NZV0O3", "3.OVCV8Q0GM4MDY5TK4RMUD4DGWRH446"], "answerLink": "8YB55OWPLT"}, {"questionId": 682, "questionText": "28CZHVHEGYLTTZEPHVLE7Q2XLNSEM63PWHCFMLBO7K2ABD3JS5K1L55ZZ0FSPFY4CS27MN1MN", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "2.RG6N66JSG0K0BRMVBSKOFGL7A4YIL5E2", "wrongAnswers": ["1.U0SH0F23M7V6CA8EJW", "3.K4NVD2OCG0EP6LJFN"], "questionOptions": ["1.U0SH0F23M7V6CA8EJW", "2.RG6N66JSG0K0BRMVBSKOFGL7A4YIL5E2", "3.K4NVD2OCG0EP6LJFN"], "answerLink": "BDVHKEMJLN"}, {"questionId": 683, "questionText": "XP8329KOQX6LKAF7R7H6OI8SX0E54M5IFKM96IPY2BYU23I1WGGLR5NNR6RJN82EQGEAJX7EA8", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "3.FENRB3O8Q8K8RBNZE", "wrongAnswers": ["1.AO88626GZEGO5AHQSNGOQAPCKBU", "2.4J1BLS3Y1AKRSVKCDR16YEQ7O"], "questionOptions": ["1.AO88626GZEGO5AHQSNGOQAPCKBU", "2.4J1BLS3Y1AKRSVKCDR16YEQ7O", "3.FENRB3O8Q8K8RBNZE"], "answerLink": "35UDHMRMZ7"}, {"questionId": 684, "questionText": "PWO9104GU8GTHVT25TMEI75MLAI7S6FVKA8O5JAS79O28SPMM4HJ2F3X2UTQ0IPHVASH7JHKHULAQD43DKD11NQGQQCPR5OIIKGZS2N6CH9", "questionCategory": "Associativa", "correctAnswers": "2.EVZ22EFUP42A3YE3OR72Y9E7", "wrongAnswers": ["1.P7L3XJEL6D5FNIVWE", "3.I7OFG97079Y9WKKSUAWV"], "questionOptions": ["1.P7L3XJEL6D5FNIVWE", "2.EVZ22EFUP42A3YE3OR72Y9E7", "3.I7OFG97079Y9WKKSUAWV"], "answerLink": "W84T3Q352I"}, {"questionId": 685, "questionText": "N3GBDMTTFZ4YIM8X9AXBZFB0U23QY21Y6SB44R4R0DR6NSST6OBYY03ROQRN8YPSHNJ7PX8C7NICJBPT1PJFSWBWUW2DN6DV051", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "3.OALJILJ1YD66GS0OFK8467VHCN", "wrongAnswers": ["1.8TMFOOMM82QZX1J0342M648", "2.FI39TQQVV32Z8PEFXL623U"], "questionOptions": ["1.8TMFOOMM82QZX1J0342M648", "2.FI39TQQVV32Z8PEFXL623U", "3.OALJILJ1YD66GS0OFK8467VHCN"], "answerLink": "UADAE6655W"}, {"questionId": 686, "questionText": "UOAFOAJ7C65D3QFPVOAC24GQHTVRH41Q7G0AR73HI7J6LUF7SCF9AVYKM3CCH71U1BXDB7AJL8WBT9B2GOX0JYG0QSZ29UHKO7UCG6NIR8WM6A8CN", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "2.DOUSBI922MEAU8TLZR9Z4A", "wrongAnswers": ["1.HZLE69RPDXHEA63PH9", "3.6TAT1SULN7W7TDJW26AS0XN"], "questionOptions": ["1.HZLE69RPDXHEA63PH9", "2.DOUSBI922MEAU8TLZR9Z4A", "3.6TAT1SULN7W7TDJW26AS0XN"], "answerLink": "3XC8WCL155"}, {"questionId": 687, "questionText": "G44XMZ6R9BOO7N34I8TONI65678TAO1FAZBQN5OYQEZN0RKD1MDE37FNCQ88XV6T5ZA29UHR8TAGK0K7XDK05C8QWXE7YEN75MNZSMBN2FGI4WPLPY0", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "3.FG00ZH3Q4EXXYXW4P8FA9HR13MC9", "wrongAnswers": ["1.0H8P5TUF97LQ1LVG9R83XQ", "2.X9R61JWKIGQYTHFFOVT87Q9ILIQ"], "questionOptions": ["1.0H8P5TUF97LQ1LVG9R83XQ", "2.X9R61JWKIGQYTHFFOVT87Q9ILIQ", "3.FG00ZH3Q4EXXYXW4P8FA9HR13MC9"], "answerLink": "YWTNGCWMXN"}, {"questionId": 688, "questionText": "4GD59F1OF2DGT44U90TE6YX4XOUYVXHT0XHN152VVENVLUQSTOSA92IW9FJVVOK4JP8FX5FFHLLJOL84YA0YL5TEEOK7W3EK3SGIRA8IP6", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "2.MKMYPX7GJBBR4GB9E0FK", "wrongAnswers": ["1.93HGB4OWK0HVOMYBQ5AUJRM", "3.JY2Z1LRLPK8R9O146LWKUWGF4G"], "questionOptions": ["1.93HGB4OWK0HVOMYBQ5AUJRM", "2.MKMYPX7GJBBR4GB9E0FK", "3.JY2Z1LRLPK8R9O146LWKUWGF4G"], "answerLink": "5JB8ASU9FY"}, {"questionId": 689, "questionText": "UOAUM3PBTQBSHHS52QIMBE375KS9B7H1JWO27SBNXMUW0KII49A88D1Z76X4NBVTEEFSRNMOSTPVT9HAF7YNTVOPP0BN6N13TIPWOPGCWTWQT827JAXOVQD35", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "2.BND2NET8V8VZARVKN90FS6UDSS", "wrongAnswers": ["1.55D1D87ZLCDK1RVUJUXT", "3.J4NVGAN0052VTA6090HFM5"], "questionOptions": ["1.55D1D87ZLCDK1RVUJUXT", "2.BND2NET8V8VZARVKN90FS6UDSS", "3.J4NVGAN0052VTA6090HFM5"], "answerLink": "H0EMWD76CC"}, {"questionId": 690, "questionText": "RX0VBZB4NQA7EAHHU2M23WBVH3I5ZOZCS5RPMDY2T7EUTWQS3020VXGZ11J4ABBYZJ2SMWLB8R1GUG2G58X0F6QJW60CIERLKVK5J9HXX7JE", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "2.N0YC9A4D889ITWCEXT655L45ZUSESU6", "wrongAnswers": ["1.ZE8W0E300GAO4QIH4E", "3.F1S6PJ6KCICTFUU9"], "questionOptions": ["1.ZE8W0E300GAO4QIH4E", "2.N0YC9A4D889ITWCEXT655L45ZUSESU6", "3.F1S6PJ6KCICTFUU9"], "answerLink": "S3OUSYS72C"}, {"questionId": 691, "questionText": "1D8V9F04P8W9SRJWS9FK9P3EKY7AAXRFWWHYHS1DRFIX43J7XE6M31JLO61FLTHBMFLE9MEZS5M", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "1.0KTD7WJ6YDFYBK9FWC3MGHMO2", "wrongAnswers": ["2.VZVT98WY3OSQBZ3UTTAZSZWBIC0", "3.PKAFV8K9KSE0DCORIY7F993WM"], "questionOptions": ["1.0KTD7WJ6YDFYBK9FWC3MGHMO2", "2.VZVT98WY3OSQBZ3UTTAZSZWBIC0", "3.PKAFV8K9KSE0DCORIY7F993WM"], "answerLink": "93SYBF761R"}, {"questionId": 692, "questionText": "BZZD0GO1P8V6C5Y1THHCMFMGEJC4NIAO3UZ8BU9PRTBPJGCXVZZH41GVP610H0OYNG39KRJ62JGUD0P5W4S7IH9VWJONOF7WPEOW76W", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "2.BD3CHC5WKT52I0WFAYZN08ANR7J06", "wrongAnswers": ["1.77ES4XGL64R6LT5B4D901IHMY", "3.CQ9MUF0J4MRJQO4SFA8TC"], "questionOptions": ["1.77ES4XGL64R6LT5B4D901IHMY", "2.BD3CHC5WKT52I0WFAYZN08ANR7J06", "3.CQ9MUF0J4MRJQO4SFA8TC"], "answerLink": "V91PWDXUB5"}, {"questionId": 693, "questionText": "XBE8Y743JQUH0A3WOL1KMG6E4VOL0YTZF31ZE4V3V9N539DOZHHCUM7TTB101PLK3C0PHYS9A3XMOF6N8316YV2738C4JZJTD82ALGGP364XYBPSYI86AV", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "3.6YQL52NO51VS4ILV1YHS7L", "wrongAnswers": ["1.W2FSA7HDN9UFYRW0LRTODD14G", "2.EWEPE4BVA90ML4SY"], "questionOptions": ["1.W2FSA7HDN9UFYRW0LRTODD14G", "2.EWEPE4BVA90ML4SY", "3.6YQL52NO51VS4ILV1YHS7L"], "answerLink": "JM80J4RT41"}, {"questionId": 694, "questionText": "GKJ4DF5UAHF8L1VY65BO3MW99EFRHCYWAIIGCT3M1RVP9EW0IOA7DIFN8CU7ZXTFK6LWMX7TNHBQM1RAM1AXYAPWCVBJS2X", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "3.0J504QTV5YV1BGFBDB89QB17IEX", "wrongAnswers": ["1.XM4WOP9WSDAPADUP80POYIQGLJW4RV", "2.3D70CIHBY0SREN7ZVBIE"], "questionOptions": ["1.XM4WOP9WSDAPADUP80POYIQGLJW4RV", "2.3D70CIHBY0SREN7ZVBIE", "3.0J504QTV5YV1BGFBDB89QB17IEX"], "answerLink": "BV6GDZUOZI"}, {"questionId": 695, "questionText": "4B8UH9HP3JMVILQIGGKVDNSC3E59BP392BJ4S777PW37BETORELMRFFXDHYEUG4VY25CYBU8", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "1.HT0KUKIPU63QQZ6112AVXE9RDTGLS05", "wrongAnswers": ["2.VJ0QCW55ABWBHZ1DSNGT8S1G2QO", "3.ARUBMTVYKKS7SOYA0I5AXJ5"], "questionOptions": ["1.HT0KUKIPU63QQZ6112AVXE9RDTGLS05", "2.VJ0QCW55ABWBHZ1DSNGT8S1G2QO", "3.ARUBMTVYKKS7SOYA0I5AXJ5"], "answerLink": "NZT95MYK8J"}, {"questionId": 696, "questionText": "VJB54GO7DBVWGZHEWCD2SI3TOEBM508O18EF7RW7VQF6QC1QQX93BK9RGR8BXKQ856WUTBLT3GHPYOAWOC7CC0C5AZCKQCZCDVRRDJWYDPIW7N5DXUBB3AV9", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "1.3NY3G5K4KK7M876Y3", "wrongAnswers": ["2.NAPZH52DCY3DRDUSYGM2K8TMZG4T1A", "3.O2EWSUYJYSDYLUK4RKF"], "questionOptions": ["1.3NY3G5K4KK7M876Y3", "2.NAPZH52DCY3DRDUSYGM2K8TMZG4T1A", "3.O2EWSUYJYSDYLUK4RKF"], "answerLink": "4UIDPMJC5K"}, {"questionId": 697, "questionText": "MD7PSP6OQ7G9RQBZJFZ9T63Q21WJJ07IGZS6CHUS6KI8MVWUTHJ73L6G6VD0ZMEJGTTKIHIE0CRAR3N32JY6CFADQ", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "1.X9SU91NTSGQJDJWW8", "wrongAnswers": ["2.JFAJ951I0DZC3NYTUHRZHAFHI51Z", "3.RB3CLS92UG2FGZIO5SO8H"], "questionOptions": ["1.X9SU91NTSGQJDJWW8", "2.JFAJ951I0DZC3NYTUHRZHAFHI51Z", "3.RB3CLS92UG2FGZIO5SO8H"], "answerLink": "BPV5CVQZ4J"}, {"questionId": 698, "questionText": "58S3BW4FYFFEYJV4AWUWL8FVWLE7LZHHRBMS3YFBXNXAN95ILKQNBK8F7XVFAR61O81IH3X06AIJTLCZASCB2YERR", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "3.DPDGLJZDCI36P91DU6ISA8", "wrongAnswers": ["1.89UGFGZM2IHBM2W2X2Q0LK", "2.Y26NVEVE18HCX4JZDSS9YR2"], "questionOptions": ["1.89UGFGZM2IHBM2W2X2Q0LK", "2.Y26NVEVE18HCX4JZDSS9YR2", "3.DPDGLJZDCI36P91DU6ISA8"], "answerLink": "2RETF3H6JE"}, {"questionId": 699, "questionText": "UE41EH0VXIC02Y4EAHB6Q6UFLQLAYANMF88NKWA0345GZ3YZOYQD4DXFZDVGYRLE9KHY1N5DNDTULEGA01A214ZD9U4QKH06AKXAUYIAHYRD4J1O5Q", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "1.SCOBNH2WBLFVYVMVVHRSOVDR", "wrongAnswers": ["2.XN14M0PZO76DZNZUHARNCABHVJGS5", "3.A4GN8OODURHPL91UWG"], "questionOptions": ["1.SCOBNH2WBLFVYVMVVHRSOVDR", "2.XN14M0PZO76DZNZUHARNCABHVJGS5", "3.A4GN8OODURHPL91UWG"], "answerLink": "F752HIKTE5"}, {"questionId": 700, "questionText": "3VWQ0ORQZK2FHC32KAPE81ZQ6MFRPQL4YYLI5AUQUM5MIHJXEXYCBLE8R4483YY34DYIWR3C6UJHPIPEF7WFLMSHESOV63D3O77005NWI9RZSURGJGZHJOW", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "1.HBM4O2T2PZYH76HDUUBJE", "wrongAnswers": ["2.6906ZTSVK9V7SH4HFGQ9A1FL008H1", "3.M5ELJ7J11W0R7VDS8T07TSE5WF"], "questionOptions": ["1.HBM4O2T2PZYH76HDUUBJE", "2.6906ZTSVK9V7SH4HFGQ9A1FL008H1", "3.M5ELJ7J11W0R7VDS8T07TSE5WF"], "answerLink": "SHFL9R5OXK"}, {"questionId": 701, "questionText": "RMJRXB6YHXDEFQZ8FGGXK4PUN0X6QQSC7WGL15VTU9D93KOSY2B1ZL3419R1MHPIRWAN126E4SEHA9J4DZ7KQAT0JULUD4D3GEZXI1I3GQKI7SDFKM9LRU8", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "2.S3A6KPE9CQOMVOVI6", "wrongAnswers": ["1.F4T98W75ADAZYB0R539BJ7ERT", "3.YKSULILJ7JSAOR55Q37C"], "questionOptions": ["1.F4T98W75ADAZYB0R539BJ7ERT", "2.S3A6KPE9CQOMVOVI6", "3.YKSULILJ7JSAOR55Q37C"], "answerLink": "EFHYS5M3VV"}, {"questionId": 702, "questionText": "YN04CXV5QKQYHLESO5P38DN6Z9QC1L72YV0ILEG8EVKQYAPXDFCFIMPGLRDNLUEMMXYMVOMSEMIP53HMK7JA4G1YPVTETPSJZICV93QV3X5DFCP4MM1Z0N8VH2MB", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "3.RKMKALLHTAFBZH4XGHO1RFZ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.DD0C4M0CFYV8U563L0GWR6VD", "2.HHE1O8PQBKP4J3Z3JKXSC64QVZ49KDUD"], "questionOptions": ["1.DD0C4M0CFYV8U563L0GWR6VD", "2.HHE1O8PQBKP4J3Z3JKXSC64QVZ49KDUD", "3.RKMKALLHTAFBZH4XGHO1RFZ"], "answerLink": "R7IGCN2OOH"}, {"questionId": 703, "questionText": "MS3C3D39SQOFP9FUR7GWXPSSE1BV078WBOH5E3KGBDAEAG96PVENZZHWIYEDA9P4UL7VW4O9DIADAZ73HBC4X497U9YF", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "3.LD7DXJH7LYACG6S00", "wrongAnswers": ["1.JD17SI5UIAZXWHQN1TH", "2.OF0SQ7R0111JLSHG972ABI8HMMX7F9"], "questionOptions": ["1.JD17SI5UIAZXWHQN1TH", "2.OF0SQ7R0111JLSHG972ABI8HMMX7F9", "3.LD7DXJH7LYACG6S00"], "answerLink": "9O0KYD5Y7H"}, {"questionId": 704, "questionText": "9T8CS5R2S0RHOGLUHS9CQPIDDWMZS1FGAF20PKVF2ZSRJHZKV6ZP58FBT7SY328LSUE", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "1.7SO82GQK2Z6WN1R5NO8RPZWU8", "wrongAnswers": ["2.93CVDDSTUCX2H9D7GL", "3.NN1A85ZRYNBK1KPR6ZMJYALX13GNW"], "questionOptions": ["1.7SO82GQK2Z6WN1R5NO8RPZWU8", "2.93CVDDSTUCX2H9D7GL", "3.NN1A85ZRYNBK1KPR6ZMJYALX13GNW"], "answerLink": "OZ8LPG5E5W"}, {"questionId": 705, "questionText": "CVEGAOG9MNIAIHEPLFI871GH1VQYB0BM7DVIK8WQ6CWQG98QYI0BVDYZN9A941VUI9KCMFX", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "2.7XEP0Z9PBTUZ9WUPA8I9BU1VG", "wrongAnswers": ["1.FGWQ4UKWJRUGQ0EN39QH7W9MS2YLIDP", "3.2LIX4PTU7BPX8P4EBI"], "questionOptions": ["1.FGWQ4UKWJRUGQ0EN39QH7W9MS2YLIDP", "2.7XEP0Z9PBTUZ9WUPA8I9BU1VG", "3.2LIX4PTU7BPX8P4EBI"], "answerLink": "GZRATFGFCN"}, {"questionId": 706, "questionText": "PT10CY24LN1GMWVNB32JGC7NAL2CKM7UCGCH4PBF0GC2BP1JILY0OH155MCVIWTZPEA81AZ3", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "1.ETQJQ0P5MHSH61OL7TT", "wrongAnswers": ["2.UK0Y3O08GPL1TX4UNR0AIS", "3.PVM4U5UC5443A2BT2SLM0QFQMYQ3"], "questionOptions": ["1.ETQJQ0P5MHSH61OL7TT", "2.UK0Y3O08GPL1TX4UNR0AIS", "3.PVM4U5UC5443A2BT2SLM0QFQMYQ3"], "answerLink": "5GU843A2SF"}, {"questionId": 707, "questionText": "UJB5VE2EMVYP6L0ZEX7YXNJG0TWTVRTUHHGO12VEBP9KMPULVSVMF6Y6ZCDT4JHPDMM1CDEGJFSYP24", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "3.NPXXV3985QC3W420P", "wrongAnswers": ["1.HXM879XPPD8Q1MQDUNLTT65Y", "2.PGPDOQW6KR9C66FAWQQ8"], "questionOptions": ["1.HXM879XPPD8Q1MQDUNLTT65Y", "2.PGPDOQW6KR9C66FAWQQ8", "3.NPXXV3985QC3W420P"], "answerLink": "QY7MYCAOP6"}, {"questionId": 708, "questionText": "RBDFALDK75D5E7JA36M3I0ASC21786T6YSLVKCANUO6B091GMP85L1IFRF9MNH4S1G1O", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "1.34AWONAZ2G72CVQ3BDBR18L8", "wrongAnswers": ["2.E9LJMHKFZJ1JPUBO5DNQ0YZ8F6A", "3.ZRQOH30XXX5RS97E"], "questionOptions": ["1.34AWONAZ2G72CVQ3BDBR18L8", "2.E9LJMHKFZJ1JPUBO5DNQ0YZ8F6A", "3.ZRQOH30XXX5RS97E"], "answerLink": "UWTU37091J"}, {"questionId": 709, "questionText": "ORKQ2RMTZJDXZRIFX5BPZ4G596KI77F19T8AHSVD0ZTLU000W64MAU5CGG9WBJVM4IQSEZ96", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "3.U3Y3V49YBST9EN1AYRHCXUIQ", "wrongAnswers": ["1.1JBCP4MDPC4G4YH57E7T0", "2.J49JLF4THVYRZH654JSEKDMKYK87WV"], "questionOptions": ["1.1JBCP4MDPC4G4YH57E7T0", "2.J49JLF4THVYRZH654JSEKDMKYK87WV", "3.U3Y3V49YBST9EN1AYRHCXUIQ"], "answerLink": "51DDZ8XGJH"}, {"questionId": 710, "questionText": "71VOGG9OTDHMIXCVNPP6ABZ9ETJ2KNBKODZPHXYSBDE3GVHEIZPFUFBWU9GXV5K655V6YH3O63P259A9G9XXZ9GJVTG7NU8FD7RTYCTOT02AWG4EKCJKUD52ZSRS", "questionCategory": "NFOT", "correctAnswers": "2.VGJOXZ4B1YTRC44T7E2VLWSN", "wrongAnswers": ["1.71Z923QKKFZLAQSPFMVIWH9", "3.I6PCE63FKY1GZHYD1CJUEDFZDIVEPVN2"], "questionOptions": ["1.71Z923QKKFZLAQSPFMVIWH9", "2.VGJOXZ4B1YTRC44T7E2VLWSN", "3.I6PCE63FKY1GZHYD1CJUEDFZDIVEPVN2"], "answerLink": "G8R7X80H69"}]